[
    {
        "idx": "1",
        "question": "U A E E K G R S R Z V K S M R D S A X O T Z T E R Q H X H C K D N K D\nD X Y E N T H U S I A S M F T V J L D B U W L B L J D L C B J I E S Z\nA P L V B D Q I E D L N N V E D G Q N V O P M L Z J B U C Z O G P V R\nA B I X K K A W X S T M I S Q N W U C A N B K U B V C Y C M N C B V U\nR O C B S D A E N S X K C R S S H D Q D P L R Y S W V Z Y J Y E Y O K\nE G B Y C F H I Y Q B Y S T Z X E E N M T M C Y Q Y K B E Y Q Z B Q K\nS K N O X W L U S T E R Y H L K U U H U G U A S X F K R H T O U R W T\nT W W F I M X T K K F F S T Z D J Z D U R X W D L I S I T G K T F W X\nO C B Z I R E X V B T Y Y O S B M Z K O S U J J I L F X Y M N I Z L X\nR R J O I V H B L M D K E V I E Z I K Y H M K T N F V R B U D M Z W W\nA V Q P R J E U E P B I T H D B D N P K X F E Y C J V J I F O K P O I\nT P L G S U W K H L E D T J V K Q X D T D J S O G E O Y Q S Z H B L T\nI O H C V W J D S Y G N Z H F N K Z U T S P G Z B H O V C U H X G F H\nO X B R A X L D L B Q O S B Z R A Q P I C C R G X D J P Y P A M R G I\nN X Y U K V E D O O D C Q I I O V T S W B G C T M L Q D J P X F P R N\nO V T G D E G R E E U V Z K O H Z P N N E D W H T K R S O O C Y I V A\nR K X R E Q T O Y R Q E D L T N N X R C L E O L S T K Q H S P V U E R\nS Z D E G S C O G W X I H W T O W F Q L X X N D G B P D M E D X F Y R\nE U A Y Z C O O H H O E Y N I Z M S N J E T K S M U P K T L F V B T O\nF A S M K S C Q H R Z S X D Q H S L S B M K M P U R P O N A Y J M D W\nL K G K V G M H W Z E E R K W O X W Z O B J G C S O M V B D P G G V S\nS U C S W W N R F P C S F D Z G R Q Y P P S H X I N D I U N V V S Y A\nI T A X K E J G D S S O Z Z D E S V O C D I R R C Q H D I L F Z N R T\nZ V M Z N W A F R L V V Y U D Z Q E M V O I K N C A C R N K K R V E Z\nA M D A Z X P I D L V Y L X A H L D N E V O S H W B R M U Z H M N A B\nR I O V R E S E R C O V S H W R T U T S I A V T U H S H D H T K C Z A\nC N B N T I A V A Q Z J E J V X E M P N I Z K M R U D O A V Y W P X T\nP K B I X J R T Q A J W R F T K G L R X P T D M H I J N X Q J H U G F\nR C X C T G L J S B Z M F A S B S W E D V D I Z L S B L K H R T Z R U\nK S U A Y P E W L W C X Y D J O O O F G F T Q V A Q M U L G N U U V W\nE V I T A T I M I X P K I Q R P G E N I A N J H E E Z U E M A W N C J\nP X P Y H P Q H E D E L D N P I W E V P A N I S Q G Z K M V B F W P S\nV O Q U P F K C F X O G U Y U V N Q M G O F T K S A K X L O X H Y V Q\nO B A C S O B V L C Q W E G T T K K F O N M K R C B H L E V H K M N V\nI W H V T H Q K I B S M K X P Y R M M R V F N S L Q T F I G Z G Y H N",
        "answer": "[[DEGREE, DISTRIBUTE, DRINK, ELEGANT, ENTHUSIASM, HORSE, IMITATIVE, LUSTER, MUSIC, NARROW, PENSION, RESERVOIR, RESTORATION, SENSITIVE, SUPPOSE, WITHIN]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "35"
    },
    {
        "idx": "2",
        "question": "M R X K Y M T Z S M W F\nF F Y C H Z H A P D Y Q\nL E M I H N D R R A C N\nE G E S Z O O F O C P Y\nV Y Q D T L G L U P E X\nR R H Z I C Q F N Y T B\nF P E U P N O U D M C F\nH D M Q Q M G N I W R W\nR A P H R I Y S E M E A\nN G Q A M J N Z P D L M\nC F O J R L J M J M A E\nQ H V P V G Q T X W X X",
        "answer": "[[FEEDING, LEVER, POUND, RELAX]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "3",
        "question": "I H A V Z A D M A P C G D P H\nF A T W F X Q C Y X O D T F I\nT J P V N R F A I R Z O M B P\nW I E L F S B R X L L A A L H\nT K R S O M P O O J M I R S F\nO L C H R O L A L N W V N Z J\nD Q U K M I R P N S T A O Z Z\nO D S U A N E E E I T A F G E\nR R S T T V T W S Q I E L L L\nR I I U I J K K T S R C R S E\nY D O W O K L I M K E D C A V\nV O N K N N M J U F P R V O E\nG J S E B M O M Z Z K F O Q N\nX T A H C O Y C X P V G C P H\nQ Z Z Y I N S C R I P T I O N",
        "answer": "[[BOLSTER, ELEVEN, FORMATION, FRONTAL, INSCRIPTION, PERCUSSION]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "15"
    },
    {
        "idx": "4",
        "question": "P W G G L L Z H P W J Z X P Z L X E Z G Q U\nQ W Z Z S D D L L Z N Y E F B S N Z U D I M\nN R R W H F Q A X I K W U R G I H F H Z I X\nE O K D G B W F G Q B O X L L F N T E Y E X\nS H I V E R L Q D N Z S I C Q Q M W F Y H S\nN O G P I U P D J A W G N B E A C U J N E D\nG P U L O H R F Z M L I Y P W W P O E K D R\nI G P N O K V E S H Q K G D S M C U J N H I\nS I Z T D S N E B O I N T I M A T E W N J B\nQ O W B R R S S D U Z V S C H V V O U E U M\nM B X Q J U F R R N K F L D P G J E P A J V\nK T Z R V D R A D B S E K E D F E C U O K B\nK A W V P J P B P L M S F N G Z D L S H D J\nF N E T W T M G A I Q S X E G Y J R S Y V S\nC H N J W A P O S A B E I D V J Z Z Q K A A\nX L L A U O F H Z X I N R T R E S Z Y C G E\nW T T U O S M T U E P T W L I U P F I Q U B\nA E S E E O T A T Z S I V F R H Z Q H N H O\nR F F I X O P Q N W H A P Y K D I U B J P I\nP K B V B T E J S J Q L F M D X X T R B L P\nY F P Y N Z D T E S B K G Y G G W O I P Y Y\nW K J H G P K V H O U L K A Q D A A M G B U",
        "answer": "[[BLEMISH, ESSENTIAL, GLOSS, HOUND, INCLINE, INTIMATE, OBTAIN, REBUKE, SHIVER, TREASURY, WATER]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "22"
    },
    {
        "idx": "5",
        "question": "D G D Q V E I C T S H T X L H Q X F G W I B G X T\nQ H H I C Q Y B R L N W Q M F L A X V H J G I C P\nH M L D X F E R W E O W O L I V E P E Y F Z F Z R\nA Q C Q C K U Z M P I Q C O I N E F T G P O P E P\nM E M W R K D H Q J M N G P L M V Q J T L E E E J\nJ V T U G N C H J S W J F G X G J P F G T W K K A\nB P G W D A V Q L G R P D X J K E Q U A L L Y X E\nF O F R T U U J H E Q W X O P T O G W F E E J Q L\nD C V T Z F R F T X I H T E R A R Q U R N V C E A\nQ F A P D Q M C K P S G J G Q N V D J B I K R F F\nB J T U A T E N W E L L B O L C R O K X A C V M N\nD D X R J S U C P R S K L B G W Z O L M C A R I E\nG N I G D O L G C I W O X L A I R R L U X A C S K\nA Y J P W W Q T N M R D O J J N T O S Q N B T H Z\nR A L U L L E C F E Y N Z G R X Y E Z J U T B D C\nN L H D C E T N J N F V U U E R H C N G F Z A V D\nP A S S A B L E X T J F Q J U G X E A U H Q Q R R\nM I Z A A N O R C P Q K D U V C F U L R R Q R Q Y\nC S U I I K C L A R X X Q R G G D A A M V E Y Q U\nV C P Y W A V B I Q L I E Q F J Y K C Z E R E I R\nH V E M E N E L D C Z G A B V D K M S X L T J Y L\nZ X F X B S V E A G G X A B G T M X Y A Q E C S Z\nH L C O N X N P Y O B V U L T Q J O L C H E U Q N\nQ K D P C Q A X S Z A L X R H U C B W Y G J T W E\nX N X E S P E C I A L L Y B W C H X A M V S V I U",
        "answer": "[[ATTACHMENT, CELLULAR, EQUALLY, ESPECIALLY, EXPERIMENT, HELMET, LODGING, OLIVE, PASSABLE, TENURE, VOLUNTARY]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "25"
    },
    {
        "idx": "6",
        "question": "L N C K X X W L C O T O G M C D K T X L\nF O X O E Z H T M P S D D W M V Y J Y D\nN I P A L L N S O L P I Z G D R A U J O\nI T A G T O I K H H E J M P H V T E I V\nA C W C E D R F P X N Q B K K Y Z O A Q\nP U Y R H T D B X M A R E W S R Z P A Z\nA D E O A S E S Z M N M G U Q I Q G Q S\nR N B B T W F P P W C Z S L A V E R Y P\nE I O S J P E L U S E M L Q B Z C D U E\nJ P X C D D N W J U S B J M N D X Q H C\nF U N U L U S P X B N C J N E A L Y M U\nZ B W R X T I A F N T P L Y X Y T A N L\nM Q D E F I V X O F O W D C Z S X G N A\nD N O U G H E C Q R R W M W S J Y S A T\nK B E U K S Q J Y U T V G H U U H X A I\nI Q X W D B Z O L N M M A X P W L Z Z O\nP Q B W R D C G L O C A L I T Y F F Q N\nM A V Q E D B B M F S Z R Y U J S V E V\nE I I C C B O J Y F J G G T D G I A V U\nQ G H N E C Z Y Z X F I R U W J D X F C",
        "answer": "[[COLOR, DEFENSIVE, INDUCTION, LOCALITY, OBSCURE, PAINFUL, PENANCE, SLAVERY, SPECULATION]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "20"
    },
    {
        "idx": "7",
        "question": "T I Q H W V V T T I N G C R U A G B B X B W F H G G O P T Q\nA N Y C B K R U D I Z K F V M F Q A A W K O P U W D N J H D\nX H K T N O Q V H E N L U P M O N X N I W X L V Y X Y E S T\nB Z R E Q J L G A S U G Q K N A Z M Z M A D C S S L V X U L\nU C R K F E X X Q J J R Q S Q V L X H N Q S P N Z U P B H L\nH O U S D T X B J Z E D R Z I W H I T P Q K E V C C X Y G I\nC N A H Q L U H W A G A Y K F W H D C C W V S A E D R C X N\nN C O Y I A V R L D J W S Y H J E X M E T X D S V L F X F O\nX E B W Z E X Y H F T P S X F Z X O P T P J T X J D E J G N\nD R H V Y B C A E N X Z Y I Y R F D L R X O W B U N D L E N\nX N W M H Q L K L X H C W H P U J A U S F P P L D B Y O Q C\nG S B Y H X I U Y F L V V Z D W S O I H G H M P S C Z K P D\nF H E T F R Z V S S N S F X G M R D U V D Z Z A R Q A C Q F\nE Z N A I B A E D T J U F E W P D X M R Y W Q W E E U H V X\nE J G M Y W N G B W E K J E Z O S H Q L R U C I J G S Q Y J\nL O Q R A U F E X O D R O Y N D W C K U B K R H V P D S X H\nI Q Q E N I N R R Q X N W S J R V L P Y Q H V I J D S I V E\nN X A C R G V P O U R Z R U B Z J S S T U V U C S U P K Y I\nG Y G B R W J L G I B Q P X M V F Q S Y L L O G I S M H Q K\nX A L A Q N L U J O W Y R E L Q D E P G D Y E V P J P G Z B\nX C V Z E W S N R Q P F O C L K P V P L O S H B J P D Q H G\nH E S W Y U O K C U B T J C A T X K P I F A L T H O U G H O\nD W W N K I N V T L P Z E J C U B L W R Z S K M F O X C A I\nX P T L C P D Z O M U D C T U B Y I X M V P S X R X U N B M\nW V N M L P A Y R M W F T O K C Z Z S Y F I F W M I T P Y G\nL O I U U D T T X P Q I I Y H A Y L T M O C X M M R T A D E\nL K Z T J I O T R W X P L A B W H Q J N A E G Y T H K E M E\nU W D I P Q U Q D S Z J E R C J O P F Y T J Q E N K E J J S\nW K J R I E Q G P I R J W O S Y B D E N Y W Q Z D C A L Y B\nW O E V W L J C Z K E K W Q X I B S F Y Z C P M M N L C M J",
        "answer": "[[ALTHOUGH, BLUSTER, BUNDLE, CASTLE, CONCERN, ENGRAVED, FEELING, MALICE, OPPRESSIVE, PROJECTILE, SEIZING, SKETCH, SPICE, SYLLOGISM]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "30"
    },
    {
        "idx": "8",
        "question": "G G I K I X O R S X N J J O Q S B X N U Z P\nF W L Q L Y M P A K I W Y E U P E L U G D J\nC M D O R S Q A A V A W H R H B A J Y S D T\nJ K O B A F S P Y P T W I A A C B F O I B A\nA S M E C K B O X Q E T G V E A T J T T B O\nE E O X E T N H D Z R C R G Z V F W U A F Q\nZ C K G I R P E V D W Q H A H K X Z O L T H\nS U Y D X W D S C Q D C G T C M P T T I N K\nI Z Q P D U S X T L M T I L V T O L R A T U\nM E G D C W I L L I N G W I U J A U T N T P\nK Z U T Z O S T B E I G V U M S T B F N W D\nI C I R J L R O D Y X O S P W H W Z L Q T N\nS O L S S M J R Q M R D T R R Q H B E E C V\nN G X V U W Y Y H F E M Y R A X O L W O K B\nP V N U Q E B X Q D U Y H J Y I Y H A T P O\nC W C P A K I H S R L W O P R F L Z R D R E\nT Q I H Z Y G H N N R G Y O O C U R D P Q L\nY N S Q B B A I O E X S M R D L M M O V O K\nJ K F M C O M M O N O X A U A Q I I X A Q A\nF S X L S A R P H N W X E M R F H C V E D M\nZ D L M C V D V K N A C T Y R V L R E L G D\nX Z O G I X L L R O H G X Y M S H W M D O W",
        "answer": "[[COMMON, DEDUCTION, EMBRYO, ITALIAN, LOOSE, POLICE, RAILROAD, RETAIN, RETURN, TRACTABLE, WILLING]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "22"
    },
    {
        "idx": "9",
        "question": "Y Z F K F B G Z S M I F Z W K Q F R F I\nH E W U B L U O D U Z L L J T V O J W W\nY K V O N Q V D H F F F Z A B B I O F I\nM X Z P Q E P Y T D H B W N J T V H Q G\nR S A P R Q R D W H F K E S J Z Q V H J\nP N W E J E L E U I O J V Y P E J S C W\nS F I C P Z U V V A B U H D X O Q M X H\nS G F R L Q L G M F F M G M I U I R Z C\nN H O X H M O A K D F M Z H M G N L G Z\nZ V B M W P I K Q O A Z O W T Q E N M U\nE F P P A A R E C J R A X C L S S T Z K\nV A C R W W G I U D V S O Z P U I Y D F\nI X C U X C G X Z K W J A M Z Q D I W H\nL E A V E S F H T Q V F N B E C L I K X\nL W R O O E E B F L W H W U G K Y Z M L\nR S K R N I A H I T G F Q M H Z C W O L\nK M K S L Z I Y G I A B C O I G S A A I\nS S K P D M G I N F L I C T I L H E R K\nU R B X O H B C C M U L V P T B D G K S\nG N S L O W L Y J K Q R K J O S R L S L",
        "answer": "[[DIGEST, INFLICT, LEAVES, PARCEL, REPROVE, SLOWLY, SOVEREIGN, SPOIL, THOUGHT]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "20"
    },
    {
        "idx": "10",
        "question": "N S Q F M G V U B A C T\nW T B Z X X A O Q A W C\nZ G G O V B I G U H M O\nS T O T A L S T U M P N\nD A P C B S I L P S K T\nE V T V Y B T F A T Q I\nZ K O S D S E F L T R N\nN D X T Z O U N U E O U\nT M X I I U B N D L Y O\nD H A U Q R K S Y I U U\nE G Q I Z F F S Y Z N S\nL O A T H I N G X E C G",
        "answer": "[[BENDING, BOASTFUL, CONTINUOUS, LOATHING, STUMP, TOTAL]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "11",
        "question": "X V F U E O V S Z W N P Z S E A B F B Y I S Z W M T C Y C L E P P B F\nK A E W O H X U P W I M W G T N W J B P T I B J G M B B Y N Q P S M N\nQ Q A T K O Z X P A A O W S X K A T O Q R S Z V B U S F V E V N G A U\nE G N W P G U N V P T U O W C L I S N X W G T U J H O V F W L F Q V B\nJ D M L T R J G E M T S J V F E E L V C J Q I U I L S X Z G H H B A F\nJ U X B I K W Y P O A H D Z A K T D J X P Q D S X S L W F G D A R U L\nE O H L L D Z A S Z S F O I A M D H V Z V C A G E Q I G U G P F Y J P\nJ U F T U S A Y V A I O Z X A O R E H G F M L M X M N E M G L A L E J\nB D M D Y W J Q P H Q C C C H P O K P O E D F K U C D U Q L R X S E V\nT H R U S T T L W T D B A W P I P T I M N X H R N M U D J F B K L Y E\nK P Y L V N C U L I Y S X Z C R N L U N N P I O S R L O K U X H S M P\nV B L X H P K M A A A I X N Y Z A Y L R S O L Q F D G D Y B F W I C A\nI B V N P D J K M P R B M T D K N M C G H T E A P C E Z E N E J H J L\nW I C R U Z N S Q Q I Z A T K L H P B J F C I S I Q O E V U G H Y P S\nK W V D N N B N G B R A S D R A Y K U L X F J T W T L J D F M I X P J\nU D P D X O O V Y R W T S F C I F O Q S E C H A U G Z F U F D U H Q Z\nM S A P H G X H F G R K N D I R Q G R W C L W M K T G T O F H C X M H\nS B E F O R E P W R C A I Z X B N K F Z R G U T S U E P F N A Y K U M\nS Y I G N O R A N C E I R R C U U S P M E A J P I M S C D G K M G C H\nG N S J R T I S Z H W I W Y K R D P U N Y A X R J L V S K H E G P E D\nF E U I Z D T X U I B W P O F S R E N W F X U L G W U H M S J Q E E X\nQ Q V G F A C M H U W I X T W U G L H Z R Y V D X M F R K N F P O J K\nG E J W Z O C Q K K T H E W Y S H L A O F F I C I A L Q Q N R N O M U\nR A X C Y T H I K Q D Q C S M M M I L Q F V D I B H F P Z M N Y O H V\nM Q X S Q F A J W F S Z H O H N V Q N E M O S R J L L O I T Q B V D L\nG L A U Q T D C P L G Q W G Y Z R L U V H I S L L K D V W T Q T W C U\nB V I R E I R V Q N Y T C W V B H V S E O N N A S K G U A M V O I G K\nF C L I G A T E E P T D X E I A U I G K G L K F F V Q V A J B Z F T C\nK L F M V B R J J H W W W V Z I X L J P H K V M Z A R Z K R P N D K G\nQ D E F F U B O M K L H S W P I C F P U P K Z I K H R F K A C W B H C\nE D F A Y B J I X J K B W M G F G Q E N F X L C N F P V S B C Y Y G W\nT M P U E F I W D E V I S E L S J Z Y D N H K X M G V P A O C W E D I\nV D B Z M O S L H A B R O W V G Z P A J S Y U U H I S J U G X J E Z W\nZ Y V H J M M C S Y J K C D N Y G S W G P R E W T Z W V M J C W T Y C\nR E B N K Z X Q D D O W I T R D Z Q Y D G E J X B X J S J H J H A G P",
        "answer": "[[ATTAIN, BEFORE, CYCLE, DEVISE, IGNORANCE, INDULGE, INSTITUTE, INVOLVING, OFFICIAL, PLAIT, QUICK, RAMBLE, RIVER, SPELL, THRUST, ZIGZAG]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "35"
    },
    {
        "idx": "12",
        "question": "O B A R U E Z B F P T D R D H T J G O V Z C Q J B C H U\nT A S T R U C T U E T B M Z O K U U J R S K N D O U Z R\nM E O C U L N M O T G U G N D A D H Q F R Z Q I I A V T\nL V Y T O O Z G B O I M V W A E X Q P T B T A I L C M S\nH F L L F M X F X A O F Y E G E N P C D Y E I L S N D L\nJ K I Y R G I K J I X V K G E G X J S L A H N Z Z Q X O\nN U Y L F U R N H X F F R V X B N Y J D S H A G U R E R\nQ R I X N T J P G L T E A K C O A I P H U L U O L B J A\nD O I Y S I V A K D R B E L L I P S E Z C Q Z U Z I E R\nK Y V Y Y S D T C S X R Q V R M D T S P Y K S B B M S W\nG K O H X H I G T O K Z P A C I E S S B Y H S V X F B H\nF V E T L J T I J L W R R L V I S M Z C J W W A J Y D N\nA E O I V M E X W G Y M U L I Z D U Z X B A D L K Q T G\nS F L M P B B M S G E F H E X F E G C L Z X Q X T V P I\nA P S S F J E M E W Z S U Y R Q M W I A N R S Z G N H D\nH P U F F J H Z W V A B Q U J Z W K A Q J J H U E V Y Y\nW I U D A N W P P N P N H Q U Y Y H N L T K U X E W J P\nT P H S H J Y U V Y G U V H Q O O G K B S O J A T F U R\nO K X R P B X F K R M U R G K M D I X N T R D D K H N L\nK M N Y A D S Z M L O D R Y X E R T K O N Y L B W J G E\nX L U S D N R C Z F L X H R Z T N A O H J Y X L K K Y M\nV G S Q M K X E Q T X J O U R N A L D K W D A C Z I E E\nC T H T N K H U X R G I N N C O A T R F I S R S B K N G\nY H M I L R H X S Y X Q S J Z H R L Z V E N H I K W X K\nD J Z H X X M E O E A R K A N H C N M B R E A D N X Q U\nR W J J E J E U A R S H K E D H L P L B J F U N G K Z R\nJ D G E Y L O K D W Z U L D U I J F D I V I N E P O B S\nT V Z G E E E Y T F L A X I K S G F K G Z V Y S L U V S",
        "answer": "[[BREAD, COATING, COMING, DIVINE, DRINK, ELLIPSE, ENGLISH, JOURNAL, NORTH, STRUCTURE, VALLEY]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "28"
    },
    {
        "idx": "13",
        "question": "A K E N M W B U G C B Q L T W T H C D B\nO F D V Q H S K M S Z A V Z V X E B J Q\nP M U G A Z F P R O T W X C B B R A X V\nR V L L K A O P J N S G T T V T P V Z B\nM P E W R P U B E J Y P I Z J J S H F J\nK G R N I D N M V M B Q U U K D Y L N R\nR L P S M Z D L T Z R E M O V E D A R G\nP B G Z N H A V T X M I I N P J O R G U\nV F A O C V T V B A L S A M U A D W W B\nN H I C R T I G V Y L Y L O R K V F K L\nN F W G T Z O J E W X J P V K I K A C X\nU X S D D E N M C L K Z J F C F Q X S R\nB K L Y P W O P H H V S W T A I U K R U\nR Q U Q I N X J W F Z Q K W X T A X O L\nD E T I N U W E A S T P B L Y K I F A R\nR O T A T I O N R B P A B C Q Y L D W Z\nD K Q P C T S O X P R E F E R E N C E A\nC L B U J N T K E G D Q D E P Q N Q N G\nH S U P P R E S S N V Z Y H G Z A C L X\nN W O L F N K P T Q H U E L N S U F V N",
        "answer": "[[BALSAM, FOUNDATION, MENTAL, PREFERENCE, PRELUDE, QUAIL, REMOVED, ROTATION, SUPPRESS, UNITED]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "20"
    },
    {
        "idx": "14",
        "question": "N W G Z X G R T E Z E C E M T J C M R J Q W X U R X K Z\nE S F R I E D D T C X C C J Q L N D N R S W K Q G M R T\nY Q F B O D U D N N W Y P U P F R Z Z M L X X S V S M A\nA B F A E W Z A R A V L E O W Q C C O I K Y N Z A R D R\nL L E X F C V G Y Z H D E R W O X W W T P L C W B T E Z\nD W Y A U D Q A U W Z C L I H H A L B U Y V M G B A L O\nG I W P A U D Q J L Y C Z Z G G C W Y N V B R V O R I C\nS Q D H G G V F V L D K M M D S Q X K N Q Q M U L Q B S\nE C U A R J X V R X H J K P J W U Q G H L O E X S O E I\nX O P K D C C P X C S D Z L P K E I D M F G M D T D R E\nL S G L V V Q O I V G R C X H A N U Z N L F O U E R T T\nF W W F R D Y I I O L J P E W W X K L W N D R K R I N S\nA H F Y M V M K R Y D S G P D N P O Q L I N Y T P N D R\nZ R N E I D U J G E C B O D N J F E N Q U Y V X E K Q E\nT B M B U R C U D F C H G V Q X A I T T C M I V K I K D\nP R J V Q T Y D Q M O I S R B X N V O L F W U S W N H H\nU K E B V M M G U F K E P O B A A F U X I A K I R G X D\nS C Z A F F P E W G V H I R L R M K D K U S A A D Z J L\nQ C F T S A L H W U W U C U O L U Y L P D D S C D G O P\nG F C Y I U Y P N I C S S R S C L Z K W A O A F L G R Y\nJ M R H G Z R P D F L M R G G Y A R Y L C R X I O Q K S\nP V Y N E C V Y A T B S B R R X A L M A J N T A M C S P\nS O V F U E O X J N I M H I P F M N A M M T W I V J Q W\nQ B D E F J S M W C S A E N Q V H I Y E L W W O C L F B\nR G B S O A T E E G Y K N H X T T F U S I U T D J L F X\nX K T G G X C Y K W B F N O D X M O W H T D Q W S E E F\nV J G F W M H X Z G W K X F O R V D O R J H Y T X F L I\nH V O R P F B F Q M N K O I R Q Y M T Q F F L I R O S Z",
        "answer": "[[ADVANCE, BOLSTER, CHEESE, DELIBERATE, DRINKING, JUDGE, MEMORY, PARTICLE, RECIPROCAL, TREASURY]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "28"
    },
    {
        "idx": "15",
        "question": "A G U D L W O V F S I J E L S Q F G H J G U G C J\nL Z F C I Q O Y P J T A T T E N D A N T J Y E D I\nB V Q Y Q Q L P Q B Q Q I Z V E D R G F D H P L Q\nA L L E R B M U A N T I M O N Y Q Q H A Q L J C U\nP B I I D I E U W L N Y S M V K R T S A Y B J J E\nG I N C S V I C I N I T Y O F R O L F Z O E I V P\nZ B T W Q Y Z D T Q J X V O F U M W T Q C T R T L\nA G R I W V Q O T M V S L T H Y S R U O E I J R V\nM H V D R N V S E R H A R S R R W W C I Z S A E I\nN N M F A T V T T V K N D K K X T Y G P C X Q H R\nO N L Y I L X R D G M X O K C A S T K V E P Y T N\nA M P S W M A U H T Q L L W P F W D Z D O S N G V\nZ M Q J B Z K G P J V D J F M N O X H L T Z W F W\nD A V J L K M G E X L N L V T L Z C O U C M Q M I\nU K M R H H W L Q I A J S J V H J S F X L F L Y L\nU K Y T N F N E F A E D D Q P A O X X U E I I C S\nO J S T R A U Y B Q G Z I N M W U S Y R R D Q J E\nX F V D F A P T I M F V Y T Z Y V F E Y S D Q V S\nR A S S E M B L E K T R U Q F L T L Q L I A K G H\nQ L D I S E A S E L N Q G A N U O F S Y C Q H G P\nA Y R U F W Q X W Q Z A L I H R Y H P B I N O F T\nM V Z Q B A I L I P I W K Q U V P H Q F J I L R E\nW S J C T J T R Q Z J V M Z N E S K U I F K N Q N\nL U N B F D B W G F P R Z A R D L C R M H O J F D\nP M K D S D J I N F A N T R Y B G X F Q U X Z L D",
        "answer": "[[ANTIMONY, ASSEMBLE, ATTENDANT, DISEASE, INFANTRY, LUXURY, STRUGGLE, THOSE, UMBRELLA, VICINITY]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "25"
    },
    {
        "idx": "16",
        "question": "Z U G E L P H O S P H O R U S Q B S\nB E O F Q H Z S Q O H Q N H G M A U\nC R M C F H V C M A I E U N B X P R\nL G F O T P V R W P B J P E W M K O\nP A A F M W G S A O P G D R C R Q H\nP B Q T Y O T K S Y A X X F Y Q T C\nE M B V M B Q X H O X D T K U G O B\nI T L O X O I G I Z P V Y E K R D E\nB F R B L C S X N Z Y S G S T R E T\nS H S S A I E P G C H O R D Q I D B\nA U O E L A D S H F S G L A I D T E\nD I U R B Y S V I E E M K G S V T X\nS Z O V A D E B J A R C H T E Q G K\nI X F E I X L R D F I E G D S Y S G\nF V V R E A H U P R N N K M Z J Z J\nT X O P D E M B F M N R C L Z L T G\nB O P A Q U E G U L I V E L Y M A V\nM S W T M O Z S G Q X Z M T C M B E",
        "answer": "[[ATMOSPHERE, CHORD, CHORUS, LIVELY, OBSERVER, OPAQUE, PHOSPHORUS, THORAX, WASHING]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "18"
    },
    {
        "idx": "17",
        "question": "E O K F O U M Z P J V C D K H L Y N W X K K Q Q Z\nM L F V R Z K N L F N D O D W K F B P T G Y Q S W\nE L D T G Q F U D R P Q X S I Q J F O C G G D R Y\nH L I N X F P F Z R N A X P M X U E M N Q N W E G\nB G I M A V P U Z V B W Q V O B W E L X D L J B Z\nD Y V V T H O Z I E V U Y T T Q K T K E U A F T A\nJ F U H K N U C I H W A L J S B M N P U P X G P I\nD E Q K V M V Z W E M T T E Q L Z L E E L J B E S\nK I Z Q X S W X M M A R G F B R U P M L F W I X M\nQ L S T J N N R P E E M R S E G W G S S D Y B H Y\nN R S T F G P F M N D C M P R A L Q K C M B J T Y\nJ W E K I F F L Y C P K O I A Q G J P M G L A Z N\nC S E D C N J U A E C Q N K B Y O Y R S O B M S F\nH N O N U K G Y P T T M E W X E H A N X I O U S S\nA Z S Y V C M U N R I E L I W C A G W S A S N P E\nV M X P A T I I I C V N R C E J V R B M C S E Z J\nN A O H H R Y N F S R H U M I L G U I U A D D G V\nW B L D H I Z Q G W H X J M I K W S I N S Q I O Y\nR H O Z M B Y H I P J E A B J N O R I U G T P L E\nY C F L D E J I Y L X Q D U N A A O F W T U S V I\nL L B E G C T P L G V R S T T M K L C A V J U K B\nR I M U X C L M N X D O M E S A R R M T M M Y K O\nK F U R T N I H U F J R D J N L S N B A R H H X W\nL A I U W J V W K J M Q W Q G T N S G R E N D E R\nC R G T F Z N K P E P O I H T K V A R I A N T G F",
        "answer": "[[ANXIOUS, BEARING, BONDAGE, DISTINGUISHED, HANDLE, PLATINUM, REDUCING, RENDER, TERMINAL, TRIBE, VARIANT, VEHEMENCE]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "25"
    },
    {
        "idx": "18",
        "question": "S D M C Y D G O R A O B Z T C A M Y I Y J A H O A\nB X D P E B D D C B Z U Y F R K S X L V N B B D Q\nG E F J H L B Z O H Y D F Z X R J O A A P H T K S\nK M K F H H Z N F R E T X I O U H A Z M I N H R Y\nQ V I W P W U Q W A G E R B U S K S U R Z O S E D\nH S I M E L B D W F P L V W Q R Z S F C B I N I V\nZ Y E T F F F Q Y U Z V X U Z V M J S Z I U S A N\nJ N Y Z K C A S N P T X E N B M J K V U Q O L V C\nN E P S C R S V K A L A B O R I O U S U N M X T V\nD E S S E R P X E Y I J M M E C H K B J Q E K C F\nJ B W N K I H A F A L Z E C A O Q N R L L E U G Q\nK O B U T T O N O B I C E F T R W R H C D O F B Y\nX T Z J F Z B N A L Y W N N Z R F Q X W Q L O J Y\nC B L Q B G F P O E V M R T D E X P M R X W U Z S\nB J P A I D G F H F L L M N M S T S M O Q T N I X\nV Q F G U A I E U S V R B Q C P G D G K J J T A F\nM H J W E U O P L A A L Q D V O H W A T N N A G Z\nD E L Q Y V G I J A L Z R N Q N E N V O Q S I V Z\nB Z Y J R S B A K B U K H R P D Y E J C M Y N V G\nV U V F I H Y T G Q E Q T D J I B A Z S Z E B Y G\nB Z V S F V N Z H W D S P E L N U M U I P I G B W\nV H X Q L F R Q D R H E Y E G G C T W G Y S Y H A\nE I N F E R E N C E U G I E D Y X S P Q P Z F M W\nI R L O K W D D B T E S V A Y R F Z E P Z B T H X\nH F N A E G E E W H R T H R J B O K K C B U A E W",
        "answer": "[[BLEMISH, BUTTON, CORRESPONDING, EXPRESSED, FOUNTAIN, INFERENCE, LABORIOUS, PAYABLE, THRUSH, VALUED, WAGER]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "25"
    },
    {
        "idx": "19",
        "question": "W G S F E E E E B C\nO S A T Z C U W E B\nK Z E S P I X A C M\nG Y I T U U L O L D\nJ L E U B J L E O M\nS P E C I E S H I V\nE U F P P J R T S J\nS I S A H P M E T A\nR E X P A N D B E D\nI Q V W O X P L R H",
        "answer": "[[CLOISTER, EMPHASIS, EXPAND, JUICE, SPECIES]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "20",
        "question": "K S B U D D H V B W Z U X Z Q S Q G L Q V L C J U U N P R A S S R X T\nE S L F L Z C Q W L I X E A A M P A C D T F W W J T B R D Z V A V E P\nZ B U A T J I B K N Z H V Z I V R N I N D W Z F O C T Y L Y L B G L P\nW M E C D Z H D Z X P V I P F E G F R M X I U I J W S Q P L T V U P Q\nY E M G C I W V L Z G E D D N D P O A R Z N V V R T O K O S X C K R A\nW Z B U Q E B H E U J K S E K Z M S T G V J C L N F V C C Y M Z J E D\nS U F L J G S K F A P X G S T F Q U H D N R W Y X B I C P K U S L P Y\nW A M Z P C U F C T Q M O B E B Q W G B F A T D V K G F X Q Q D U C Z\nF L X B M N U Y J C T Y V A R U V E S Y T T G N H Z X A D E V E L O P\nB Y K D Q L L K M O Z A W J R P C C V R X N U P J O T G G R I B F C Z\nL N Z Q E O E H W A P A F J E M I K H L B M R Q K B F Q H I O J P Z Z\nJ O K G M S G X Q T U L S S S A J T A S U W S B N G M K D V L P M Q Y\nA A P A X I T O I X T J A N T S G G B B X Z I L M C E Y F B H Z P T O\nO V N G N J P F F R F T U Q R B H P U Z O I A K V S E E H V O C N G R\nW L V L T V B R H R V M P O I V K F Q W W U P A Z M W J K J R I A H T\nU Q W X I K M Y T Z S Y K Q A T D K M F L J E B B G Y B S X E R D S K\nR G N E S Q G X E Z O Y Z E L Q M S V G X K S V M F H T D N L U R H S\nE H S J S I T V Y X N S D N Q U M S T H O U G H O L A R P O H X O Q I\nD Q V I I G G U M T J J B B V M H U K N O V K E X O I J W G U T O L Q\nM X X C C C N I P X P A I J B D J X A R E E U H J O F I N Q U C A B I\nE B P E S T O E F E I U I T M L G D J Q W Q L O T R N N O S B Y E I H\nB D Y F L A I N M R W O F R X H H Y H E Z H P L C C D D V L T J L O W\nQ M K E D H N W T V A O R E V C T Q R U O L V K L O J I L Z Q M Y E K\nV T L H R U M C U I B U V B Q C L K E A S Q J Q R Z G R O L Z Q T F X\nD X H V S H F B T K N A A E Z D Z M Q F M R G O F W N E X F G L D U U\nJ W R C Z K K Y R I Z E W K N W L T D F Z M M W U C A C R G C V F E K\nM P O L E R H N A D T E N C H E C L X P E P A D N W S T M W M U N A Z\nY R K W Z P S T W K T Y C T G R R P D J P S L J I H I O I E Q E K R G\nE J F B D Y Q D O K C T M Q E G Q E G R A L Z Z G K E P F T X H P T F\nL V F E Q Z Q G R K T F B Y F N R O A N G E Q G H F D S R H J J E I D\nY V R N X S K Z N Y R Y X P C C V J Y L V Z F I D H G T Y F N Z C S D\nT D Q R T I I Z U S C E T H K R A G M B S G S K A V G U H L E W T F N\nA G C G H A I A R R R D E O S K A D A M P G F X G S Y O X B N M A I F\nD Y W W S Y A G K T Z O J W B Z W N J Y S A M E A N V X I Z L I D U M\nI D R D M A A T C T M Q T P R G E O E A H S N B W F O R T I F Y C P I",
        "answer": "[[COLLAR, CONTINENT, CRANE, DEVELOP, FLOOR, FORTIFY, GENERAL, INDIRECT, PERPLEX, SANCTITY, SCORE, SUCCESSFUL, TERRESTRIAL, THOUGH, VENEREAL, VIOLENT, WHICH]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "35"
    },
    {
        "idx": "21",
        "question": "P E R F O R M E D E W V L E M Y Y Y Y H\nH V P Y T T V I I T U Y W S J T Y C R C\nK O S M Z F N V J A V A D K K N Y I A N\nX L T K Y C O G O N B J U A T I I F N E\nF R B R I I I B F E E M B B K A X N O R\nT B S D Y H K G W S X G J L Z T L Q I T\nQ C E N L Q C S H Z C H R T E R D D S G\nH N V H P E C P A W H F F U O E N E I P\nT K L E G X I T E V A R M Y P C L F V K\nU D Q R U H Y H G A Y B Q L W Z M E T H\nX E W Y W Z M K E R M Q N R B O Y A M E\nG F G Y I O U N L D A N B Y O Z Q T K W\nG C A N L N S H W X S T E W E V I Y Q C\nB I X R C P D Y P U W T E V D G S U A P\nL N R S X N O N M H L B C P R M E R N A\nW R C W H L U S P U C M A L L X B V P S\nP U L Z P X W U Y Q Z K N H S Q S I P Q\nV Y Y H D B E E P Q G U O A G O W B R W\nJ W F Z J W Y R Y O I Z N V R Z M V S J\nS W V J U F F E B E T R A Y U V N X K G",
        "answer": "[[BETRAY, CANON, CERTAINTY, DEFEAT, GRATE, INCIDENT, PERFORMED, SENATE, TRENCH, VISIONARY]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "20"
    },
    {
        "idx": "22",
        "question": "Q S T X P Q F E Q S H I K I S L D Y Q S I O X T R J D A J I\nH I H H E E D E W F V W E Q C O S R V S W C C M V L D K N H\nP X G T S E O I Z R J F F I L H J M T A L R Y Z N C H U F Q\nQ F S O P L D R H F A O Q X E Y R P M I J I I Q T O A M C X\nM B V R I Z U Y R A W J V A A L B T K Y C A L B O Y U J W U\nV B I P M F Z Y F Z K J G H E M T O R N C Q D M R J G U E N\nJ V M W G U L V W X J X M Z C Y C M X N S P S W J G Z Z M T\nE F Q U X X L N W Q N Z P H Q I Y R K M T U H O Z H O D P R\nT A H G R J R T P M E H G W S Z B I Q B E T Q A H D S X H L\nG T T M V W T L I T E Z W U A R M V J M R G T K X K Z F O P\nB M M L J Q Y T E T Y R R L R B N F K X N P T Y D V Z N C B\nP M Z U H W F T O X U S C N S P M G Q Z U P Y U Q Y S Y L R\nP J R K I G H K S O A D R U I Q P J F U M I M W Y O H N A A\nS X F C M N V Y C F V T E U R U N B L C O V H L W A R O W S\nK D K Q Z A O Q F A T A M F Z Y H A R D L T M M L O N X F A\nP E P E M W S I E D G F J Z F K P Y L L C E I D Q E B N U W\nD Z Y R R M R B K V N J C J P S R R T H R A M E A M P E L T\nG K B O R M K Z N T E L C P D G C S Z P I F A A N N Z O T I\nL T A C A E U T C U P M P A G M V F Q H C D J H R T P J S J\nE R H T W M Y O G F Y A B T F K F A U R Q Y E N O Y I I M U\nP L I O A L X L Q T E Z U I X C O I L U L N A P R Y B E U Z\nQ O S O U Z F D E K O U N E O M W P L A A L R C R A T B Z G\nN O S N X G E Z I T F T S N B L C J B S B B R H X I Z D X N\nU Z E G E W H T P A G T Y T O L J J P T R U F F V E V W I H\nC I G E Q C C Q I B V E N D H C Q I I B K Y P V V B F E S G\nQ X B R R T O N K L K R A N M E D A L D Z R W A S G K O D S\nF Z Z Z J P W B B E X L F A K T W K V J D S M T S E Z N A M\nQ W G N X H Z M Z T A Y L T R C X W Y T E K Z N Q Z M Y T A\nM I O X T J R H H X W Y F P A D I U Q H O X X P E Z Z U C W\nC H F B B N C H X C H Z O N G C P W N M R H G D U W A V Z H",
        "answer": "[[AFFIRMATION, DEPRIVE, DEPRIVED, LAWFUL, MERCURY, MULTITUDE, PATIENT, QUOTIENT, STERNUM, SYMPTOM, TABLET, THOUGH, UTTERLY, WICKED]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "30"
    },
    {
        "idx": "23",
        "question": "V K Z X I N J R F L W R F H V\nH C T A N S A X K A Q G P P O\nD F K S X C F G C M W I I S L\nK K X T K Y F P R H B W C O A\nF B E C O S I L T E K Y T E T\nC O U R A G E F H W E U S R I\nA A F L N E I R C P W M Z P L\nV R C P W E X E B A R T E Z E\nP B D R W J L N J Q B P O N L\nJ C D W I W R D Z D Q G S C T\nP F C T R P J W B Y X J Y P S\nE Q L Y E X P L Y R J A A I W\nE V S B P N B L K J C M J C Y\nR R X I V R L B E C V B U Q W\nI S S U B M I S S I V E Y H H",
        "answer": "[[AGREEMENT, COURAGE, KERNEL, RIPPLE, SNATCH, SUBMISSIVE, VOLATILE]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "15"
    },
    {
        "idx": "24",
        "question": "R R E U W F C A V K\nD O O A B J T D I P\nP E Y T W R L Q M V\nN K J M L F U O X Q\nV J V E M X L I T D\nN R C Z C D D A S D\nY T J L K T E T S E\nY A V E R S I O N H\nE G O Q K Z I O Z E\nM J R V J E R N N E",
        "answer": "[[AVERSION, BRUISE, DEJECTION, FLASH]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "25",
        "question": "X C I W E L C F F C M L P T H Y D X L E I Z R U I T B A S I C Z T Z N\nE F K D D Y U V V M E G H Y Z R J F D R B Q Z L N Y X D N G I L Z N E\nN W A M S K N G J F C P E W W K B F Z I V M X L T F D J K R G V B C O\nP J P X V Y T H E I R B S B B O B S E E F X V K X Y W B I I Y G A Q W\nW I C I T P U K U P D T K S D L L W L X Z J P N I P F O N M D H J R A\nK D C D N A P M M H R F O U R T E E N Y P H V W S N G A A U O F L R M\nS I U Y X Y R Z F D E F H L R A N B W M C L G O R L V V O N R Z X S C\nE H A X K P I W J W I A X U R B Y E Q Y S B O N H H L E M A L U X P E\nA N L X L Q N N V O C I G D J W C R A M C M O S M T A U R D A L O G C\nF C Q L C E C U X O R F W T E K F K V G A Z L I I C Y L R S B H X Q G\nX Q U I X H I A N X H K D A J C Z M A P T N J P T V D H M H I E G J U\nE X C Y A F P B Y L J A Y Y B X F Z X X U R Z L N Z E Q G Q U O Z F H\nB X V G T F L V W D F E G W B C R L X J V U A H F Z O Y A U H X N M L\nP C C B G V I I S N Z I Q P R T R S F B Y Q X X F T R Y D X W F W A Z\nH Q T J T K M G Q E J Z W Y T A E O L O L H O X D G B O I U G M S P W\nP X B K I I M A J W G E C I C P X F L F Z S E O N I L K U D D Y J V V\nR U L P R P E X K X O F Z L K T X O O Y C G A P M B A K F I U A V H M\nM T H Y X K X Q R C G W B I U D P K Q O K I Z V R R J R D F L T B A G\nP C R S U T V X D N S Q I W N J N J Y P Y T K I B A Q J W Y S H Q S Q\nV U K I Y W X F W C H B J C K W C G R R Q I I Z K B F G Z W J J L W F\nS V X T M B J F V I M H P P K I L S D G X C Q W I W E S A A J G G N G\nL D D H T Z U E S A F T R Y U I T O E P B C X Z P R G U W E R K R T G\nE V A H S K K P K O I F O N K Z C F N K Q R Y T J A V E Y N U Q R H Z\nQ B S Y X N P H D B H I D T G Q V M Q I U D N D M J G T K P O H C U W\nU K H G C H C J A D T N U T W K F Q U U U J X I L G T L Y W U K E A L\nM V G G M X H J S T M N E B X W G Z G R O S P S W E A T R Y G A R T R\nV G M D I C T S P D C K D X M H P I A N U C J D R G B H D S S G I F S\nA T Z D K R S Y U B I H P A L I F O R U H B G N R O L W H C P E H P D\nH V Z X M A G G H G A J R J P C P J I I O X O A O E D D O H E N X I J\nH K B E T H P U R D S K E O I G U P D H G K C K V V S K N O C T B Y M\nO S O G V H X F Q D R B S V R F R R J E H Q L W O O T A M U I D N T F\nI S O A Y X U E R W D P E O T W U S A M S M O C W M V N T S F Z H Q T\nK B B J J L M O B S A O N U Y J X R G V Q U R H R T C H U I I E L S Q\nU L R T S H J Z J Q E E T F I B J H H T Z G E A Z X Z Y J N C M C Y M\nE Q A V I O L H T J P U G J C O N T R A C T H C V B Q J E G I I H O F",
        "answer": "[[AGENT, BASIC, CONTRACT, EXPLOSIVE, FOURTEEN, FRUIT, HATCH, HOUSING, INVERSION, PRESENT, PRINCIPAL, PRODUCE, SHAVE, SPECIFIC, SWEAT, THEIR]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "35"
    },
    {
        "idx": "26",
        "question": "R R C I J O T N N Y H U R Y N\nC H E E L H R V G I P O T B M\nN Z T W X B W D K T V P M J J\nX F R M L M G D N M Z D G E C\nX F A L H M F K N A I U O O H\nF I D H U P I H Z W N E J C N\nL M G H P V W S B Q X C R P R\nA A R E H P H D F F V V E S I\nB C U J H X V M C O F Q R U H\nG B Z P B B L Q U A R T E R U\nA J E N F X B H O O Y T G U E\nU V Z P X R S B A V T U U I X\nN T B Y H G D E T E R M I N E\nK E M N Y Y N I M F Z E I G E\nB K R A Y F H L Q M B E R B D",
        "answer": "[[DETERMINE, MISFORTUNE, ORDNANCE, QUARTER]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "15"
    },
    {
        "idx": "27",
        "question": "H R V Q U G O I N S F Q N H D C K B W K I B R M Q H W P\nQ E M P Q L I Y U T X O Z E T L X O Q S W X M U O L C V\nW L F A A S A C M H K O I F F S G H P H H B T Z P S O R\nC E E Z N T K E H Y T L Z S C F U X G B Y S D Q R M B C\nF V S U P Y H N Q W L M E R S Q X B A P H V H R F A J G\nJ A T C M B N M G A C V J U X L E V C X A W Z E R V D R\nM R I E R C B K N J O X B M Z Y O K M G J P R K A N Y W\nF T V H L B D R Y X N X T K T C N X U S Q S W S N G P U\nA C A I Z N U R D O T J F T N H U F K Y X D I T W A A I\nJ A L R L Z O P T V I G Z P K G V Q V M G W P Y T H T P\nY G U I E T N I R Y N H Y L O L I R Q K N I I G R H W K\nV N Z L N P L U M V U L L A N P Q L W P N D V E C N B H\nJ O A Y T L B R T P O I B T A E A D F Q K N U E J Y Z S\nG V W H L U T L A F U W F E H R R B L N Y D F U N G K W\nW H H F H P E D N G S F B W B P Y U T L K O Y F Q B A U\nW M Q D J N J P C O U N C I L L B F L P M B N H O E G R\nN T U Y B V X E E M J Q M C N E L C T W S N T G M A C U\nY A U H D I S P O S E D E H Y X L P S A B Q C T Y X C Q\nA L S W P P Y S R W V I X O V I X Z V R X R Y T I V L I\nK H C Y L M X K T I N P S L J T T Q E H B G Y E S L O S\nI H K B D A D F Q R Z E Z I O Y J A H T W R W D H C D Q\nM W U X M K D E D J O J V S K O C D E N G B Z A M W T Q\nM S P E C U L A T I O N F S H C W A N S M W J D G A F T\nN O V W A J C O L O K A I T P F E L N L S Y M Z E L E D\nT A R D B B X Z Z C B H B U O P P R E S S I V E B O M X\nR F F Q C Q Y Y S S Q C T P X C B H M B Y E Q G T Z M T\nW U M U E B G F R A F D M J A F O W A M F X H R V B E Y\nX O A V S C R A P E F D N Z C P Y B Z M D P L Q Q B H J",
        "answer": "[[ALLIED, CONTINUOUS, COUNCIL, DISPOSED, FESTIVAL, GIVEN, OPPRESSIVE, PERPLEXITY, PLATE, SCRAPE, SPECULATION, TRAVELER]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "28"
    },
    {
        "idx": "28",
        "question": "E N D U R I N G I Z P L\nC A I B D B A A F I N N\nZ T P S C D W G E A N D\nA M P P L T A X S Y E F\nA G M M E H E A R T J A\nX J A B A A L E G A V S\nC Z M I A S R P L R U T\nT R O J N I Q A R V P U\nI V D R E A A B N I U D\nA B E K Z Z N I P C J E\nD O L N W U A U F U E N\nC Y Z T R E U G J Q D T",
        "answer": "[[AGAIN, APPEARANCE, ENDURING, HEART, MODEL, STUDENT]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "29",
        "question": "H A G Y S K Y K O X S B\nO V T P I L L A G E G J\nF T Y S S X K H T J G I\nA U Q X E L Z M A J J N\nB B Z E Q A N G L E S S\nF X S L A H T D G Q B I\nO E D T A M V O Y L L P\nR D N V R W D Z A F O I\nN S H C X A P O E Q E D\nA I H S E M C W V X P M\nD U L Y O C X T X J Q O\nT K C F A R T H R Z Q S",
        "answer": "[[ABSTRACT, ANGLES, FARTHER, FENCE, INSIPID, PILLAGE]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "30",
        "question": "I L G Z X N S R Q M D C E M O Z W A J Q A T X B I M G L Z Q\nH C K X V N D B A Z R S E E Y X M O A G T E T Q I S N M E D\nY M Q X D E X L J S V V F L K U D J S C H V A D B D M V G Q\nO Y K U G P P H K Y S G J D L E Q Z M O X F I D Y M M N C E\nA H W B O R J W F G T I K Q Z U R X B N R Q F S G U C P K P\nH Z K C X O P D A A V E K Y S G L G T V R B E E Y H B N F F\nI E C G C P I F D T F O Q H C I A A T E B S O I D M F H H R\nJ U P B Z O Y W Z R X I J F K R O S R Y M E W T C W J D V A\nR L B L D S C G Y F B S P S Q Z G A R A I J Z N Y S S F W S\nX V T K S I G J O D I S P O S E D O E N M Q G K U A M H V I\nL T H G G T O A O D Z M C G I X A G W C J O K M A G O U B O\nB P T V N I O U T R A G E D N E K I H E S S E M E O O L O T\nE W P H P O U V N S P N W I G N S Z J Z E L A F W U H F V C\nG Z E P S N M A T L Z O T Q Q P N O P I J B O S G T L L T L\nT L U K B Y V J V V F S J V Y K E G X Y M G E M J K Z L Y D\nC U C F U L H O W C P L B M N B Z E R V M B V U N H Q C D M\nN C A H K U U E V S I N O I U I R W K M I O K S W B O K U N\nP S J D T T B S I C D Y P L Q J B G M J F I F G Q S Q B D X\nZ Z Q S V T N P T W J L O C R S S A L E T L Z U A X Y R B Q\nC V A V R E Z A W E M D W S P E N M Z W V E H V V N O L J X\nJ A L U K D R X M N R J A Q E D K Z N K G R C J X M Z J N P\nA Y M N N P O S P G E T O X F U P V T Z Z E G C B B I T B T\nC I S A B K G Y E N D R A F O F D T O Z Y K Z G N C X A T H\nF R L T J F Z G Q F S I N L A S T I N G J G Y Q S R W A V K\nV I Y O J G C U Q S J C U W H B X O T E O I O A L G R D Y J\nN L I A R G X M O K X K Z O H W M S W F W L D C D K C S A J\nB Y K W A D Q U P B O E E Q C I G Z F G Z Q W H Q K X V C V\nG D N W U W B Y P K S R K P R K M J D M W F V X Q L N M R D\nH A M C M H E S R E C Y D W R Z H J L P L L V E A F D Y F J\nT D U K Q Z U N L I M I T E D A Y Y I N U T E L J F Y S C N",
        "answer": "[[ADVERSE, BASIC, BLUSTER, BOILER, CELLULAR, CONVEYANCE, DISPOSED, IDIOM, LASTING, OCCUR, OUTRAGE, PROPOSITION, SMOOTH, TRICKERY, UNLIMITED]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "30"
    },
    {
        "idx": "31",
        "question": "G L X M L A E S B R L Q\nK N A C R N C L U R C C\nC D I P S T L E S S H W\nE W J W W L K T Z N A A\nI C F E O F H O K D S P\nS L L P D L E B V O E B\nF F D J T S F U M Z N T\nN M R S I V N Y G C I Y\nE N R I C H D B A U O T\nR I L M R B L O C K M A\nZ E P Z R W G I T H P F\nK Z K E K C I W X P E P",
        "answer": "[[BLOCK, CHASE, ENRICH, FLOWING, RESTLESS]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "32",
        "question": "S S Y M P A T H Y K F P J O F V G Y U N E U X W V U N I A T R B E S F\nV P J Q P L D R O U M T U C N J Q Q I Z U G E J G K B H V Z R R L S I\nF Z J L I Z T E Q Y W O L T D V H Z Y A T O C A F Q F L Q E Q Y R F V\nE I Y D T W O X Z H P B U S P R O A L Q D T U Y H D F D X B Q I N F I\nF X Y W Z O I E M A W Y S R X Q T V C B E M V F J I P H H W P S W W G\nT M B L M A V F G J C S S G N P P L I D Y L R L K I R O U N A X G E O\nR Q U I K C L I L E O K R K V I T L H M H D I P K S B C P P U C V Q R\nO B H Q L G L O C F Q J D P H A N P C O M X J A A K O B R Y J Y F M G\nC T S J Q X C J U F I W Q I D E D G C R S E S W C Z S P Q E L F Y W U\nR O S E A F P K C E M X N Q J C X Z G M L M R Y C Q L R D P I P G K V\nT H N E I C G L R B J D I S H X L Q F J O P O S P X B B F T M I W X V\nF K X A L Y X B C P X Y H D C F O A L G Q U M D E L K Y E R R P Z F N\nK P K W H T I H W W S R S L C H N Y U N K G Z S T R I R Z A B W E I J\nV Y W H R B E D Z A L O F C D F U Z F S N X M P D Q N I Z T P L U I S\nM W Q J G X O D W W P V Y G Z K Z O B D E P V V I R L X O K N C S Z J\nI M N X S H J M I T Y X S C F I A V T C J B Y S P E K D J E P Y R H P\nF I Q T U N J V B Y C H A M B E R X J T J S J A Q I T D V O C K T O R\nF I M Y K E U N U G N E B H L L G S G J Y S R A N Z B U Q W I K U N M\nE L B B U B Q A Y I R G G B A K B S X T Z A E G U C H R H V R C O T O\nI A V T B O R I P Y E W H X X U F K O J M M N C I G V N C O I L O L B\nG V P I S C U V T X Z Q M F G Q Z S E Y L N V B S M M I X T U R E C X\nF I V G O M N G M H Y X X H L B H H A L X F R W U X M W G S B Y M J X\nT A U B Z T L P G F Y U G M O Q S A N U B M X A I V O O T S M I Q I R\nX O D D D A A H A L Y A X Y Q P F B B R Y P B N P Q U L V G S W O P G\nU F O U Y N Q K E C H W T U D Y M I Q A F I E F N T O X H A Q I L M Y\nN D R I V D P N V M D M V H I J L Q M F Q O O V O Z U T Q L B Z S S T\nU N B K A G B I M L S N E A X X W Z S A Z R Y V N U E K G C D L V A S\nH G N H G D F P Q O S I T G Q T M O W L L D T D X Y X J K R O S E S M\nY F T Q A O Q R K Z L T N V D G G A Z D T R K M Q V U K R R K L X Y N\nT O O P S B M H P T R Q K B O H V T A E P W N K L P R O P E R T Y X S\nD K Y G X G J G F N O H O K P G C Z X H L Y Z K L O W P A F F G M F R\nM R Z T H F B C Z W C H A O O X O J O Y W E A N O D V I E O A E R U T\nK Y O S B O F M V K D K J W E L N B O D S D K L P F F Q P S G U A A Y\nE H O N J L L L K N J F H A M D D F C E U F B F L J K L X I H L X Y B\nD E S T A B O I V L T K I T D K T K N N W U T S Q H A V V K S I G H B",
        "answer": "[[ALDEHYDE, ASCERTAIN, BUBBLE, CHAMBER, CLAUSE, IMMERSE, IMMOVABLE, MIXTURE, MOURNING, PROPERTY, RECITE, SPEAKING, SYMPATHY, VIGOR]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "35"
    },
    {
        "idx": "33",
        "question": "Q N X G E Z O H L S\nN O P N L T U L I M\nF I A H I S L X E J\nF T J N C C S D X F\nZ O A F N D L U D C\nX M P C O R Z O H S\nS J X U C T G U O H\nI K V B E Y Q G J P\nE Q V Z R R Q G R C\nV F E A T H E R E D",
        "answer": "[[FEATHERED, MOTION, RECONCILE]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "34",
        "question": "J F K W T R L A L R P D D Q J J J S\nN J Z Y C Q Q S D N L G A N C Q W J\nN O I T U C E S O R P S R I N G Q P\nH W R T E L Q E M E I O V D C R G U\nY G D A Q O D M N I S P J Q I D G O\nR U O Y P M S B X E E K G C H P P G\nI N E P X T U L P R X K B H Z P M X\nU J T H J X I A S W N M Z J Z L C U\nW D K L H A N G G P U R E E V F K Y\nY I S M G F S E Q P R M A N O L W J\nJ K G T E B E V I R L I U W H T R D\nG D E M A A R O Q H I G N E A D X N\nQ A P U T Y T S S W C Q X K V K S M\nR L R R N A I K O E R Z N W L C E W\nK W Q L E C O G R K W T M G S E J J\nC W W K S N N U E F Z D V L P M Q R\nD Z B B S Z H N A Q S T I F L E E B\nD E L L A C K T F G W N Z K T H D T",
        "answer": "[[ASSEMBLAGE, AWAKE, CALLED, GREATNESS, INSERTION, PROSECUTION, SPRINKLE, STIFLE]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "18"
    },
    {
        "idx": "35",
        "question": "N S K X H G C F L P\nP Y A H S O O O I M\nR Z R V I H M U M P\nQ O V I R H I N P Q\nA F C I A Q N D E J\nT M Z A P E G A T U\nF N G W Z R W T U G\nY F R O Z E N I O Y\nJ R F A W D E O U Q\nY P G C G Y Q N S T",
        "answer": "[[COMING, FOUNDATION, FROZEN, IMPETUOUS, PARISH]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "36",
        "question": "S Y O U G R J Q J N X H E P T E Q H L M G U\nS Y I W S H B N A R B E U Y R C C I E N M O\nV C D B C N R E W S U L T G U X A E E F E O\nF B E M D B F M J U I R E B M X N H F O K G\nM U W L E K Y P B M K U P Z R C S A Q M T V\nK P X Q X F Q I S T Y D U H Q E V B C M I U\nZ S R N C Y Q E X Z Y S S N R H I K L K T U\nV Z Y Z E S A D O P K U L R T S X E B W T J\nQ S R Q N M A Q T H E M S E L V E S A S W Y\nF H M P A Z C C G L G U G I Y G W N K B Y S\nO I U T X F P V S W W Z N Y Y S I V U Q H U\nC U B K D Y F C K U K B X D R W W U L J N R\nC F N N A U D R L K C I X A M Q H Z U G T V\nU O R S S K P P O H A H Z P W E C Z C B C E\nP R K X D E X H L N H R U C P T U T M W X V\nA F H Q P F V Y F M T J R F X Z I S E V E K\nT E U L F J R N E E K S L M X X K Q W F L C\nI I L S L O U O B B J V I T B Q F I L L E T\nO T T U S E C N A N E U G J M Y H K I R T U\nN Q I I H C U I I R O F W K A R I J G L K V\nR I N C I D E N T O H A R D Y P N P F R B S\nT T Q J W T H I R I R M L A S S O C I A T E",
        "answer": "[[AFFRONT, ASSOCIATE, FILLET, FORFEIT, HARDY, INCIDENT, JUNIOR, OCCUPATION, SCREEN, THEMSELVES]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "22"
    },
    {
        "idx": "37",
        "question": "S I D G L X U S E X J X Z S E R P L E X U V I R G B G I W K\nG K N U T Z V P N C Y Z S C Y O U X G W J L U A W A J E Q S\nJ P Y X P J C V D B D F G C L G L C S Q G X H P F V I C A G\nI W Y F D G D V L U U X S U D Z Y R H I U K F O R V C H K K\nN I E U C I X Y G L Z C G S A B M K H T M B K B V W D F W R\nL A C I S Y H P B S R B Y S D M W F F G L P H H Z J X S T R\nL Q P Z I W A L V X S F K L W O R K P Z D R L M Q Y T B R H\nT S A V J M Y Y H K T D J F N Z D V A A L W E I Y V D P N E\nF I B O B A F G S X U T S Y J H C F S G E H L U C N V I I V\nW W B F R G M Q M V F Q X B W J I G X L C A U M C I G I E R\nV B Y X L Y G H R Y F S H D F V N D K P Q J J Z H Z T P D I\nA D Z T T A I P Y F I C A R R Y I N G S J H M G U E A Y A A\nP J L G Y N B O C Q N M P D W F S E T E L E Y V U I A U I H\nB S H Y O Q Q R Q N G Z B F Y K J B Z G N A D Z A P X N G X\nJ T K U Q O Z W E K T B W Q W R H F W X V L S D R S J Y S L\nK Z F V N T D L H Q A V Y Z S A E F I N D T T D S S A U L B\nA G J Q O R E C F E V V D Y A I Z E M W A H B M K L K V S J\nT M C S E W X E S C X B E D L P C P E O P M G X S W L R L Z\nH U E T U D T I S O L A T E D Z L T F C V Z C S C S B H W N\nJ S A D B I E S D R D P H H T T H T W N N K Z O O Y O M K J\nJ I Z U U D R P F I J Y A H E T H G Y I H N F B X T H Y I H\nN Y L X X U O R X A W D R R Y F Z K W A O U Z Z Y U A I P Z\nY B B P P F U L E I H G M Y W F K D W N S T V B Y Y T N P P\nG T U B P Z S S I N R O H S G V D E D T N E V B M U X S R E\nT I T V Y R N P X W D K S B S G U R O U H H T X N M S R A B\nA I T X X Y F U N K R E T R V Z N I K L A K W J Y P S V Z P\nD S O Z O P F H W Y H W R H E Z D V A L W N C D B Z Y N K W\nC M N B F Q D J P X U U D I K V R E E C Z Y O B K C D V C H\nN X U H J M C Y I U R S T B N R E D T W C W R R C Y K J C U\nT O G R A J Z Q F E A W A C E G I U D Y X G G N N C I Y L Y",
        "answer": "[[BUTTON, CARRYING, DERIVED, DEXTEROUS, HEALTH, ISOLATED, LABOR, PERPLEX, PHYSICAL, RENDERING, RETAIN, SIMPLICITY, STUFFING, SUCCESSFUL]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "30"
    },
    {
        "idx": "38",
        "question": "P W J U O A U V U X A M S I P W E L S V N Y W A G Y G M\nI V N M J G Z O D N T W A E O W M S J J Y Z H D L O F J\nW I N M P K D X V M G B B Z L A E P Q V Y G S U D D S E\nE B X L F Q B Y Q I B Y S C E P R X W I U Z B Z A E G P\nQ F K N A H L Z J R I N F G V O P I N B Y V U X Y G U O\nZ D W F H T N Z F V X S G R N M U C I R Z L O H J G J Y\nO C N O I B M S J N X P N B E E S N R V Y Q P F D Z Q Q\nS A S F A S E I Z E I W O I F E P W A J I L J I S R T E\nK M T Q Q T U A Z S K E Y V N X R A I Z H E J D V V U J\nA P P O F S X F G L Z X M Q I G Q N Y Z W K C Z V P Q I\nM E K N S P L I T X M G O K I R W E U M Q U J I L I W M\nI L L U S T R A T I O N D R I U F Q Z E E O V C B E I I\nM F Q C E E L Z U M U E V L E A C P L D H N M Z K C S A\nN B J U O B K J O G V O O A G N S G M V N U T R X E W P\nZ R U Z X I F G C X A R E B Q K Z V R H S H M P G H A Z\nR E E O W P W I M V E I N O W D P W W A Q B J H B I L R\nP E N O R M O U S P A Q T R F G F Q N L I D I C S O L U\nH H E T J B R A K S Q V P J P T I C G A H T S Z K B O L\nF C S O C W L U T Y A Q D O L P H I N X W I O Q O V W Q\nR S H T N T U W A R D Z P R F O Z L O B E W S B H C Q Z\nL H R X L T B N K G X M M U V D B Y W L C K Z J Y W Q T\nW C U Y R S R F E T V G K M S T O R Q T Y R P O S U N B\nO V F H R W G P E B M Z E A Y K W Y E L L O W H C K K Q\nX Y W Q V R L M D X W S T L I D M B I I F W X L Z W N A\nY N J P G H C P O W P U Y V I C R V O X Y G C L G X D Q\nL T S K Y R U E I N V U U B Z Z T M Z O F R X S D X H D\nY I U G C W S W H Z O H Y G T B Z W P J Y D Y G L A Z D\nY T I P E S A N P P Z A V X Y A S Z H I H M U J I U J O",
        "answer": "[[DOLPHIN, ENORMOUS, ENVELOP, ILLUSTRATION, LABOR, PAYMENT, SEIZE, SPLIT, SUPREME, SWALLOW, YELLOW]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "28"
    },
    {
        "idx": "39",
        "question": "L Q E W S B A P T F\nS U M G P G Y H J R\nO P A V Y Z G Z Z A\nR Q I T O P B C J C\nI K W N T G T O H S\nF I H J D A T I O J\nI O E U D L C M A Z\nC P P E O H E H S N\nE I F D I S Q F E O\nJ F C H R I P T T D",
        "answer": "[[ATTACHED, EGYPTIAN, ORIFICE, SCARF, SPINDLE]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "40",
        "question": "F K Z R B E H L W U Z T C C T\nV T K H Z U L I D Z E F H U Q\nH U O W W T P G W E K W J U I\nK L I R L C O H C R A N K K D\nQ L T X P Q I T Y W Q D Q S I\nR E S C H E A E A K A Q I B S\nN V A I F I D N L I D Z K Q E\nO E G T W T R O L Z N S O X A\nW Q J R C E X J L D X G T Z S\nL M G O Q Z P R F Z M U J Z E\nH O A U J N K R L L O F O V G\nE V E K D X V B I D V W I P N\nT S N P K B R N I E E G S T M\nT F P V U E C S H C S X J E P\nF R Q R H F H D P J G T G O Q",
        "answer": "[[DISEASE, LIGHTEN, PRIEST, REQUEST, TORPEDO]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "15"
    },
    {
        "idx": "41",
        "question": "I B O T R Y I A H Q Q E\nQ G K E G A C D P T X G\nK R O W E M A R F S E R\nR K E P R E L U D E N M\nC I A L D A I H D Q H A\nQ C O R R E C T I O N B\nN D H Y X Z I B V I G W\nT R E A T M E N T S Z D\nH R C Y K C X K P U Q L\nK C A T T A J L H Z T G\nF D G Q H Y Y P T H I N\nL X S D X W W C L B L T",
        "answer": "[[ATTACK, CORRECTION, FRAMEWORK, PRELUDE, TREATMENT]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "42",
        "question": "L U L O T T F D Y G N N D O U T E F W H A U\nY C B R E Y D P R D Y Z L Y G E C J E K Q L\nM J P J A D N F R A D V I S E E N G L F G D\nD E X O E S E O V I H T C W D W A V X R H D\nX Q G R N C C E F M M Q N Q A U R N P U O L\nU S F O H E T S Z V N P R P R A U W J D W G\nF B B A R G X E F O V Y L S B U S W W D B E\nN V H E Y J Y C D G Y J X E L M N G M N Y P\nH Q C M Q R F V T Y M F M P M D I U M L H B\nZ N P O S Q N F Z H H C C Q T E E Q G X Y L\nH F Y V N T Q Y L O D P R X K P N Y C F K D\nV D B O K F U X V O O P U Z Z Q X T Q K P L\nG M N Q D B U D A M A G S W K C S K K L Q N\nV K A B J B W S Y J Y T K X X X A T X E A Q\nO Y P D O C U J E H A D T A Q R F S L S U S\nE G I B H G A C R D Y L F A O E C G T Z I X\nF U W A E H K P H R O T R E Q T R M G L C X\nK R I V R N G D I A X Q Y D A U N E M U E S\nZ U R U W I M B I T S U X T R N X I D Y U P\nU S N E W N J K S M A A L O A Y C A U L C B\nB F E Z S X C J D W F L U W K L X P Z V N I\nU C O E V F S B S D E Z B E F W W Q L R O O",
        "answer": "[[ADVISE, CAPITAL, CASTLE, CONFUSED, DOUBT, FLOAT, IMPLEMENT, INSURANCE, RECORDING, STUDY, SUBJECTED]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "22"
    },
    {
        "idx": "43",
        "question": "R T D K G G O N D X E O T Y T W B X Y Y L A U C B\nJ A O X A D J A C E N T N U A U T X E H X V K F U\nR O E P Z F R L B H U W A R E L A A I F O F Q W F\nQ I P Y J G F G A P N Q T J S F A Q F V Z I W L X\nC W J J F C B I H G G A S N G O Q F X E Y L J E M\nT Z G V T V S S V G C J I U Q B O D N E Z L N F P\nK I I A O W N X C H Z N D O R J S L P M S I T R J\nB D C G R C I S T Z C A N X K F K E D A S N C H M\nB Z A Q N U T F D K J D J G L A T A E M P G B A D\nJ G F I A C M X E R D X M A N V U L D D S K G E Q\nX A Q M M I I L E P F F C H Y H Z D U F X U N X K\nC U A E E W Q X A B S K F I Q F G X A W N Y H E W\nK P V H N Z S K G L S K K C C U L B X N W S X P F\nC K J S T R I K F E Y Y A M O V I I P J F N F U S\nL G I N N Q J A K Q S O X R Y V E R T P G L B J D\nN L P F V K Y U E T U X Y D V L E J P P T Y J S N\nJ J G T B R Z C A J S Q Q K F M V R J V I G W U L\nP W R S Q M C R E S C E N T V Y D S I N L F W V P\nO C Z J O Y N Q U T P U M B R E L L A N R Y Q X R\nP L G T P Y C E M W F X G J K D Y X S V G L S X W\nV K G U M R P N K B G P V J H Q Q I H O B L I N I\nG P J A Z O W B L E R X T V I F E N P U J K Q H Y\nJ G M Q T A D E F O R M I T Y O I G Z V Q D Y C I\nD L N D B F Y L O N O V S X A Z D L N O C S T W W\nV F D I S P O S E H X A H D E P E Z W J R I S G R",
        "answer": "[[ADJACENT, COVERING, CRESCENT, DEFORMITY, DISPOSE, DISTANT, FILLING, ORNAMENT, UMBRELLA]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "25"
    },
    {
        "idx": "44",
        "question": "W U P Z B W P B F P J H D N P\nF F N N B D C R O T T Z Z L X\nZ Z G W D U Y A D H C O U Z E\nW Y O C D K Z C I Q F P H Z U\nA U S B O O H E F X H D P N R\nH S N U E Y Y E V S B F R S B\nH M A U C D H O N E Y F O E D\nL V G Y I C I P I P N H D X I\nE Q E F J Z E E B O O Z I C S\nW M N J A K B S N Z Z H G I M\nE F X J G C N W S C K D A T I\nD A K K H U U Q T F E N L I S\nD L K N K I Q X Q L U Q Z N S\nR T G U R L Y P Q N O L O G O\nC Z N E G G U W M O T O W N O",
        "answer": "[[BRACE, DISMISS, EXCITING, HONEY, OBEDIENCE, PRODIGAL, SUCCESSFUL]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "15"
    },
    {
        "idx": "45",
        "question": "O Y X E G V E V M N R H F X I C R L M S G M R A R W T B\nY K A E M U R L V I W M F A B R E F O S N M E W M U N Z\nK Z Z X H I D S S P N R E W M E N Z D E I T B M Y B A O\nR R F T X C D O F T R L C F T M S J C N T T S X A G R L\nB S Y R W P S M M Q J O T V H X V R L D A R H I T C G E\nG E J E U S P H D K G T I Q Z O M M Q A E Q F B O S T T\nV C O M K O U Y X B Z G N O P M L W V M F K Q G L G G B\nA H J I R H J S I E P N G J Y W Z I S O X N M N Q O A P\nB T B T K J Z H X L N N H D R D H F U J H O K E D Q U Z\nH T T Y O O E W N L U M G K I S G A X N E L L I P N A K\nT S I E M L F H N M B J O A M V R O F R L H R W V Z R M\nL L G E N Y D I A T W A F H O R I U E B H K I O O C B F\nX P E D H D I L B F X B D F Q Z U N D J B S Q U U H G K\nH I Q E G T W H R N F T H X Y E X Y A R H M P W M J T F\nG B S K T B C O O L Z I O L F C I Y H T A X T G O V Q Z\nD Z O A W Y W E A E D K R F I V N C F B I G X Y Q R V P\nG S B F J H K E D G Q T Q M X V E O Q Q I O N X P B S L\nO I E Z Z T C P S R E P D F A S I Q B T Z Y N T B N W O\nW P R O M A N C E I K D T G S T S N F Z V U S R M B N S\nA G B Z T C Z W O J K E E Q S J I I G L W S I S I F E X\nW C R B W Y C A I A L P K O K T V V M P I I V B L M E R\nJ G K B K S X J O K U J Q T Y Q V T E B T F D G H Y F J\nZ F O W O E P I V Z F K P B J L G A O K Q L E K V J F L\nS E H V C W B N F I A Y W A N E M N N G D J U L H B N Z\nM B Z D B B Y P H Y F B F L M F W H A B Y W F G E X K F\nK P T J N T M W R P D F I O C V R I Y D A T I Z A S B D\nT B A H I Q Z L Z A I R O Q H W C R A E S K G H S D S A\nR Z D Z S Q U Q P J W U J F B H V E H Z X M V K Z N D C",
        "answer": "[[ABROAD, AFFECTING, AFFIRMATIVE, ATTEND, DIVINATION, EATING, EXTREMITY, GRANT, HABIT, LIFELESS, LIVING, MADNESS, ROMANCE]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "28"
    },
    {
        "idx": "46",
        "question": "O J Q C I T E U C J Q M E J Q N K H F V S Z M H X B Q Z L W\nU I H V G E X J R O D D Z I X E I W T D F S S F Z N J Q G B\nZ D P V B E I S T B U J D P F V N K K U X W P A I Y T X L C\nZ J K U X F J P B O J B P P L E P S L I Z O G R K T S I I V\nN J E V Z G L D M T J W Q Y X S O N H X N T K W O J C S X N\nS B C N X B L B E V S C N B J F L T J J F T S O W U H T A V\nC J L H B E A S J S D T K U V R I T U A Y Z E V I F T I N Y\nJ U D E A T C U A G W I S Z S D S Q W N B W F R J R C R L N\nV T P E S R W L K V Q M U T K S H L H G E N W G F H Z G E S\nX H F S G S R D H B F B J D U D E L Y H S L Y J F E Q F N P\nA R T A S P E O C S Z E D M C M D V S I L G M U T I R Q E S\nA I T N L D U D W B Z R P G N V P X J N G J L R E O U E F I\nH E T K O S H S X S V D U J K H G C V P I W E R Y U Q Q K U\nF K G P W N E A L B R Z G R D Z C H W I Z X E A R J G B N Y\nB B Q T H I W F P G O Q B I T Y H P I S B X N I K J D N H O\nJ E B K H Z U F S N P L A R H F B U N Y H Z O J A F P X T K\nA S M Y T F N N T P K Y T E T T W Q Q D Z J B I L D V N U O\nI K C V D E L S R C B C P H G Y F V W J G B R G B O C Q P X\nR E T I R W P H A D M P J N K I J M D Y P C A L L E D C G D\nZ Y I R C A H Q P U R X Q X F L L Q N D F K A C K Y F W J D\nC I F M F D R T V I I F G C E R D G Z A Q S N B I V T T E S\nF T N L O O C K A L K J E K W W C B K P V Y H H Q U O V E A\nK V G S S U S L T M F T T L C K B I U D M D W A E M Z S V L\nM J C W D X K T V R P F L E E A Q F N E A A D V I S E G J B\nE X M N Y Y Y M W N P I L J Z R U Q S D P O J W K G N A D D\nY X R F M J N U C Z T L D J J E E I M H S D X N H E Q Z M J\nJ R K D L G B U O I A J Z F L F G O C O M M U N I C A T E R\nZ W J E D V Z N C B L T H B L B J M K F T R P U L M Y S Z G\nF E K K O O B A C O H T I A C R H V N A D Y Y S E X R Z G D\nE W Z D T G X F O G Q X W X A Y Z K Z T N C F W H L W W J U",
        "answer": "[[ADVISE, BLESSED, CALLED, COMMUNICATE, CONDUCT, FALSE, HARROW, INTERFERE, POLISHED, SEVEN, SPROUT, STRAP, STUMP, TIMBER, WRITER]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "30"
    },
    {
        "idx": "47",
        "question": "Y B E I C R N H B D D G H I H X X N P I U I G O Y H V T A H X J C O J\nJ V C F N L R G F O U F S R A R K Z C H Z M V V U I Y N S E V E N T Y\nY Y X T R O N O A D C O G M A H P A U M E D I U M A X Z Z C A R T E S\nW E G M N S R K C M H R S F E I R C Q D A U X P L I U O X K X E R O X\nO T M P Y E K Q I C Q I M O D A L D L O Q M L T R I H V H P E M Z Z W\nI J N V C G G T N A E E M Y G M R D U Y H O S Z F E J H D S P I G V X\nK D N T Y U Y J G J B N M A B O D Y S W B F I D K E C P M M C V V U H\nS G M G R Q T V Z X Y T F H R C G H E X T R E M E L Y E K M Z A D N X\nR H K R K H S Y K Q H A Q Z B Q X F F K E H E N K H I X D W K D X U M\nK Q J Z Y U U J Y W M L Y V D T M X W F W M N Y G Z P W N E X L M T Z\nC Y R E F T T M P U J P S W C M C R U M F H L O K C V O L S N I M D H\nQ K G X J U E K D C D M J V D N Z F N C U P V P O A H X T F Q T D U G\nV Z P I B X W W J E R Y B C H O U P M D T P Y G Z C N D W A P L A Q Y\nJ M U G Z F U L L N E E E Z R R U H S T V Y L Z E Q V O M Z D W F N J\nA C W O D E B Z I H C I K O S Q A F T N L G W V M R D L Q H F W W E V\nT A O X J I Y K Q X K E P Q N S A K R E C C C X X Q Y M T V U L G A R\nC K G O B Q S Y X T K K H L H F V Q A B L S T M I I U M I I T Q A R B\nZ U X G J N E C E D I V K F Y O K E N Z E C F Y A U Z O D W B O O W T\nD J X Q V D U J O H Q D S K G T E N G S A B V K Z W H N Q P B I S E H\nF U T B F O F P W U E O O M Q E B M E E N D E E O E I K K F D P N C O\nZ R F O K S M W I X R F V Y S R K O K E Z N G F U Z P S H A H F K D O\nY S D V K G Y W V E M S J Y Q F S X E X D X V D J J O Q R Q O F X Y M\nE W K H O W V U O Y W W E R K Z R Q O C Y C B F F G Z H R D V J W E Z\nM X G G S L W L W R L C B F Z Y K T I L O P N T K R X Q J E F B B A R\nH H C X T O K T A H P V C T E K E P U U H V K M H J M G B V F D F J M\nP S N M W V K V F H Z Z Z K O T E S X S T T G W L E H C O O G C O E J\nW K P L I K C W B H R E G I Z C S C I I L K Y W A B O A C T Q G M P I\nJ Q P W X O U L A U Q C W V B J N P R V Z N T M J H Q R R E I Z D Q U\nX F W V A A V T O U D F E N G T D X O E F O V V Q N D D Y M A Q G T O\nU K L K I P T G Q D C I Q M B I Q R J W V N M W F K Q F N H T A W D V\nS R R M M K M D S J R S K G Q V S C L P I R O B J R A J Y O Y V Y S F\nZ C U F N A G H L S F Z L M Q H O U Y C Y Z N X L J X S R S I Z N E J\nB A C D T T Z M B U H H T L I D T L P Z D T H R U S T I N G O S Q A U\nK I V B Z F X X R E D D I S H K V F Q F U K T J K X K E M T W I W Z T\nC O E R X K D R O E T S K V J R G K S Q A M M Q Q V A D Z K O V X R K",
        "answer": "[[CLEAN, DEVOTE, DISCOURSE, EXCLUSIVE, EXTREMELY, FACING, MEDIUM, ORIENTAL, PRECEDENT, REDDISH, SEVENTY, SMEAR, STRANGE, THEORY, THRUSTING, VULGAR]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "35"
    },
    {
        "idx": "48",
        "question": "A R G I D M Z Z L A\nP S U B I P J C U B\nP E O H S Y Z A O H\nA P L Y H L J Q S R\nR A I R O N L Y D S\nA R V Z N F X P O E\nT A N Q O M R M O V\nU T Z A R J W D W Q\nS E S C Z U N M R H\nP D K X E A T U X Q",
        "answer": "[[APPARATUS, DISHONOR, SEPARATED]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "49",
        "question": "M B E O F O T Z N R O Y Q L V Q K Y V S I U D G E\nD N P G W K L R B D K Q L J X J D L T Q A N L T B\nW T O I M N G A Q X F A W Q X F T Y J Z A W R Q O\nL U W F Z E S Y L H J L D N F L H G X Q H K Q V X\nV A D T D B B W R F A V G E I F T O T F T I A P G\nW E V Z V P H P T Q O Y T T C S C J S X J F D Q M\nG P V H B V C R M Z I D E P T Z H O E H H W R I A\nU I R T E A M D L F F D S K I N C C H V I J S Y T\nG J A H S T J L Q T N V V H O N E B A F P X Q L T\nM Z A U T T R A N S M I T F N S D H U L D V X T E\nQ X K M O Z D N B E M B R Y O D M X W N J T E O R\nM U L B W T T B C I M L U O A Z R M X W D Q C A E\nE W C K R J H Z H N O L C E D E Q T E J N L E P K\nU S B G I Y T N O Y Y J V R U V L M A D T N E W H\nT I T U R F S M U K U P O T E R C A C G I V P P E\nG U F A M R O G H A F K L T K A F C V E I A K A U\nZ N U D T Q U A S O T Q U Z S B T N A A X K T Z T\nK M B C A E N W A C C W N I I F O E G G Z D T E K\nZ V V V V M D T N G Z W T J T D T Q K L M I B R J\nR K W T I U J W L I P P A Q O C H A T O G H J N F\nT H N Q X L Q R T C M X R F B O R C E O Q Y Z V Z\nR W Q R A Z P W B M Y W Y F K B O H B U S M D E Q\nA L B K S S C M Y I L N P N G G D E D A J O F E X\nD Y X Q W C Z H P Y F A P L A J B E L T M T A W Q\nE X P E B N Z N D R U J N S N L Z J H R K R L D J",
        "answer": "[[BESTOW, BUNDLE, CREATE, EMBRYO, ESTATE, FICTION, MATTER, MEDIATE, SOUND, TRADE, TRANSMIT, VOLUNTARY]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "25"
    },
    {
        "idx": "50",
        "question": "G B M Z C I S Q C H B E A T D X Q B Y H E W B E T C L B\nL R L A T E R A L H D Q H N V B S B G T S S F G F G G E\nY T I S S E C E N C A F A W L P G H A M M F Q S H B C G\nX D D G S V P N O Y G G Z X G S T M X E P H U W Z G H D\nP L R E A S O N A E Q I O Z R G I H V M D Z R E K H V D\nH O N P Z K N J X K X K C O Z N N L C A P X H R L O F I\nR J P X J U W J X P N P F D A M W B O V W E L T J M E Z\nC B B F G F A A C H D E Y N E J L M H H F I B A W K H T\nQ D D L K F R I E Q P V I U P C R P X H U O R Y F F W Q\nL Z K J O H X G V A A E F X W F L L C D N N A E W J B Y\nK W Z F E P L A C E N T A C Q X G A O A W N T W X M X Z\nR E D R U M P S S U C O K B H K B A R L Z U F S Q N T B\nI F B G S O R D I Y C Z K E H Y N Y I A F E X P E L E Y\nX V E S X L U Z V X F D V T T N B F R Z T V Y G L S R H\nW T X N L E Y Z E Y E A S A C F W P B U J I E S L X R E\nE I T H U N L K T T O S B W V X S R N X G Z O O A E E L\nQ C F U K O I M L U T H C R R X A O O F Z E R N U M S X\nQ K A L E E E V F N G C T E I B W C X Q N T P P D J T R\nH P U B E M Z L S M G T B I M C T E I P F A Z I I L R H\nW I K J X U L T E H T Q Z Y S V R S Q R Z Y P O T L I F\nU C D Q Q S Q V P M V R K E U Z P Z I Y C S R I C B A U\nG Q Z T M F Y F S V E H S C H J Q J R O S B N T N X L G\nK D O F K C A W W J R N O G S V C I Q E N F X I J K Y V\nC J Y B E N Z U C W K C T Q O V K J Y F F H P D T V V P\nG N H I W Z Y J L K U O T A V Q N B Z C D R Q R U R B K\nW W O B G G C G A T U C T D Y O P Y O J U O N V G R C X\nE Q Y G V T B A F I A P H J U L I R Y M C R J B Q W F U\nH H P W V Q E M H I M I O K A I J D M J V G G X L H R M",
        "answer": "[[DECLARATION, ELEMENTARY, EXPEL, FABRIC, FAULT, INANIMATE, LATERAL, MURDER, NECESSITY, PLACENTA, PROCESSION, REASON, TERRESTRIAL]]",
        "rule_id": "8",
        "length": "28"
    },
    {
        "idx": "51",
        "question": "  4 4 3 4 4 3 1 2 3 2 3 3\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n1 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n  3 4 3 3 3 1 2 4 5 2 2 4\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[1 2 9 8 3 10 12 7 5 11 6 4,5 6 2 7 8 1 3 12 4 9 11 10,8 10 4 6 2 3 9 11 7 5 1 12,2 12 7 10 4 9 5 1 6 8 3 11,12 5 1 9 11 7 6 2 3 10 4 8,10 9 11 3 12 4 7 8 1 6 2 5,7 1 10 11 6 8 2 9 12 4 5 3,9 7 8 4 5 11 1 10 2 3 12 6,6 3 12 1 10 2 4 5 11 7 8 9,4 11 6 12 7 5 8 3 10 2 9 1,11 8 3 5 1 6 10 4 9 12 7 2,3 4 5 2 9 12 11 6 8 1 10 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "52",
        "question": "  3 3 2 3 2 1 4 5\n6 X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X 3\n5 X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X 1\n1 X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X 3\n  2 3 4 1 4 3 2 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[1 3 5 6 7 8 4 2,7 6 8 2 3 1 5 4,5 1 2 7 8 4 6 3,3 2 1 4 6 7 8 5,4 8 6 1 5 2 3 7,6 4 7 5 2 3 1 8,8 7 4 3 1 5 2 6,2 5 3 8 4 6 7 1]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "8"
    },
    {
        "idx": "53",
        "question": "  3 4 3 4 2 2 1\n3 X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X X 5\n2 X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X 3\n  3 2 4 1 3 2 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[5 2 1 3 4 6 7,6 1 4 5 7 2 3,2 4 7 6 3 1 5,7 5 6 4 2 3 1,1 7 3 2 5 4 6,4 3 5 1 6 7 2,3 6 2 7 1 5 4]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "54",
        "question": "  2 3 2 2 1\n2 X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X 4\n1 X X X X X 3\n  1 2 3 2 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[4 3 2 1 5,2 4 1 5 3,1 2 5 3 4,3 5 4 2 1,5 1 3 4 2]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "55",
        "question": "  2 3 2 1\n3 X X X X 1\n1 X X X X 3\n2 X X X X 2\n2 X X X X 2\n  3 1 2 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[2 1 3 4,4 3 1 2,3 2 4 1,1 4 2 3]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "56",
        "question": "  3 2 3 5 1 3\n3 X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X 1\n1 X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X 3\n  2 2 2 1 4 4\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[4 5 3 1 6 2,2 6 1 3 5 4,5 3 4 2 1 6,6 1 2 4 3 5,1 2 6 5 4 3,3 4 5 6 2 1]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "57",
        "question": "  5 1 2 2 4 3 2 2 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X 5\n4 X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X X X X 6\n2 X X X X X X X X X 3\n  2 5 3 3 1 3 4 2 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[2 9 8 7 3 4 6 1 5,6 3 1 5 7 8 4 9 2,1 2 7 4 6 3 9 5 8,7 8 6 9 1 2 5 4 3,3 4 2 1 8 5 7 6 9,8 5 3 6 2 9 1 7 4,4 7 9 2 5 1 8 3 6,9 6 5 8 4 7 3 2 1,5 1 4 3 9 6 2 8 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "58",
        "question": "  2 4 3 1 4 5 4 2 3 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n1 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n5 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n  4 4 3 4 1 2 3 4 2 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[2 3 8 10 6 1 5 9 7 4,10 4 9 5 3 6 8 2 1 7,5 7 2 8 4 3 9 10 6 1,9 6 5 2 1 7 10 8 4 3,4 10 6 7 2 9 1 3 8 5,6 9 7 3 8 5 4 1 10 2,3 2 1 4 9 8 7 6 5 10,8 1 10 9 7 4 2 5 3 6,1 8 4 6 5 10 3 7 2 9,7 5 3 1 10 2 6 4 9 8]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "59",
        "question": "  1 2 3 2 3 3 3 3 4 3 3\n1 X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 1\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n  3 3 5 2 5 2 2 3 1 3 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[11 10 2 1 6 9 5 7 8 3 4,7 4 8 11 3 2 1 10 5 9 6,6 9 11 4 8 1 10 3 7 5 2,9 8 10 3 1 7 6 2 4 11 5,8 1 6 2 7 4 9 5 3 10 11,1 7 9 5 4 3 8 11 2 6 10,2 5 4 9 11 10 3 8 6 7 1,5 11 3 8 10 6 2 1 9 4 7,10 6 5 7 9 8 11 4 1 2 3,3 2 7 6 5 11 4 9 10 1 8,4 3 1 10 2 5 7 6 11 8 9]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "11"
    },
    {
        "idx": "60",
        "question": "  2 3 3 5 3 1 4 2 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X X 6\n3 X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X 3\n  4 4 3 1 2 6 2 2 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[4 2 7 3 6 9 1 8 5,9 6 3 1 4 8 2 5 7,2 3 8 5 1 6 7 4 9,5 9 2 6 8 7 4 3 1,7 8 6 4 5 3 9 1 2,1 7 9 8 3 2 5 6 4,8 4 1 2 9 5 6 7 3,6 1 5 7 2 4 3 9 8,3 5 4 9 7 1 8 2 6]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "61",
        "question": "  3 1 2 3 2\n2 X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X 1\n1 X X X X X 4\n  1 2 3 2 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[3 5 1 2 4,1 2 5 4 3,4 1 3 5 2,2 3 4 1 5,5 4 2 3 1]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "62",
        "question": "  4 3 2 3 3 2 4 1\n6 X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X 4\n1 X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X 2\n  2 3 3 4 1 4 2 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[3 1 4 5 6 7 2 8,1 7 3 4 2 8 5 6,6 2 8 7 3 5 1 4,2 5 6 8 1 4 7 3,5 4 2 6 7 3 8 1,7 8 1 3 5 6 4 2,8 6 7 1 4 2 3 5,4 3 5 2 8 1 6 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "8"
    },
    {
        "idx": "63",
        "question": "  4 3 2 4 2 3 4 2 1 4 2\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 6\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n1 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 1\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n  2 4 3 3 5 3 2 2 6 1 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[6 7 5 1 2 4 8 9 11 3 10,7 8 1 6 11 2 3 4 10 9 5,5 1 11 10 9 3 6 8 4 7 2,10 5 2 11 3 8 1 7 9 6 4,8 3 6 7 10 11 9 2 5 4 1,2 11 9 4 7 6 10 1 8 5 3,11 10 4 2 8 7 5 6 3 1 9,1 6 10 5 4 9 7 3 2 8 11,3 9 7 8 5 10 4 11 1 2 6,4 2 3 9 6 1 11 5 7 10 8,9 4 8 3 1 5 2 10 6 11 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "11"
    },
    {
        "idx": "64",
        "question": "  3 2 2 2 3 3 1 2 5\n3 X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X 4\n1 X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X X 2\n  3 5 2 5 1 3 6 3 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[4 3 7 6 5 2 9 8 1,6 1 3 9 8 7 2 4 5,5 2 9 8 3 6 4 1 7,1 9 6 5 7 4 8 3 2,9 5 1 2 4 3 7 6 8,2 8 5 7 6 1 3 9 4,8 7 2 4 1 9 6 5 3,3 6 4 1 2 8 5 7 9,7 4 8 3 9 5 1 2 6]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "65",
        "question": "  3 2 2 3 1 3\n3 X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X 1\n1 X X X X X X 4\n  1 2 2 4 3 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[4 3 5 2 6 1,2 6 4 3 1 5,3 1 2 6 5 4,1 4 6 5 2 3,5 2 1 4 3 6,6 5 3 1 4 2]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "66",
        "question": "  2 2 2 3 3 3 1 2 3 4 5 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X X 1\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n6 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n  4 4 4 3 4 2 3 4 1 2 2 5\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[11 3 9 10 4 5 12 8 7 2 6 1,8 12 5 7 10 4 1 3 11 9 2 6,3 1 4 11 7 10 6 12 8 5 9 2,5 10 12 2 6 1 7 4 9 3 8 11,7 8 2 4 5 9 3 11 10 6 1 12,2 5 8 1 12 3 4 9 6 11 7 10,6 9 11 12 3 8 5 2 1 7 10 4,12 6 10 8 11 7 2 1 3 4 5 9,9 4 3 6 1 12 10 5 2 8 11 7,10 11 6 5 9 2 8 7 4 1 12 3,4 7 1 9 2 6 11 10 5 12 3 8,1 2 7 3 8 11 9 6 12 10 4 5]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "67",
        "question": "  3 3 4 3 1 3 2 3 2 4 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n1 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n6 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n  6 1 4 2 2 3 2 3 5 2 5\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[4 9 3 5 11 2 10 7 1 8 6,9 2 5 10 8 7 6 1 11 3 4,11 8 9 2 6 3 7 5 10 4 1,5 10 1 11 2 6 8 4 9 7 3,8 3 2 7 4 5 1 10 6 9 11,10 6 11 8 7 4 3 9 2 1 5,7 1 6 4 5 11 9 8 3 10 2,6 4 8 3 1 9 5 2 7 11 10,2 7 10 6 3 1 4 11 8 5 9,3 5 7 1 9 10 11 6 4 2 8,1 11 4 9 10 8 2 3 5 6 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "11"
    },
    {
        "idx": "68",
        "question": "  2 2 3 4 2 4 1\n2 X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X 5\n3 X X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X 2\n5 X X X X X X X 2\n  3 3 2 2 2 1 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[6 1 2 4 5 3 7,3 7 6 5 1 4 2,2 5 7 3 4 6 1,7 4 1 6 3 2 5,4 2 3 1 7 5 6,5 6 4 7 2 1 3,1 3 5 2 6 7 4]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "69",
        "question": "  3 3 2 2 5 4 3 1 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X 5\n1 X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X 4\n  2 3 4 4 2 1 2 3 4\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[2 4 8 6 3 1 7 9 5,4 1 6 9 2 7 8 5 3,1 7 9 5 4 8 6 3 2,9 5 4 1 6 3 2 7 8,3 2 7 8 5 4 1 6 9,6 9 2 4 8 5 3 1 7,7 8 5 3 1 6 9 2 4,5 3 1 7 9 2 4 8 6,8 6 3 2 7 9 5 4 1]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "70",
        "question": "  1 4 2 2 2 4 3\n1 X X X X X X X 5\n2 X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X 2\n5 X X X X X X X 1\n  4 3 2 2 3 2 1\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[7 2 6 4 5 3 1,5 3 7 1 2 4 6,3 1 2 7 4 6 5,6 5 1 3 7 2 4,1 7 4 2 6 5 3,4 6 3 5 1 7 2,2 4 5 6 3 1 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "71",
        "question": "  2 3 1 4 3 2 5 4\n2 X X X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X 2\n  4 1 3 2 5 4 3 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[7 5 8 2 4 6 1 3,8 7 2 4 6 1 3 5,3 1 5 7 8 2 4 6,1 6 3 5 7 8 2 4,4 2 6 1 3 5 7 8,6 4 1 3 5 7 8 2,5 3 7 8 2 4 6 1,2 8 4 6 1 3 5 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "8"
    },
    {
        "idx": "72",
        "question": "  4 1 4 3 2 2 3 2\n2 X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X 2\n1 X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X 2\n  2 3 2 4 3 3 1 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[1 8 4 2 7 3 5 6,4 1 6 5 3 8 7 2,7 5 3 1 6 2 4 8,5 2 7 8 4 6 1 3,3 7 8 4 2 5 6 1,6 4 2 7 8 1 3 5,8 3 1 6 5 7 2 4,2 6 5 3 1 4 8 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "8"
    },
    {
        "idx": "73",
        "question": "  1 2 5 2 3 3 3 4 2 5\n1 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n5 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n5 X X X X X X X X X X 6\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 5\n5 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n  6 2 4 4 2 2 1 3 3 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[10 9 2 6 4 1 7 3 8 5,3 7 4 1 8 9 5 2 10 6,9 2 5 10 6 3 4 7 1 8,2 5 8 9 10 7 6 4 3 1,4 6 10 7 3 5 1 8 2 9,8 1 3 5 2 6 9 10 4 7,7 4 6 3 1 2 8 5 9 10,6 10 9 4 7 8 3 1 5 2,1 3 7 8 5 10 2 9 6 4,5 8 1 2 9 4 10 6 7 3]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "74",
        "question": "  4 3 1 3 3 2 5 4 2 3 3 5\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 1\n  2 3 5 4 3 4 4 2 2 3 3 1\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[5 6 12 8 10 7 3 4 11 9 1 2,1 4 3 10 2 12 5 8 9 6 11 7,7 1 10 9 6 8 2 11 3 5 12 4,6 2 11 12 3 1 9 7 8 10 4 5,4 7 9 3 5 11 6 12 10 2 8 1,10 3 4 1 11 6 8 5 7 12 2 9,8 12 6 5 1 9 4 3 2 7 10 11,9 10 1 7 12 5 11 2 4 8 6 3,3 9 7 4 8 2 12 6 1 11 5 10,2 5 8 11 9 4 10 1 12 3 7 6,12 11 2 6 4 10 7 9 5 1 3 8,11 8 5 2 7 3 1 10 6 4 9 12]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "75",
        "question": "  1 2 3 4 4 2 4 2 3 4\n1 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n  3 4 3 2 1 2 6 4 2 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[10 8 4 6 2 9 1 3 7 5,1 3 9 7 8 6 2 10 5 4,4 7 10 2 6 1 9 5 8 3,3 2 5 9 1 4 10 8 6 7,6 4 2 3 5 8 7 9 10 1,2 10 6 5 3 7 8 1 4 9,9 5 1 8 7 2 6 4 3 10,7 9 8 10 4 3 5 6 1 2,5 6 3 1 9 10 4 7 2 8,8 1 7 4 10 5 3 2 9 6]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "76",
        "question": "  2 3 2 3 5 2 3 4 1 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 6\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n5 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 1\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n1 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n  2 1 3 3 2 4 3 2 4 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[9 2 8 5 4 3 7 1 10 6,4 9 3 6 5 10 8 7 1 2,5 4 10 2 6 1 3 8 7 9,8 7 2 10 3 9 6 5 4 1,6 5 1 9 2 7 10 3 8 4,2 6 7 4 9 8 1 10 3 5,7 1 6 3 8 2 5 4 9 10,3 8 9 1 10 4 2 6 5 7,10 3 4 7 1 5 9 2 6 8,1 10 5 8 7 6 4 9 2 3]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "77",
        "question": "  2 1 3 4 2 3 5 3 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X 5\n2 X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X 4\n1 X X X X X X X X X 5\n  1 4 2 3 2 3 2 3 4\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[8 9 7 3 2 6 1 5 4,5 3 1 4 9 8 2 7 6,4 1 8 2 7 3 5 6 9,3 7 6 1 5 9 8 4 2,2 8 3 5 6 1 4 9 7,6 2 5 9 1 4 7 8 3,7 4 2 6 3 5 9 1 8,1 6 9 8 4 7 3 2 5,9 5 4 7 8 2 6 3 1]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "78",
        "question": "  4 2 3 1 2 2\n3 X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X 1\n4 X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X 3\n  1 2 3 2 3 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[1 5 4 6 3 2,3 4 5 2 1 6,2 1 3 4 6 5,5 2 6 3 4 1,4 6 2 1 5 3,6 3 1 5 2 4]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "79",
        "question": "  1 2 5 4 3 3 3 2\n1 X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X 3\n5 X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X 3\n  3 2 1 2 2 5 4 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[8 6 2 4 5 1 3 7,5 8 4 3 2 6 7 1,3 4 1 6 7 2 8 5,2 5 3 7 4 8 1 6,6 1 5 2 8 7 4 3,4 2 7 1 3 5 6 8,7 3 6 8 1 4 5 2,1 7 8 5 6 3 2 4]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "8"
    },
    {
        "idx": "80",
        "question": "  4 5 3 2 5 3 2 3 4 1\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n1 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n  2 3 3 3 1 3 5 4 2 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[6 2 8 5 4 7 9 3 1 10,8 4 9 10 3 2 1 6 5 7,7 1 2 6 5 9 4 10 3 8,3 7 6 1 2 10 8 4 9 5,1 6 5 2 8 3 10 9 7 4,5 8 10 4 9 6 7 1 2 3,4 10 3 9 7 5 6 2 8 1,9 3 1 7 6 4 5 8 10 2,10 9 7 3 1 8 2 5 4 6,2 5 4 8 10 1 3 7 6 9]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "81",
        "question": "  3 4 1 2 2 3 3 5 3 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n1 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n  5 3 3 2 4 2 3 1 4 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[8 3 10 2 9 6 4 1 5 7,9 4 5 10 6 1 2 7 3 8,2 9 7 1 10 5 6 3 8 4,7 5 2 4 8 9 3 6 10 1,10 6 8 7 5 3 1 4 9 2,6 2 3 5 1 7 10 8 4 9,1 10 4 3 7 8 5 9 2 6,5 1 9 8 3 4 7 2 6 10,4 8 1 6 2 10 9 5 7 3,3 7 6 9 4 2 8 10 1 5]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "82",
        "question": "  3 4 3 2 5 4 2 3 1\n4 X X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X X X X 5\n4 X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X 5\n  3 2 1 3 2 2 3 2 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[6 1 7 8 2 3 5 4 9,4 3 2 7 1 5 9 8 6,3 8 6 9 4 7 2 5 1,8 5 1 2 3 9 6 7 4,9 2 8 4 7 1 3 6 5,5 7 4 6 8 2 1 9 3,2 6 5 3 9 4 8 1 7,7 9 3 1 5 6 4 2 8,1 4 9 5 6 8 7 3 2]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "83",
        "question": "  6 3 4 2 4 3 2 3 1 3 4\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 5\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n1 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X 1\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n  2 4 2 3 4 3 3 2 3 1 2\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[1 6 2 7 3 5 10 4 11 9 8,4 10 7 11 8 1 3 2 6 5 9,5 11 4 2 10 9 6 1 7 8 3,6 5 3 8 4 11 1 10 9 7 2,8 2 5 1 11 3 7 9 4 10 6,11 9 10 3 1 7 5 6 8 2 4,9 7 1 4 6 8 11 5 2 3 10,3 4 9 5 7 10 2 8 1 6 11,2 3 11 6 9 4 8 7 10 1 5,7 8 6 10 5 2 9 11 3 4 1,10 1 8 9 2 6 4 3 5 11 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "11"
    },
    {
        "idx": "84",
        "question": "  4 2 4 3 2 5 1 4 2 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n5 X X X X X X X X X X 2\n1 X X X X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X X X X 5\n  2 3 1 5 3 2 3 3 4 4\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[7 9 3 2 6 1 10 4 8 5,5 2 6 9 3 4 8 1 10 7,8 4 9 1 2 5 6 7 3 10,9 8 7 10 5 6 1 3 4 2,4 3 8 6 10 2 5 9 7 1,2 10 5 8 7 3 4 6 1 9,3 7 4 5 1 10 2 8 9 6,6 5 1 7 4 8 9 10 2 3,10 1 2 4 9 7 3 5 6 8,1 6 10 3 8 9 7 2 5 4]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "10"
    },
    {
        "idx": "85",
        "question": "  4 2 4 4 3 3 2 3 4 2 1\n5 X X X X X X X X X X X 1\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n1 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n  4 5 2 1 3 2 2 4 5 3 3\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[3 1 7 2 5 9 6 8 4 10 11,2 11 8 1 10 6 5 9 3 4 7,8 6 10 9 1 3 2 4 7 11 5,6 10 3 5 7 1 11 2 9 8 4,10 3 1 4 9 7 8 11 5 6 2,7 9 5 8 2 4 3 10 11 1 6,4 2 11 3 6 8 9 7 10 5 1,11 8 6 7 3 10 4 5 1 2 9,9 5 4 6 11 2 1 3 8 7 10,5 4 2 10 8 11 7 1 6 9 3,1 7 9 11 4 5 10 6 2 3 8]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "11"
    },
    {
        "idx": "86",
        "question": "  3 4 4 2 2 1 4\n4 X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X 2\n1 X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X 3\n3 X X X X X X X 2\n6 X X X X X X X 1\n  3 3 2 3 2 3 1\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[3 1 4 6 5 7 2,6 4 5 7 2 1 3,7 5 2 1 3 4 6,2 7 1 3 4 6 5,4 3 6 5 7 2 1,5 6 7 2 1 3 4,1 2 3 4 6 5 7]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "87",
        "question": "  2 2 4 3 5 1 3 3 4 3 3 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n1 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 1\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 3\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n3 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 2\n2 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n4 X X X X X X X X X X X X 4\n  5 2 3 1 3 4 4 4 2 3 2 6\nPlease provide each element that is unknown under 'X' in order from left to right, and from top to bottom, with each element separated by a space and each row separated by a comma. Ensure that your final answer is wrapped in double square brackets.",
        "answer": "[[2 11 7 10 8 12 6 5 4 9 3 1,12 4 6 7 9 10 8 1 5 3 11 2,4 8 2 1 10 5 12 3 9 7 6 11,10 5 8 6 3 7 9 2 1 11 4 12,6 2 3 9 4 8 11 10 12 5 1 7,7 1 9 8 11 6 3 12 2 4 5 10,3 7 5 4 2 11 1 8 6 12 10 9,11 6 1 5 12 4 2 9 8 10 7 3,5 9 12 2 7 1 10 11 3 6 8 4,9 10 4 11 1 3 5 6 7 2 12 8,8 12 11 3 5 9 4 7 10 1 2 6,1 3 10 12 6 2 7 4 11 8 9 5]]",
        "rule_id": "25",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "88",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n13 6 6 10\n",
        "answer": "[[(13 + (6 / 6)) + 10]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "89",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n3 2 13 3\n",
        "answer": "[[(3 / 2) * (13 + 3)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "90",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n8 1 3 5\n",
        "answer": "[[(8 + 1) + (3 * 5)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "91",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n6 4 2 7\n",
        "answer": "[[(6 + 4) + (2 * 7)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "92",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n3 3 7 1\n",
        "answer": "[[(3 + (3 * 7)) / 1]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "93",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n8 3 7 12\n",
        "answer": "[[(8 - 3) + (7 + 12)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "94",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n13 5 2 4\n",
        "answer": "[[(13 - (5 + 2)) * 4]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "95",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n4 8 12 6\n",
        "answer": "[[(4 + 8) * (12 / 6)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "96",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n9 4 6 4\n",
        "answer": "[[(9 * 4) / (6 / 4)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "97",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n6 1 4 6\n",
        "answer": "[[(6 * (1 + 4)) - 6]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "98",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n12 2 1 13\n",
        "answer": "[[(12 - (2 - 1)) + 13]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "99",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n2 1 3 5\n",
        "answer": "[[(2 + 1) * (3 + 5)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "100",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n12 13 9 11\n",
        "answer": "[[(12 * (13 + 9)) / 11]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "101",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n11 9 3 7\n",
        "answer": "[[(11 + 9) - (3 - 7)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "102",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n1 7 1 4\n",
        "answer": "[[(1 * (7 - 1)) * 4]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "103",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n8 9 6 13\n",
        "answer": "[[(8 + 9) - (6 - 13)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "104",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n9 7 2 3\n",
        "answer": "[[(9 + 7) / (2 / 3)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "105",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n13 4 3 1\n",
        "answer": "[[(13 + (4 * 3)) - 1]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "106",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n12 11 8 3\n",
        "answer": "[[(12 - 11) * (8 * 3)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "107",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n7 12 9 4\n",
        "answer": "[[(7 + 12) + (9 - 4)]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "108",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n4 11 9 12\n",
        "answer": "[[(4 - (11 - 9)) * 12]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "109",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n5 9 11 8\n",
        "answer": "[[(5 + (9 - 11)) * 8]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "110",
        "question": "The four randomly selected numbers are:\n6 9 2 1\n",
        "answer": "[[(6 + (9 * 2)) * 1]]",
        "rule_id": "10",
        "length": null
    },
    {
        "idx": "111",
        "question": "X X X 4\nX 4 3 1\n4 X 1 X\n1 X X 3",
        "answer": "[[3 1 2 4,2 4 3 1,4 3 1 2,1 2 4 3]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "112",
        "question": "X 2 3 X\nX X X 2\nX 1 X 3\nX 3 2 1",
        "answer": "[[1 2 3 4,3 4 1 2,2 1 4 3,4 3 2 1]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "113",
        "question": "6 5 X X X 2\n2 3 1 X X 5\n5 6 X X 1 3\n4 1 X X 2 X\nX 4 X X 6 X\n1 X X 3 X X",
        "answer": "[[6 5 4 1 3 2,2 3 1 6 4 5,5 6 2 4 1 3,4 1 3 5 2 6,3 4 5 2 6 1,1 2 6 3 5 4]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "114",
        "question": "X 2 1 X 4 X\nX X X 2 X X\nX 1 3 4 5 2\n2 X 4 6 X 3\n5 3 X X X 4\n1 X X 3 X X",
        "answer": "[[3 2 1 5 4 6,4 6 5 2 3 1,6 1 3 4 5 2,2 5 4 6 1 3,5 3 6 1 2 4,1 4 2 3 6 5]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "115",
        "question": "X X X 4 X X\nX X 4 X 6 2\nX 5 3 X 2 X\n2 X 1 X 4 X\n3 4 6 X X 5\n1 X 5 6 X 4",
        "answer": "[[6 3 2 4 5 1,5 1 4 3 6 2,4 5 3 1 2 6,2 6 1 5 4 3,3 4 6 2 1 5,1 2 5 6 3 4]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "116",
        "question": "X X 5 X X X\n6 X 4 5 X 3\nX 4 X X 6 2\nX X X X 4 X\n1 X 2 6 X 4\n4 3 6 2 5 X",
        "answer": "[[3 1 5 4 2 6,6 2 4 5 1 3,5 4 3 1 6 2,2 6 1 3 4 5,1 5 2 6 3 4,4 3 6 2 5 1]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "117",
        "question": "X X X X\n3 4 1 X\n2 X 4 3\nX X 2 1",
        "answer": "[[1 2 3 4,3 4 1 2,2 1 4 3,4 3 2 1]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "118",
        "question": "X X 4 1\n1 4 X X\nX X 2 X\n2 X 1 4",
        "answer": "[[3 2 4 1,1 4 3 2,4 1 2 3,2 3 1 4]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "119",
        "question": "X X 2 1 X 4\nX X X 2 X 5\nX 4 X 3 5 2\nX X 5 X 1 X\nX X 6 X 4 3\nX X 4 6 2 1",
        "answer": "[[5 6 2 1 3 4,4 1 3 2 6 5,6 4 1 3 5 2,2 3 5 4 1 6,1 2 6 5 4 3,3 5 4 6 2 1]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "120",
        "question": "X 4 3 2\n2 X X X\nX 1 2 X\nX 2 1 X",
        "answer": "[[1 4 3 2,2 3 4 1,4 1 2 3,3 2 1 4]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "121",
        "question": "1 2 X X 3 X\n3 X 5 4 X X\n4 5 2 6 1 X\nX 1 3 X X 4\nX X 1 3 X X\nX X X X 4 5",
        "answer": "[[1 2 4 5 3 6,3 6 5 4 2 1,4 5 2 6 1 3,6 1 3 2 5 4,5 4 1 3 6 2,2 3 6 1 4 5]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "122",
        "question": "X X X X X 7 2 9 6\n4 X 9 2 X X X 3 X\nX 6 X X X 8 7 1 4\n6 X 4 X 2 3 9 8 5\nX 5 X 8 4 9 6 2 1\nX X X 1 X X 3 4 X\n8 4 6 X X 2 X 7 X\nX X 2 X X X X 5 X\n5 9 X X 7 X X 6 X",
        "answer": "[[1 8 3 4 5 7 2 9 6,4 7 9 2 1 6 5 3 8,2 6 5 9 3 8 7 1 4,6 1 4 7 2 3 9 8 5,3 5 7 8 4 9 6 2 1,9 2 8 1 6 5 3 4 7,8 4 6 5 9 2 1 7 3,7 3 2 6 8 1 4 5 9,5 9 1 3 7 4 8 6 2]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "123",
        "question": "X 7 6 3 4 X 2 X X\n1 8 4 2 X X X X 6\n2 9 3 X 5 X 7 X X\n6 X X X 8 X 3 5 4\nX 4 X X X X X 2 7\n8 3 5 4 X X 6 X X\n7 X 8 5 9 X X X X\n4 5 X 7 6 2 X X X\n3 X 2 X X X X 7 5",
        "answer": "[[5 7 6 3 4 8 2 1 9,1 8 4 2 7 9 5 3 6,2 9 3 1 5 6 7 4 8,6 2 7 9 8 1 3 5 4,9 4 1 6 3 5 8 2 7,8 3 5 4 2 7 6 9 1,7 1 8 5 9 3 4 6 2,4 5 9 7 6 2 1 8 3,3 6 2 8 1 4 9 7 5]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "124",
        "question": "7 8 X 3 4 6 X X X\n3 6 X 7 X X X 8 1\nX 4 X X X X X X X\n4 X X X X 9 2 3 6\nX 9 X X 6 X X X X\nX X 2 4 X X 8 X 9\n9 2 X X 8 X 3 7 5\n8 1 7 5 2 3 X 9 4\nX X 6 9 7 4 X X 8",
        "answer": "[[7 8 1 3 4 6 9 5 2,3 6 5 7 9 2 4 8 1,2 4 9 8 1 5 7 6 3,4 7 8 1 5 9 2 3 6,1 9 3 2 6 8 5 4 7,6 5 2 4 3 7 8 1 9,9 2 4 6 8 1 3 7 5,8 1 7 5 2 3 6 9 4,5 3 6 9 7 4 1 2 8]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "125",
        "question": "X X 1 4\nX 1 X 2\n1 X 2 X\nX 3 4 X",
        "answer": "[[3 2 1 4,4 1 3 2,1 4 2 3,2 3 4 1]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "126",
        "question": "X X X 8 X 6 9 4 X\nX 6 X 4 X 1 7 8 3\nX 1 8 X 3 X 6 X X\n5 X X 7 4 X X X 6\nX 4 6 X 1 X 5 X 9\nX X X 6 X 5 X 3 2\n6 9 7 X 8 3 X 5 X\n1 X 4 2 X 9 3 X X\nX X X 5 X 4 X 9 X",
        "answer": "[[7 2 3 8 5 6 9 4 1,9 6 5 4 2 1 7 8 3,4 1 8 9 3 7 6 2 5,5 3 9 7 4 2 8 1 6,2 4 6 3 1 8 5 7 9,8 7 1 6 9 5 4 3 2,6 9 7 1 8 3 2 5 4,1 5 4 2 7 9 3 6 8,3 8 2 5 6 4 1 9 7]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "127",
        "question": "2 8 X 6 X 5 X X X\nX 5 X 2 3 4 X 7 X\n3 4 7 8 9 X X 2 X\n6 X X 7 X X X 3 X\n7 9 5 4 X 3 X 6 1\nX X X X X 6 7 X X\n5 2 X 3 6 X X X X\nX X 8 9 4 X 3 X X\nX 7 3 5 X 2 X 8 9",
        "answer": "[[2 8 1 6 7 5 9 4 3,9 5 6 2 3 4 1 7 8,3 4 7 8 9 1 5 2 6,6 1 2 7 5 9 8 3 4,7 9 5 4 8 3 2 6 1,8 3 4 1 2 6 7 9 5,5 2 9 3 6 8 4 1 7,1 6 8 9 4 7 3 5 2,4 7 3 5 1 2 6 8 9]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "128",
        "question": "3 X X 1 X X 9 5 4\n4 9 7 5 X X 2 8 X\nX X X X 9 4 X 7 X\nX X X 7 X X X 6 X\nX X X X X 1 5 X 8\n1 2 5 X 6 X X 9 7\n6 X 8 X X X 7 4 X\n2 3 X 6 4 7 8 1 X\nX 1 X 9 X 5 3 X 6",
        "answer": "[[3 6 2 1 7 8 9 5 4,4 9 7 5 3 6 2 8 1,5 8 1 2 9 4 6 7 3,8 4 3 7 5 9 1 6 2,9 7 6 4 2 1 5 3 8,1 2 5 8 6 3 4 9 7,6 5 8 3 1 2 7 4 9,2 3 9 6 4 7 8 1 5,7 1 4 9 8 5 3 2 6]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "129",
        "question": "7 3 4 X X X X X 9\nX X X X 1 8 4 3 6\n6 X 8 X X 4 5 2 X\nX X 7 X X X X 4 X\nX 4 3 X 8 7 2 X X\n5 9 X X X 1 3 7 8\nX 7 X X 6 5 X X 3\nX X 9 1 4 X 7 X 2\n3 5 1 X 7 X X 6 X",
        "answer": "[[7 3 4 2 5 6 8 1 9,9 2 5 7 1 8 4 3 6,6 1 8 3 9 4 5 2 7,2 8 7 5 3 9 6 4 1,1 4 3 6 8 7 2 9 5,5 9 6 4 2 1 3 7 8,4 7 2 9 6 5 1 8 3,8 6 9 1 4 3 7 5 2,3 5 1 8 7 2 9 6 4]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "130",
        "question": "4 8 X X 9 2 X 1 X\nX 9 3 8 X 5 X 4 7\n5 X 2 4 1 X 3 8 9\nX 2 1 6 X 8 4 X 3\nX 5 X 1 3 4 9 2 6\nX X 4 X 2 X 1 X X\nX X X X 7 1 X 9 X\n8 X X X 4 3 X X X\nX X X X X X 7 X X",
        "answer": "[[4 8 7 3 9 2 6 1 5,1 9 3 8 6 5 2 4 7,5 6 2 4 1 7 3 8 9,9 2 1 6 5 8 4 7 3,7 5 8 1 3 4 9 2 6,6 3 4 7 2 9 1 5 8,3 4 6 5 7 1 8 9 2,8 7 9 2 4 3 5 6 1,2 1 5 9 8 6 7 3 4]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "131",
        "question": "4 6 8 2 X X 9 7 X\nX 7 5 8 X 9 2 6 3\nX 9 X X X 7 4 X 8\n8 X 4 X X 6 X 5 X\nX 5 X 4 8 X 6 X X\n3 X 6 X X 5 7 8 X\nX 3 X X X X 8 9 X\nX 8 1 X X X 5 X X\n5 4 X X 7 X 1 X 2",
        "answer": "[[4 6 8 2 3 1 9 7 5,1 7 5 8 4 9 2 6 3,2 9 3 5 6 7 4 1 8,8 2 4 7 1 6 3 5 9,9 5 7 4 8 3 6 2 1,3 1 6 9 2 5 7 8 4,7 3 2 1 5 4 8 9 6,6 8 1 3 9 2 5 4 7,5 4 9 6 7 8 1 3 2]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "132",
        "question": "X X 1 X 7 X X 3 6\n4 X 3 X 8 X 1 9 X\nX X 6 3 X X 2 X 8\nX 1 X X 9 X 6 8 4\nX 4 X X X 8 3 7 X\nX X 8 7 1 4 5 X 9\n8 X 4 X X 9 7 X 3\n3 9 7 X X 5 X X 2\nX 6 X X X 7 X X 5",
        "answer": "[[5 8 1 9 7 2 4 3 6,4 2 3 5 8 6 1 9 7,9 7 6 3 4 1 2 5 8,7 1 5 2 9 3 6 8 4,2 4 9 6 5 8 3 7 1,6 3 8 7 1 4 5 2 9,8 5 4 1 2 9 7 6 3,3 9 7 4 6 5 8 1 2,1 6 2 8 3 7 9 4 5]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "133",
        "question": "X X X 1\n1 X 2 X\n2 1 X X\n3 4 1 X",
        "answer": "[[4 2 3 1,1 3 2 4,2 1 4 3,3 4 1 2]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "134",
        "question": "6 2 5 3 X X\n4 X 3 X 2 X\nX 4 6 X X 3\nX X 1 X 6 X\n3 X 2 X 1 5\n1 X X X 3 X",
        "answer": "[[6 2 5 3 4 1,4 1 3 5 2 6,2 4 6 1 5 3,5 3 1 2 6 4,3 6 2 4 1 5,1 5 4 6 3 2]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "135",
        "question": "2 X 4 3 6 X\nX 5 X 4 X X\nX X X X 4 3\n5 X 3 X 1 X\nX 2 X 1 3 4\n4 3 X X X 2",
        "answer": "[[2 1 4 3 6 5,3 5 6 4 2 1,1 6 2 5 4 3,5 4 3 2 1 6,6 2 5 1 3 4,4 3 1 6 5 2]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "136",
        "question": "X X 2 5 6 X\n5 X X 2 3 X\n1 X 5 X X X\n4 2 3 X 1 X\n2 3 4 X X X\n6 X 1 X X 2",
        "answer": "[[3 4 2 5 6 1,5 1 6 2 3 4,1 6 5 4 2 3,4 2 3 6 1 5,2 3 4 1 5 6,6 5 1 3 4 2]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "137",
        "question": "4 X X 2 X X\nX X X X 4 X\nX 5 6 X 3 2\nX 4 X 5 6 X\nX X 5 X X 4\n2 1 4 6 5 3",
        "answer": "[[4 6 3 2 1 5,5 2 1 3 4 6,1 5 6 4 3 2,3 4 2 5 6 1,6 3 5 1 2 4,2 1 4 6 5 3]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "138",
        "question": "X X X 1\nX X 3 X\nX 3 1 4\n1 4 2 X",
        "answer": "[[3 2 4 1,4 1 3 2,2 3 1 4,1 4 2 3]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "139",
        "question": "1 X X X\n3 X 2 X\nX 1 X 3\nX 3 1 2",
        "answer": "[[1 2 3 4,3 4 2 1,2 1 4 3,4 3 1 2]]",
        "rule_id": "15",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "140",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common prefix so that they form a word:\nabled, abling, able, ability, abilities",
        "answer": "[[dis]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "141",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common suffix so that they form a word:\nabsorpt, abort, abduct, accelerat, accommodat, absolut, aberrat, abominat",
        "answer": "[[ion]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "8"
    },
    {
        "idx": "142",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common prefix so that they form a word:\naugural, adequacy, appropriately, admissible, adequate, accuracies, advertently, appropriate, accurate, ability, active, accessible",
        "answer": "[[in]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "12"
    },
    {
        "idx": "143",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common suffix so that they form a word:\nabnormal, admirab, absolute, actual, aching, absurd, adequate, abrupt, abundant, active, according, accidental, accurate, accident",
        "answer": "[[ly]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "14"
    },
    {
        "idx": "144",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common prefix so that they form a word:\nchief, communication, cellaneous, carry, calculated, calculation, conception, carriage, behave",
        "answer": "[[mis]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "9"
    },
    {
        "idx": "145",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common prefix so that they form a word:\nacting, ader, acted, actions, actor, actors, ached, aders, actionary, ach, aching, acquaint, ad, acquainted, adily, act, acts, aches, active, action",
        "answer": "[[re]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "20"
    },
    {
        "idx": "146",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common prefix so that they form a word:\nable, armed, attainable, acceptable, bearable, answered, authorized, affected, advisedly, annoced, balanced, appreciated, avoidable, available, attended, appealing, attractive, aware, animous, attached, animously",
        "answer": "[[un]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "21"
    },
    {
        "idx": "147",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common suffix so that they form a word:\ncold, baro, cleanli, bad, empti, clever, bald, competitive, effective, cool, black, close, big, dull, blind, dark, bitter, aware, dizzi, cute, busi, clumsi, awkward, assertive, conscious, crazi, careless",
        "answer": "[[ness]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "27"
    },
    {
        "idx": "148",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common prefix so that they form a word:\nchief, calculation, behave, conceptions, ery, erable, informed, cellaneous, conception, demeanors, creant, givings, fit, deeds, calculated, fortune, handled, construed, heard, interpret, carriage, erably, guided, carry, communication, hap, fits, interpretation",
        "answer": "[[mis]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "28"
    },
    {
        "idx": "149",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common prefix so that they form a word:\nappointed, appointments, appearing, appears, able, approve, approves, appointment, allowed, agreements, appearance, approval, appeared, agree, appoint, advantage, agreeing, agreement, appearances, approved, appear, appointing, agreed, abling, appoints, abilities, abled, ability, agrees",
        "answer": "[[dis]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "29"
    },
    {
        "idx": "150",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common prefix so that they form a word:\nactions, acting, actor, ad, action, actors, alize, adily, acquaint, ach, actionary, ached, acts, alistic, alism, al, acquainted, alised, ader, ality, ading, adout, alization, alise, alities, act, alistically, adings, ady, ads, alises, aders, acted, alist, active, aches, aching",
        "answer": "[[re]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "37"
    },
    {
        "idx": "151",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common suffix so that they form a word:\namputat, administrat, absolut, adorat, addict, affiliat, anticipat, admiss, ammunit, activat, alliterat, admonit, abort, accelerat, allegat, abominat, absorpt, admirat, ambit, addit, accusat, annihilat, abduct, adopt, accumulat, aggravat, agitat, alienat, aggress, affect, acquisit, alterat, animat, aberrat, altercat, accommodat, act, actualizat",
        "answer": "[[ion]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "38"
    },
    {
        "idx": "152",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common suffix so that they form a word:\nabsorb, advertis, access, admir, agoniz, accept, add, advanc, accus, advis, accelerat, ach, accompany, adjust, act, affect, age, advocat, abduct, aggravat, abus, abid, adopt, activat, admitt, ador, ag, affirm, accommodat, accord, ac, account, adapt, address, achiev, administer, agree, abandon, accomplish",
        "answer": "[[ing]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "39"
    },
    {
        "idx": "153",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common prefix so that they form a word:\ngivings, cellaneous, ery, erable, interpretation, interpreting, conception, creant, demeanors, fit, interpret, hap, behave, carry, chief, interpreted, calculation, conceptions, heard, informed, fortune, judged, construed, erably, calculated, lead, fits, carriage, deeds, handled, guided, communication",
        "answer": "[[mis]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "32"
    },
    {
        "idx": "154",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common suffix so that they form a word:\nadopt, advis, admir, advanc, age, account, advocat, ac, affect, accus, administer, add, accord, aid, abus, accelerat, accommodat, abandon, achiev, activat, agree, affirm, aggravat, advertis, accomplish, adjust, agoniz, access, accompany, adapt, act, address, admitt, ador, abid, ach, accept, abduct, absorb, ag",
        "answer": "[[ing]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "40"
    },
    {
        "idx": "155",
        "question": "For all the following fraction of words, add a common suffix so that they form a word:\nagree, detach, advance, annul, amuse, announce, attach, condi, astonish, com, adjust, acknowledge, content, cle, depart, docu, contain, compart, disagree, commit, compli, disillusion, dismember, conceal, assort, assess, arrange, apart, amend, displace, arraign, argu, advertise, accomplish, develop, confine, assign, disappoint, ce, atone, ele, command, achieve, base, appoint, ail, bereave, abandon",
        "answer": "[[ment]]",
        "rule_id": "2",
        "length": "48"
    },
    {
        "idx": "333",
        "question": "HAHA + HOOF = MOJO",
        "answer": "[[2929 + 2778 = 5707]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "334",
        "question": "NIP * BOY = STOPS",
        "answer": "[[264 * 307 = 81048]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "335",
        "question": "ROBBIN - MIRAGE = GRILL",
        "answer": "[[408817 - 314695 = 94122]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "336",
        "question": "MAKERS - TREK = TURNER",
        "answer": "[[701245 - 6421 = 694824]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "337",
        "question": "HAUNTS - PADRE = TENANT",
        "answer": "[[712064 - 31958 = 680106]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "338",
        "question": "MATT + TAPE = PEEP",
        "answer": "[[2655 + 5683 = 8338]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "339",
        "question": "BANAL - LADEN = LATTE",
        "answer": "[[79293 - 39412 = 39881]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "340",
        "question": "PERISH + GRIN = USHERS",
        "answer": "[[195403 + 8547 = 203950]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "341",
        "question": "CAT * TO = GOWN",
        "answer": "[[146 * 67 = 9782]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "342",
        "question": "ANA * POP = TEASED",
        "answer": "[[353 * 606 = 213918]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "343",
        "question": "EDITOR + RAPTOR = FORBID",
        "answer": "[[468093 + 325093 = 793186]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "344",
        "question": "NE * JOSH = DUNES",
        "answer": "[[34 * 2569 = 87346]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "345",
        "question": "ALT * FUSS = SHREDS",
        "answer": "[[183 * 2955 = 540765]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "346",
        "question": "SEALS + WASHES = INTENT",
        "answer": "[[54785 + 175645 = 230430]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "347",
        "question": "THEE - HOOT = POP",
        "answer": "[[4311 - 3554 = 757]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "348",
        "question": "ROD * AMI = SHOWY",
        "answer": "[[284 * 179 = 50836]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "349",
        "question": "SNIPER - STENO = ALERT",
        "answer": "[[104632 - 15307 = 89325]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "350",
        "question": "KAT * IFS = CRANE",
        "answer": "[[284 * 179 = 50836]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "351",
        "question": "DOE + DEE = ODD",
        "answer": "[[256 + 266 = 522]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "352",
        "question": "TANNED - GLANCE = NECKS",
        "answer": "[[569931 - 476903 = 93028]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "353",
        "question": "FOX * SO = SHUN",
        "answer": "[[124 * 32 = 3968]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "354",
        "question": "MITTEN - RENAME = BRAVED",
        "answer": "[[984461 - 261396 = 723065]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "355",
        "question": "COO + CORY = SIGHS",
        "answer": "[[955 + 9526 = 10481]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "356",
        "question": "HIDDEN - SCABS = BALLS",
        "answer": "[[140096 - 82758 = 57338]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "357",
        "question": "PITIED + PUPPIES = COMPOST",
        "answer": "[[659541 + 6366548 = 7026089]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "358",
        "question": "GRINS - SILLY = RALLY",
        "answer": "[[86542 - 25771 = 60771]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "359",
        "question": "WINK * FAT = TENDED",
        "answer": "[[1329 * 506 = 672474]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "360",
        "question": "WINDY - POT = DEED",
        "answer": "[[10394 - 725 = 9669]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "361",
        "question": "BIMBOS + HOMING = DISOWN",
        "answer": "[[192105 + 602938 = 795043]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "362",
        "question": "OR * DRIP = AURAS",
        "answer": "[[39 * 1948 = 75972]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "363",
        "question": "BAA - ATT = TUT",
        "answer": "[[922 - 266 = 656]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "364",
        "question": "TAXI + FRAUDS = DESIST",
        "answer": "[[4871 + 598263 = 603134]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "365",
        "question": "CHESTY - PRESS = SCHMO",
        "answer": "[[153894 - 72388 = 81506]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "366",
        "question": "KANE * NE = PACKS",
        "answer": "[[6713 * 13 = 87269]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "367",
        "question": "TA * DAY = PAYS",
        "answer": "[[17 * 572 = 9724]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "368",
        "question": "TET * JIB = DECOR",
        "answer": "[[313 * 259 = 81067]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "369",
        "question": "AVERSE - GEYSER = CREAK",
        "answer": "[[346596 - 260965 = 85631]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "370",
        "question": "LACE + ANA = CLAN",
        "answer": "[[6872 + 808 = 7680]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "371",
        "question": "ALT + HART = LOVER",
        "answer": "[[812 + 9842 = 10654]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "372",
        "question": "EYED + DUN = GIZMO",
        "answer": "[[9893 + 364 = 10257]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "373",
        "question": "WORDED - FEEDS = TITS",
        "answer": "[[102484 - 98847 = 3637]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "374",
        "question": "PRAYED - GLOOMY = ALAMO",
        "answer": "[[256390 - 187743 = 68647]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "375",
        "question": "DEALS * DUE = GUINEAS",
        "answer": "[[26830 * 296 = 7941680]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "376",
        "question": "FOX * IFF = UNTIL",
        "answer": "[[287 * 122 = 35014]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "377",
        "question": "DEEDS + OUTDO = SHUSH",
        "answer": "[[26624 + 19321 = 45945]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "378",
        "question": "ATOM * YE = TWISTS",
        "answer": "[[3196 * 47 = 150212]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "379",
        "question": "GOT * DAH = BRACE",
        "answer": "[[179 * 284 = 50836]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "380",
        "question": "VERGER + STOOGE = BIKERS",
        "answer": "[[215415 + 687741 = 903156]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "381",
        "question": "HIRED - MOTTO = OHM",
        "answer": "[[50183 - 49229 = 954]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "382",
        "question": "UM * ANY = AIDS",
        "answer": "[[12 * 307 = 3684]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "383",
        "question": "TWEET + POOPED = TRENDY",
        "answer": "[[94669 + 811863 = 906532]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "384",
        "question": "ABETTED + SADDEST = CARAMBA",
        "answer": "[[3042241 + 6311462 = 9353703]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "385",
        "question": "DOST + FOSSE = SHAKEN",
        "answer": "[[8613 + 96112 = 104725]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "386",
        "question": "FELL * JO = ROLLS",
        "answer": "[[4077 * 23 = 93771]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "387",
        "question": "RIM * OW = REDS",
        "answer": "[[307 * 12 = 3684]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "388",
        "question": "BUM * TROT = VICTORY",
        "answer": "[[394 * 2672 = 1052768]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "389",
        "question": "FEW * YEN = GASSY",
        "answer": "[[364 * 268 = 97552]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "390",
        "question": "THEME + CITIES = FREEZE",
        "answer": "[[52838 + 695980 = 748818]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "391",
        "question": "ERA * EL = NAME",
        "answer": "[[249 * 28 = 6972]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "392",
        "question": "BI * LIER = AGILE",
        "answer": "[[15 * 6504 = 97560]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "393",
        "question": "EXAM * RIP = TASTES",
        "answer": "[[3695 * 214 = 790730]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "394",
        "question": "MORN * BAD = HARDER",
        "answer": "[[5743 * 168 = 964824]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "395",
        "question": "ERASES + PENS = PUDDLE",
        "answer": "[[496747 + 5487 = 502234]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "396",
        "question": "PAM * HMM = GATED",
        "answer": "[[182 * 322 = 58604]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "397",
        "question": "OX * SAC = ROAR",
        "answer": "[[27 * 304 = 8208]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "398",
        "question": "GOONEY - SUIT = FISTS",
        "answer": "[[100367 - 5842 = 94525]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "399",
        "question": "DYED + TABLE = COMBO",
        "answer": "[[4964 + 25816 = 30780]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "400",
        "question": "METERS - MELT = FILING",
        "answer": "[[604012 - 6074 = 597938]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "401",
        "question": "GONG + NA = OXEN",
        "answer": "[[8958 + 57 = 9015]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "402",
        "question": "DRESS + DISKS = UNWIND",
        "answer": "[[89244 + 86434 = 175678]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "403",
        "question": "TAU * IT = THIS",
        "answer": "[[243 * 12 = 2916]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "404",
        "question": "WART * KEN = POTATO",
        "answer": "[[4975 * 162 = 805950]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "405",
        "question": "HAT * TAB = ARISE",
        "answer": "[[143 * 342 = 48906]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "406",
        "question": "THONG - LOO = STILL",
        "answer": "[[90421 - 744 = 89677]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "407",
        "question": "AA * AT = MET",
        "answer": "[[11 * 19 = 209]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "408",
        "question": "NAPS - NAN = SNAP",
        "answer": "[[7496 - 747 = 6749]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "409",
        "question": "ABRUPT - SPOOK = TREK",
        "answer": "[[103576 - 97228 = 6348]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "410",
        "question": "STOWED - DWELL = SISSY",
        "answer": "[[107549 - 95433 = 12116]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "411",
        "question": "TA * CHIN = LEECH",
        "answer": "[[58 * 1264 = 73312]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "412",
        "question": "WRY * WOW = LAUGH",
        "answer": "[[316 * 303 = 95748]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "413",
        "question": "MEDICS - TOMCAT = SISSY",
        "answer": "[[701385 - 647826 = 53559]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "414",
        "question": "EM * SHEET = HANKIE",
        "answer": "[[43 * 17448 = 750264]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "415",
        "question": "MAG * AH = WALL",
        "answer": "[[128 * 25 = 3200]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "416",
        "question": "TOPLESS + PATTEN = SPLASHY",
        "answer": "[[2984133 + 862217 = 3846350]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "417",
        "question": "STIFLE - TREADS = STERN",
        "answer": "[[326574 - 294083 = 32491]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "418",
        "question": "ATE + TIBIA = SCRAP",
        "answer": "[[235 + 39892 = 40127]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "419",
        "question": "SEA * TA = WERE",
        "answer": "[[264 * 14 = 3696]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "420",
        "question": "DOSE + VIDEO = RAPIDS",
        "answer": "[[7824 + 95748 = 103572]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "421",
        "question": "WET + NATTY = SCUBA",
        "answer": "[[617 + 49772 = 50389]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "422",
        "question": "LOG * GULF = REGRET",
        "answer": "[[134 * 4512 = 604608]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "423",
        "question": "SOX * EX = DEKE",
        "answer": "[[429 * 19 = 8151]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "424",
        "question": "LEARN - STEAL = LIST",
        "answer": "[[53162 - 47315 = 5847]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "425",
        "question": "SLIPPED - REALLY = CICELY",
        "answer": "[[1403392 - 897446 = 505946]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "426",
        "question": "OTTO + POOL = AMPLE",
        "answer": "[[6226 + 8669 = 14895]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "427",
        "question": "LITER - PACKS = LIT",
        "answer": "[[60431 - 59827 = 604]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "428",
        "question": "UN * ANA = ARSE",
        "answer": "[[12 * 323 = 3876]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "429",
        "question": "FALSE * AI = SABERS",
        "answer": "[[51083 * 16 = 817328]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "430",
        "question": "MATH * ETA = SALAMI",
        "answer": "[[1403 * 604 = 847412]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "431",
        "question": "OMELET + ATTEMPT = EYESORE",
        "answer": "[[176468 + 5886728 = 6063196]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "432",
        "question": "LO * LEX = BILL",
        "answer": "[[29 * 218 = 6322]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "433",
        "question": "RYE + PUNKY = SHEAR",
        "answer": "[[871 + 49267 = 50138]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "434",
        "question": "STEREO - ROOMS = COUNTS",
        "answer": "[[703534 - 54427 = 649107]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "435",
        "question": "IS * MAY = MOPS",
        "answer": "[[12 * 406 = 4872]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "436",
        "question": "PATTY + PEA = CHILL",
        "answer": "[[79663 + 759 = 80422]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "437",
        "question": "SATYR + CORRAL = LOWERS",
        "answer": "[[97085 + 315574 = 412659]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "438",
        "question": "STEEP + ACTED = DONATE",
        "answer": "[[78443 + 26841 = 105284]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "439",
        "question": "SWAMPS + PASS = RECITE",
        "answer": "[[593785 + 8355 = 602140]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "440",
        "question": "MEL * ORB = LURES",
        "answer": "[[163 * 209 = 34067]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "441",
        "question": "DOOR * BABE = VAMPIRE",
        "answer": "[[3886 * 1410 = 5479260]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "442",
        "question": "IF * REE = JIFF",
        "answer": "[[15 * 277 = 4155]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "443",
        "question": "ERE * FRO = IVORY",
        "answer": "[[202 * 304 = 61408]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "444",
        "question": "FOG + OFF = DEMO",
        "answer": "[[682 + 866 = 1548]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "445",
        "question": "US * PLANE = BLUFFS",
        "answer": "[[37 * 26051 = 963887]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "446",
        "question": "SHRINE + SNAG = ROTTEN",
        "answer": "[[697128 + 6254 = 703382]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "447",
        "question": "FIVES - TRASH = TOR",
        "answer": "[[70451 - 69812 = 639]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "448",
        "question": "GRIME + BRIG = OXYGEN",
        "answer": "[[95427 + 8549 = 103976]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "449",
        "question": "ROSTER - FROM = WELTS",
        "answer": "[[103561 - 7108 = 96453]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "450",
        "question": "BELLY - CUBED = MAD",
        "answer": "[[50226 - 49508 = 718]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "451",
        "question": "KA * OKRA = NANCY",
        "answer": "[[17 * 5167 = 87839]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "452",
        "question": "TEE * FA = AARGH",
        "answer": "[[599 * 74 = 44326]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "453",
        "question": "BINDING + NEEDY = GROOMER",
        "answer": "[[3952954 + 58826 = 4011780]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "454",
        "question": "TUT * CORE = GLOVER",
        "answer": "[[272 * 1984 = 539648]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "455",
        "question": "AMA * FAR = NIFTY",
        "answer": "[[454 * 148 = 67192]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "456",
        "question": "ES * RES = APES",
        "answer": "[[25 * 325 = 8125]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "457",
        "question": "KIDDER + PRAYER = SPACES",
        "answer": "[[129904 + 743604 = 873508]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "458",
        "question": "TUMMY - HANG = YUAN",
        "answer": "[[14337 - 6852 = 7485]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "459",
        "question": "JAG * INTO = DELETE",
        "answer": "[[408 * 2357 = 961656]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "460",
        "question": "MARE * CUE = COYOTE",
        "answer": "[[1035 * 285 = 294975]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "461",
        "question": "YIELD - TAE = OUTER",
        "answer": "[[30541 - 785 = 29756]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "462",
        "question": "UM * PECK = DEALER",
        "answer": "[[64 * 5798 = 371072]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "463",
        "question": "VEE * DOS = OTTER",
        "answer": "[[122 * 574 = 70028]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "464",
        "question": "SLANTED + ANTENNA = IMITATE",
        "answer": "[[1732085 + 3208223 = 4940308]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "465",
        "question": "LUNG * AA = CRUDE",
        "answer": "[[1426 * 55 = 78430]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "466",
        "question": "INN * SH = FILL",
        "answer": "[[177 * 29 = 5133]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "467",
        "question": "LONELY + FLECKS = SELVES",
        "answer": "[[136510 + 815249 = 951759]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "468",
        "question": "LIS * RAG = COSTA",
        "answer": "[[453 * 217 = 98301]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "469",
        "question": "PEACHES - CORRECT = REPORT",
        "answer": "[[7436042 - 6588461 = 847581]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "470",
        "question": "UNITED - DECENT = TENDER",
        "answer": "[[792641 - 143496 = 649145]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "471",
        "question": "TRAMPS - ACCEPT = STENO",
        "answer": "[[514302 - 488605 = 25697]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "472",
        "question": "SLAM + AMEN = SCALE",
        "answer": "[[1692 + 9275 = 10967]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "473",
        "question": "BAD * DO = NOSY",
        "answer": "[[146 * 67 = 9782]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "474",
        "question": "GANG + FRANK = CLERGY",
        "answer": "[[7837 + 96835 = 104672]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "475",
        "question": "TRIPS + STRUTS = IRONIC",
        "answer": "[[50493 + 350753 = 401246]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "476",
        "question": "AREA - BRR = WARE",
        "answer": "[[9369 - 433 = 8936]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "477",
        "question": "CODES + LARVAE = ERRAND",
        "answer": "[[39752 + 460865 = 500617]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "478",
        "question": "SHY * HAT = HORNY",
        "answer": "[[120 * 248 = 29760]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "479",
        "question": "BREECH - ICICLE = PILING",
        "answer": "[[967710 - 515127 = 452583]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "480",
        "question": "GAG + ANA = NAME",
        "answer": "[[989 + 818 = 1807]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "481",
        "question": "DEW * TURN = RATING",
        "answer": "[[208 * 4397 = 914576]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "482",
        "question": "DO * YUK = YIPE",
        "answer": "[[12 * 307 = 3684]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "483",
        "question": "LINGO + FROLIC = PEEING",
        "answer": "[[80216 + 396805 = 477021]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "484",
        "question": "MEW * TIS = ROBOT",
        "answer": "[[167 * 349 = 58283]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "485",
        "question": "NOISY * SI = FORGER",
        "answer": "[[16359 * 53 = 867027]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "486",
        "question": "AR * SAW = BASK",
        "answer": "[[19 * 217 = 4123]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "487",
        "question": "BLESS + NIBBLE = LESSER",
        "answer": "[[73411 + 267734 = 341145]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "488",
        "question": "ARRESTS + CASINO = CAPTAIN",
        "answer": "[[2881575 + 325694 = 3207269]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "489",
        "question": "NINTH - HISS = DENY",
        "answer": "[[14138 - 8422 = 5716]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "490",
        "question": "SMEARS - DENSE = GARNET",
        "answer": "[[315493 - 65735 = 249758]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "491",
        "question": "ELK * VIE = BRAWL",
        "answer": "[[268 * 152 = 40736]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "492",
        "question": "STABBED - OLDEST = POSTERS",
        "answer": "[[5872263 - 913658 = 4958605]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "493",
        "question": "PA * CUP = HAVE",
        "answer": "[[67 * 146 = 9782]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "494",
        "question": "PHOOEY - CHEEP = SEALS",
        "answer": "[[132286 - 73881 = 58405]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "495",
        "question": "CIGAR + DODGE = PROVED",
        "answer": "[[79483 + 56542 = 136025]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "496",
        "question": "SPURS - SPUR = KOBO",
        "answer": "[[10841 - 1084 = 9757]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "497",
        "question": "HA * NOH = FAIL",
        "answer": "[[67 * 146 = 9782]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "498",
        "question": "TEMPEST + DRIPPY = STERNER",
        "answer": "[[2541532 + 709118 = 3250650]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "499",
        "question": "ULCERS + RUBS = COYOTE",
        "answer": "[[697432 + 3652 = 701084]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "500",
        "question": "AWE + HEED = BUGGY",
        "answer": "[[675 + 9553 = 10228]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "501",
        "question": "TOLL + EAGLES = INVEST",
        "answer": "[[8677 + 493741 = 502418]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "502",
        "question": "SHOO + HATH = SEXES",
        "answer": "[[1833 + 8568 = 10401]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "503",
        "question": "PUP * ANE = MUMMY",
        "answer": "[[242 * 309 = 74778]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "504",
        "question": "DYE * IDLE = MOTELS",
        "answer": "[[287 * 1257 = 360759]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "505",
        "question": "SOAR * HIM = ABSURD",
        "answer": "[[4397 * 208 = 914576]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "506",
        "question": "GAUGING + ASSURED = IGNEOUS",
        "answer": "[[3583963 + 5778124 = 9362087]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "507",
        "question": "IS * MEOW = ENSUE",
        "answer": "[[12 * 5608 = 67296]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "508",
        "question": "HA * ANA = POND",
        "answer": "[[23 * 373 = 8579]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "509",
        "question": "MU + MY = YUM",
        "answer": "[[98 + 91 = 189]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "510",
        "question": "SAFELY - LACES = CHARM",
        "answer": "[[162380 - 86731 = 75649]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "511",
        "question": "LAS * ODDLY = CREASES",
        "answer": "[[160 * 29913 = 4786080]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "512",
        "question": "TAJ * PEA = JEEPS",
        "answer": "[[374 * 107 = 40018]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "513",
        "question": "DUD + AD = ANA",
        "answer": "[[181 + 21 = 202]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "514",
        "question": "WONDER - GENTLE = TONED",
        "answer": "[[204875 - 174397 = 30478]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "515",
        "question": "WARNED + REPAID = ARRIVE",
        "answer": "[[274568 + 469738 = 744306]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "516",
        "question": "AS * WIMP = SPLIT",
        "answer": "[[37 * 1962 = 72594]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "517",
        "question": "DYE * SAWS = REPUTE",
        "answer": "[[248 * 1571 = 389608]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "518",
        "question": "USHERS - WELCH = LAZAR",
        "answer": "[[139043 - 60759 = 78284]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "519",
        "question": "STERN - GRAMS = HAG",
        "answer": "[[30495 - 29813 = 682]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "520",
        "question": "PETTY + DELETE = SLIDER",
        "answer": "[[78441 + 286848 = 365289]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "521",
        "question": "DATE + DEER = MOMMA",
        "answer": "[[7892 + 7226 = 15118]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "522",
        "question": "CONES + ROOTS = BIDDER",
        "answer": "[[58943 + 68803 = 127746]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "523",
        "question": "IFS * YO = OILY",
        "answer": "[[173 * 24 = 4152]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "524",
        "question": "CANCER - TRENCH = DISC",
        "answer": "[[703789 - 698372 = 5417]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "525",
        "question": "VAT * ERR = CAGES",
        "answer": "[[179 * 322 = 57638]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "526",
        "question": "SNORT + HATCH = PRINTS",
        "answer": "[[56947 + 83728 = 140675]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "527",
        "question": "WHITE + SCHLEP = LOWEST",
        "answer": "[[42087 + 592671 = 634758]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "528",
        "question": "WOES * NAM = CANAPE",
        "answer": "[[5724 * 168 = 961632]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "529",
        "question": "SHE + PEON = LOADS",
        "answer": "[[537 + 9708 = 10245]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "530",
        "question": "PROP * AY = WRATH",
        "answer": "[[4374 * 19 = 83106]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "531",
        "question": "BONES * OF = HUMBUG",
        "answer": "[[12598 * 27 = 340146]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "532",
        "question": "RIB * MI = RUIN",
        "answer": "[[327 * 12 = 3924]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "533",
        "question": "HOSTS + SHERRY = HUNTER",
        "answer": "[[69585 + 561227 = 630812]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "534",
        "question": "CHORD + MOD = HAWKS",
        "answer": "[[89562 + 752 = 90314]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "535",
        "question": "HOMOS + GODDAM = DOUSED",
        "answer": "[[92523 + 728845 = 821368]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "536",
        "question": "UNDEAD + READ = TIMBER",
        "answer": "[[198738 + 6738 = 205476]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "537",
        "question": "STUN * TED = DATING",
        "answer": "[[1302 * 364 = 473928]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "538",
        "question": "KENT + SPEEDS = PRISON",
        "answer": "[[7435 + 894428 = 901863]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "539",
        "question": "DAY * BID = FICUS",
        "answer": "[[489 * 154 = 75306]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "540",
        "question": "SUBMIT - ORBS = FORTE",
        "answer": "[[107325 - 8671 = 98654]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "541",
        "question": "NOIR * ER = DADDY",
        "answer": "[[1728 * 38 = 65664]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "542",
        "question": "WARSAW - FRIGHT = HEIGHT",
        "answer": "[[465864 - 157932 = 307932]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "543",
        "question": "NAME * TIT = PONDER",
        "answer": "[[1276 * 393 = 501468]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "544",
        "question": "AS * PUFF = TRUTH",
        "answer": "[[69 * 1088 = 75072]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "545",
        "question": "RUG * GANG = FOOLED",
        "answer": "[[183 * 3523 = 644709]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "546",
        "question": "FAX * EX = BEAN",
        "answer": "[[137 * 47 = 6439]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "547",
        "question": "MINDS - JIN = HOBO",
        "answer": "[[10542 - 805 = 9737]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "548",
        "question": "SEES + LEG = GALL",
        "answer": "[[8338 + 739 = 9077]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "549",
        "question": "WHOOSH - BLOUSE = OBSESS",
        "answer": "[[821192 - 651793 = 169399]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "550",
        "question": "DOTTED - EXIT = FEIGN",
        "answer": "[[106681 - 8246 = 98435]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "551",
        "question": "OD * YO = MOO",
        "answer": "[[57 * 15 = 855]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "552",
        "question": "SCOUTS - POLL = OMELET",
        "answer": "[[403264 - 5388 = 397876]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "553",
        "question": "YAP * ON = YETI",
        "answer": "[[307 * 12 = 3684]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "554",
        "question": "WE * LOBE = TOMBS",
        "answer": "[[12 * 5082 = 60984]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "555",
        "question": "LOUDLY - SEXUAL = MOMMA",
        "answer": "[[814980 - 763428 = 51552]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "556",
        "question": "DWARFS + DECADE = SHAKERS",
        "answer": "[[934561 + 907490 = 1842051]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "557",
        "question": "SHREDS - FAILED = SOLO",
        "answer": "[[701427 - 693842 = 7585]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "558",
        "question": "SIP * CAN = FECES",
        "answer": "[[208 * 169 = 35152]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "559",
        "question": "PRICED - CLAMS = LADIES",
        "answer": "[[236504 - 51897 = 184607]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "560",
        "question": "AVA * ZED = GUESS",
        "answer": "[[393 * 154 = 60522]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "561",
        "question": "HUFFED - BANKS = NEEDS",
        "answer": "[[107728 - 65439 = 42289]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "562",
        "question": "MISS - ILL = AMI",
        "answer": "[[1200 - 288 = 912]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "563",
        "question": "LIKELY - DOSES = DIET",
        "answer": "[[106512 - 97454 = 9058]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "564",
        "question": "GRAPE - YAW = EDDY",
        "answer": "[[10649 - 762 = 9887]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "565",
        "question": "MOR * ARF = FEARS",
        "answer": "[[372 * 124 = 46128]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "566",
        "question": "BO * REEF = MIMIC",
        "answer": "[[17 * 3446 = 58582]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "567",
        "question": "DUBBED + TUMBLE = PRESETS",
        "answer": "[[583375 + 489367 = 1072742]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "568",
        "question": "PI * SOCKS = CHIMPS",
        "answer": "[[16 * 25432 = 406912]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "569",
        "question": "OP * PUG = EGOS",
        "answer": "[[16 * 607 = 9712]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "570",
        "question": "FUMES - YUM = TROY",
        "answer": "[[10542 - 705 = 9837]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "571",
        "question": "AIR * TEED = SERIES",
        "answer": "[[184 * 3559 = 654856]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "572",
        "question": "MILLET - PORTS = MEETS",
        "answer": "[[107726 - 95463 = 12263]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "573",
        "question": "STOPS * KA = DEFIES",
        "answer": "[[20812 * 46 = 957352]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "574",
        "question": "RALLY - KAT = FISTS",
        "answer": "[[30551 - 804 = 29747]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "575",
        "question": "GREASY - SONNET = CONES",
        "answer": "[[406532 - 387769 = 18763]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "576",
        "question": "OP * GIST = WASPS",
        "answer": "[[39 * 1864 = 72696]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "577",
        "question": "HAT * DUES = MONTHS",
        "answer": "[[682 * 1430 = 975260]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "578",
        "question": "TRENDY - WRATH = HOODED",
        "answer": "[[305791 - 60832 = 244959]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "579",
        "question": "MITTS + OASIS = ARMOUR",
        "answer": "[[87332 + 61272 = 148604]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "580",
        "question": "GODDAM - GYMS = TANNED",
        "answer": "[[402298 - 4586 = 397712]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "581",
        "question": "PE * ETA = CELL",
        "answer": "[[12 * 274 = 3288]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "582",
        "question": "SHAVE - TOD = PEDRO",
        "answer": "[[50139 - 872 = 49267]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "583",
        "question": "MONEY * HER = IMAGERY",
        "answer": "[[34760 * 268 = 9315680]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "584",
        "question": "TA * IT = VIA",
        "answer": "[[20 * 42 = 840]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "585",
        "question": "BOON + BORA = ABBA",
        "answer": "[[1550 + 1563 = 3113]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "586",
        "question": "WEEP + POPPET = DATING",
        "answer": "[[8664 + 494463 = 503127]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "587",
        "question": "BAR * HM = ARMED",
        "answer": "[[514 * 29 = 14906]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "588",
        "question": "SHERIFF + ASSESS = SINCERE",
        "answer": "[[7034966 + 877377 = 7912343]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "589",
        "question": "HULK + FLASK = UPROAR",
        "answer": "[[8162 + 96372 = 104534]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "590",
        "question": "SHORTS - CASKET = REED",
        "answer": "[[803528 - 798412 = 5116]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "591",
        "question": "UH * LOW = LADY",
        "answer": "[[12 * 307 = 3684]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "592",
        "question": "HON * GRAM = BARRING",
        "answer": "[[807 * 2396 = 1933572]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "593",
        "question": "POW * OUT = BUMPY",
        "answer": "[[159 * 507 = 80613]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "594",
        "question": "AS * CEE = GANG",
        "answer": "[[18 * 233 = 4194]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "595",
        "question": "POURS - HAH = REACH",
        "answer": "[[60154 - 282 = 59872]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "596",
        "question": "DRUDGE - LORAN = TREAT",
        "answer": "[[120189 - 57243 = 62946]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "597",
        "question": "VENEER - TESTS = CHANCE",
        "answer": "[[620223 - 72171 = 548052]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "598",
        "question": "AL * LA = AVA",
        "answer": "[[21 * 12 = 252]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "599",
        "question": "YA * SAD = DEED",
        "answer": "[[21 * 418 = 8778]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "600",
        "question": "NOO * PEA = ARGON",
        "answer": "[[433 * 198 = 85734]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "601",
        "question": "YAWN * NUN = GROCER",
        "answer": "[[1862 * 292 = 543704]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "602",
        "question": "ORATOR + REELED = SPROUTS",
        "answer": "[[867986 + 600305 = 1468291]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "603",
        "question": "BONER + RAZOR = SALINE",
        "answer": "[[92084 + 43624 = 135708]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "604",
        "question": "ABIDE - MAVIS = DAIS",
        "answer": "[[75984 - 67192 = 8792]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "605",
        "question": "AW * KOBO = SLAYED",
        "answer": "[[93 * 7414 = 689502]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "606",
        "question": "UN * ART = ROTO",
        "answer": "[[17 * 486 = 8262]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "607",
        "question": "PASS * RE = FLUFF",
        "answer": "[[1077 * 58 = 62466]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "608",
        "question": "TOOTH * EL = LODGED",
        "answer": "[[43348 * 17 = 736916]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "609",
        "question": "SEVENS + AWARDS = PANAMA",
        "answer": "[[235392 + 414082 = 649474]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "610",
        "question": "PHOEBE - SHOES = RABIES",
        "answer": "[[924010 - 52405 = 871605]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "611",
        "question": "PA * ROAR = NASAL",
        "answer": "[[29 * 3093 = 89697]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "612",
        "question": "SAP + SRI = IRIS",
        "answer": "[[685 + 631 = 1316]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "613",
        "question": "SO + ESS = SOS",
        "answer": "[[50 + 455 = 505]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "614",
        "question": "SIGN * PUN = TACTIC",
        "answer": "[[6057 * 137 = 829809]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "615",
        "question": "CALMER + COMMENT = CARTOON",
        "answer": "[[574826 + 5188293 = 5763119]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "616",
        "question": "ETA + LOGAN = SINCE",
        "answer": "[[867 + 49271 = 50138]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "617",
        "question": "YAK * EN = ACHED",
        "answer": "[[215 * 64 = 13760]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "618",
        "question": "BARREL + BADDER = RANGES",
        "answer": "[[295501 + 298805 = 594306]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "619",
        "question": "REVERE - CUCKOO = BUSY",
        "answer": "[[604060 - 595133 = 8927]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "620",
        "question": "MEW * OHM = SOFAS",
        "answer": "[[497 * 164 = 81508]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "621",
        "question": "MANO + ROLL = RAZOR",
        "answer": "[[9064 + 1477 = 10541]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "622",
        "question": "LUPUS + SEES = SPELL",
        "answer": "[[81019 + 9669 = 90688]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "623",
        "question": "RABBI + ROUTE = AIRMEN",
        "answer": "[[71224 + 75869 = 147093]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "624",
        "question": "SEAM * AG = SINGER",
        "answer": "[[7192 * 98 = 704816]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "625",
        "question": "PRETEXT - SPECTER = WALLETS",
        "answer": "[[3769659 - 2368967 = 1400692]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "626",
        "question": "HEH + GATED = SPELL",
        "answer": "[[868 + 19765 = 20633]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "627",
        "question": "OR * TOR = COMA",
        "answer": "[[14 * 514 = 7196]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "628",
        "question": "REP * AG = FEAR",
        "answer": "[[327 * 19 = 6213]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "629",
        "question": "GREENS - GLASSY = CATTY",
        "answer": "[[925546 - 907663 = 17883]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "630",
        "question": "TIMBER - BEEFY = BELLY",
        "answer": "[[135674 - 67792 = 67882]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "631",
        "question": "FLIRT + DID = PURER",
        "answer": "[[39657 + 868 = 40525]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "632",
        "question": "FIVER - AXIS = FADE",
        "answer": "[[10263 - 8407 = 1856]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "633",
        "question": "GIB * WHIT = SCENES",
        "answer": "[[157 * 2459 = 386063]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "634",
        "question": "YO * NE = ONES",
        "answer": "[[86 * 79 = 6794]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "635",
        "question": "LORD + SULFUR = CORSET",
        "answer": "[[8061 + 398296 = 406357]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "636",
        "question": "DIP * AD = SAGA",
        "answer": "[[397 * 13 = 5161]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "637",
        "question": "ROTATE + GIRLIE = SKATER",
        "answer": "[[258081 + 432731 = 690812]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "638",
        "question": "TAPED - SNORT = SPY",
        "answer": "[[80352 - 79618 = 734]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "639",
        "question": "HARDER - REEKS = GYPSY",
        "answer": "[[148028 - 82293 = 65735]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "640",
        "question": "PRO * HAG = WRAPS",
        "answer": "[[148 * 369 = 54612]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "641",
        "question": "TEN + EVEN = NEAT",
        "answer": "[[834 + 3534 = 4368]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "642",
        "question": "DRYING - HEATED = DITTY",
        "answer": "[[852910 - 763468 = 89442]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "643",
        "question": "RENTS + TYKES = SIMONY",
        "answer": "[[68571 + 72381 = 140952]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "644",
        "question": "TABLET - NUDIE = BYLINE",
        "answer": "[[827648 - 91054 = 736594]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "645",
        "question": "SPECS + WIPED = PHYSIC",
        "answer": "[[81678 + 24169 = 105847]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "646",
        "question": "MARIA - PURE = MERE",
        "answer": "[[10870 - 9285 = 1585]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "647",
        "question": "SAILOR - OPERAS = DEVILS",
        "answer": "[[903128 - 245809 = 657319]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "648",
        "question": "REP * PIT = FUTON",
        "answer": "[[172 * 209 = 35948]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "649",
        "question": "OS * GO = SOL",
        "answer": "[[29 * 32 = 928]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "650",
        "question": "FELLOW - MOUND = SOULS",
        "answer": "[[128893 - 59407 = 69486]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "651",
        "question": "MAR * ON = TOOT",
        "answer": "[[198 * 32 = 6336]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "652",
        "question": "ZEROED - FATHER = HEADER",
        "answer": "[[802504 - 693102 = 109402]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "653",
        "question": "CRITIC + TACO = RANSOM",
        "answer": "[[895658 + 6084 = 901742]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "654",
        "question": "BIOS * LAD = DELTAS",
        "answer": "[[1238 * 546 = 675948]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "655",
        "question": "OCCUR + WOOZY = LUNACY",
        "answer": "[[67750 + 86629 = 154379]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "656",
        "question": "BO * ALSO = PEELS",
        "answer": "[[34 * 1764 = 59976]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "657",
        "question": "TRUMP + GIMMIE = EFFECT",
        "answer": "[[53176 + 847749 = 900925]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "658",
        "question": "FLAME / WEE = FAR",
        "answer": "[[37092 / 122 = 304....4]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "659",
        "question": "OD * ROD = YOKE",
        "answer": "[[14 * 514 = 7196]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "660",
        "question": "TEMPLE - PRANKS = ASSES",
        "answer": "[[806740 - 791235 = 15505]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "661",
        "question": "TAKE + CREAK = MISFIT",
        "answer": "[[8462 + 95246 = 103708]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "662",
        "question": "MID + BABA = PUFFS",
        "answer": "[[752 + 9696 = 10448]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "663",
        "question": "BALLS + HERBAL = PREACH",
        "answer": "[[81332 + 597813 = 679145]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "664",
        "question": "WEEKS + RARE = SMILED",
        "answer": "[[94461 + 8784 = 103245]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "665",
        "question": "ME * EGOS = SPUNKY",
        "answer": "[[86 * 6295 = 541370]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "666",
        "question": "AA * OY = YAP",
        "answer": "[[44 * 17 = 748]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "667",
        "question": "BAG * BRA = DOUBT",
        "answer": "[[184 * 168 = 30912]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "668",
        "question": "PIP * COZ = HOPPY",
        "answer": "[[424 * 185 = 78440]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "669",
        "question": "SLAY + FREELY = POTATO",
        "answer": "[[8415 + 297745 = 306160]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "670",
        "question": "DAY + AY = ADD",
        "answer": "[[894 + 94 = 988]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "3"
    },
    {
        "idx": "671",
        "question": "SWEDES + NAILED = DONATE",
        "answer": "[[260802 + 574908 = 835710]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "672",
        "question": "TA * OAK = MOJO",
        "answer": "[[18 * 289 = 5202]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "673",
        "question": "PLANS + RILE = MISERY",
        "answer": "[[97382 + 5074 = 102456]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "674",
        "question": "RETRO + SEEP = PATOIS",
        "answer": "[[94297 + 8441 = 102738]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "675",
        "question": "MAC * GUT = CROOK",
        "answer": "[[529 * 184 = 97336]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "676",
        "question": "AA * WIN = SHAH",
        "answer": "[[22 * 174 = 3828]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "677",
        "question": "FAN * HAD = FLAGS",
        "answer": "[[704 * 108 = 76032]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "678",
        "question": "AGA * IF = FEEL",
        "answer": "[[474 * 19 = 9006]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "679",
        "question": "GEN * ARF = SOWING",
        "answer": "[[803 * 246 = 197538]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "680",
        "question": "ZAP * MUM = ADMIRE",
        "answer": "[[312 * 595 = 185640]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "681",
        "question": "DEBATE - NOVA = FITTED",
        "answer": "[[304760 - 8157 = 296603]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "682",
        "question": "MOUSY - BLAND = YOM",
        "answer": "[[60134 - 59728 = 406]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "683",
        "question": "STREWN + DEITIES = TINIEST",
        "answer": "[[946175 + 3104019 = 4050194]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "684",
        "question": "DOODLES - MERMAN = TALENT",
        "answer": "[[1661253 - 758704 = 902549]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "685",
        "question": "THRIFT - LEADER = TIDES",
        "answer": "[[842308 - 759152 = 83156]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "686",
        "question": "NAW * HAM = SHRED",
        "answer": "[[357 * 258 = 92106]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "687",
        "question": "ATT * DORY = UNFOLD",
        "answer": "[[233 * 4108 = 957164]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "688",
        "question": "BELLE + WALLED = ROASTS",
        "answer": "[[63113 + 741139 = 804252]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "689",
        "question": "HOT * FEN = GROWS",
        "answer": "[[284 * 179 = 50836]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "690",
        "question": "TOP * MEW = VIEWER",
        "answer": "[[452 * 398 = 179896]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "691",
        "question": "HOODED - AWOKE = DEEDS",
        "answer": "[[155828 - 73542 = 82286]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "692",
        "question": "THONG - WAKES = THO",
        "answer": "[[60431 - 59827 = 604]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "693",
        "question": "MA * CRY = CUBE",
        "answer": "[[12 * 307 = 3684]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "4"
    },
    {
        "idx": "694",
        "question": "SPHERE + SHAKER = RHYTHM",
        "answer": "[[406787 + 462378 = 869165]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "6"
    },
    {
        "idx": "695",
        "question": "SER * IFS = STOOD",
        "answer": "[[384 * 103 = 39552]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "5"
    },
    {
        "idx": "696",
        "question": "DANG * NOD = SICKOS",
        "answer": "[[3812 * 173 = 659476]]",
        "rule_id": "5",
        "length": "7"
    },
    {
        "idx": "697",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*^v*v\n_ _ _ _ _\n***^*\n_ _ _<_ _\n****v\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _<_ _",
        "answer": "[[1, 4, 2, 3, 5, 3, 5, 1, 2, 4, 2, 1, 4, 5, 3, 4, 3, 5, 1, 2, 5, 2, 3, 4, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "698",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _>_\n**^v*\n_ _<_ _ _\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n****^\n_ _ _ _ _\n^***^\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 1, 3, 2, 3, 4, 5, 2, 1, 5, 2, 4, 1, 3, 1, 3, 2, 5, 4, 2, 1, 3, 4, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "699",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_<_ _ _ _\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _<_\n**v*^\n_ _ _ _ _\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 2, 3, 1, 3, 1, 5, 2, 4, 5, 3, 4, 1, 2, 2, 4, 1, 5, 3, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "700",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_>_ _ _<_\n^****\n_ _ _ _ _\nv****\n_ _ _ _ _\nvv***\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 3, 5, 1, 2, 5, 1, 2, 4, 3, 3, 5, 1, 2, 4, 2, 4, 3, 5, 1, 1, 2, 4, 3, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "701",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _>_ _\nv^***\n_ _<_ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _<_ _\n*^**v\n_ _ _<_ _",
        "answer": "[[2, 3, 1, 4, 5, 5, 1, 4, 2, 3, 3, 2, 5, 1, 4, 1, 4, 3, 5, 2, 4, 5, 2, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "702",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n^*v**\n_<_ _<_ _\n*****\n_ _>_ _>_\n*v***\n_ _ _ _ _\n^**v*\n_>_ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 4, 1, 5, 4, 5, 1, 3, 2, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 1, 3, 2, 5, 4, 2, 1, 5, 4, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "703",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_>_ _ _<_\n*****\n_ _ _ _>_\n^****\n_ _>_ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _>_ _\n**vv*\n_ _<_<_ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 2, 3, 1, 5, 2, 4, 1, 5, 3, 3, 5, 4, 2, 1, 1, 3, 5, 4, 2, 5, 1, 2, 3, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "704",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _<_ _\n****^\n_>_<_ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n**v**\n_ _ _<_ _\n**v^*\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 5, 1, 2, 4, 2, 1, 4, 3, 5, 4, 3, 5, 1, 2, 5, 2, 3, 4, 1, 1, 4, 2, 5, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "705",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_<_ _ _ _\n*^^**\n_ _<_>_ _\n*vv*v\n_<_ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 3, 4, 5, 1, 2, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1, 5, 1, 2, 3, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "706",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _<_\nv*v**\n_ _ _>_ _\n**v**\n_<_ _ _ _\nv****\n_ _ _ _ _\nv****\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[5, 1, 3, 2, 4, 4, 5, 2, 1, 3, 3, 4, 1, 5, 2, 2, 3, 5, 4, 1, 1, 2, 4, 3, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "707",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _>_ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n^****\n_>_ _>_ _\n*^***\n_ _ _>_ _\n***v*\n_>_ _ _>_",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 2, 1, 3, 2, 3, 1, 5, 4, 3, 1, 5, 4, 2, 1, 2, 4, 3, 5, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "708",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\nv****\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^**\n_<_>_<_ _\n**^^*\n_ _ _ _ _\n***v^\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 2, 5, 1, 3, 1, 4, 2, 3, 5, 2, 5, 3, 4, 1, 3, 1, 4, 5, 2, 5, 3, 1, 2, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "709",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v*^*\n_ _ _ _ _\n**v**\n_ _<_<_>_\n*****\n_<_ _>_ _\n*****\n_<_ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 5, 4, 1, 2, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 4, 1, 2, 5, 3, 1, 2, 5, 3, 4, 2, 3, 1, 4, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "710",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _>_ _ _\n***^*\n_ _ _>_ _\n***v*\n_>_ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n*^***\n_ _<_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[1, 5, 4, 2, 3, 2, 3, 5, 4, 1, 5, 4, 1, 3, 2, 3, 1, 2, 5, 4, 4, 2, 3, 1, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "711",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n****v\n_ _>_ _<_\n**^^v\n_ _<_ _ _\n^****\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 5, 4, 2, 3, 2, 4, 1, 5, 2, 5, 1, 3, 4, 4, 1, 2, 5, 3, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "712",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n^*v**\n_<_ _ _ _\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n****v\n_ _ _ _>_\nv****\n_>_ _<_ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 4, 2, 1, 5, 4, 5, 1, 3, 2, 1, 3, 5, 2, 4, 5, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 1, 4, 5, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "713",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*^***\n_>_>_ _ _\n**^**\n_ _ _ _ _\n*^**v\n_ _>_ _ _\nv****\n_>_ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[5, 2, 4, 3, 1, 4, 3, 1, 5, 2, 1, 4, 3, 2, 5, 3, 5, 2, 1, 4, 2, 1, 5, 4, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "714",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*^**v\n_ _>_<_>_\n^vv**\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n^**v*\n_ _ _ _>_",
        "answer": "[[5, 2, 1, 4, 3, 1, 4, 3, 5, 2, 4, 3, 2, 1, 5, 2, 1, 5, 3, 4, 3, 5, 4, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "715",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _<_ _\n*v*v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n**v*v\n_ _ _ _>_\n^****\n_ _ _<_ _",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 5, 1, 2, 3, 4, 2, 4, 5, 1, 3, 3, 5, 4, 2, 1, 4, 3, 1, 5, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "716",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^**\n_ _<_<_ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n^*v*v\n_>_ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 1, 3, 2, 5, 2, 3, 4, 1, 3, 4, 2, 1, 5, 1, 3, 5, 2, 4, 2, 1, 4, 5, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "717",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_>_<_ _ _\n*v***\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^**\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _<_>_\n**v^*\n_>_>_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 4, 1, 5, 2, 1, 3, 5, 4, 1, 4, 5, 2, 3, 4, 5, 2, 3, 1, 5, 3, 1, 4, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "718",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _<_>_ _\nv****\n_ _ _ _ _\nv*v**\n_ _ _ _>_\n*****\n_<_ _ _<_\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 5, 1, 4, 2, 1, 4, 3, 5, 1, 4, 3, 5, 2, 4, 5, 1, 2, 3, 5, 3, 2, 4, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "719",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v***\n_ _<_ _>_\n**^^*\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v*^*\n_ _ _ _ _\n****v\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[2, 4, 3, 1, 5, 5, 3, 4, 2, 1, 1, 2, 5, 3, 4, 4, 1, 2, 5, 3, 3, 5, 1, 4, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "720",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v***\n_<_ _ _>_\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^*v\n_ _ _ _<_\nv****\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 3, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 2, 1, 2, 3, 1, 4, 5, 5, 1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 4, 5, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "721",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^*v\n_ _ _>_ _\n**vv*\n_ _ _ _<_\n*^*v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n^****\n_ _>_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 3, 5, 4, 5, 1, 4, 3, 2, 4, 3, 1, 2, 5, 2, 4, 5, 1, 3, 3, 5, 2, 4, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "722",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_<_<_ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _<_ _\n****^\n_<_ _ _>_",
        "answer": "[[5, 4, 2, 1, 3, 3, 1, 5, 2, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1, 4, 5, 1, 3, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "723",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_<_ _ _ _\n*^*v*\n_>_ _ _ _\n^****\n_ _<_<_>_\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _>_>_>_",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 3, 5, 4, 4, 3, 1, 2, 5, 5, 1, 2, 4, 3, 3, 4, 5, 1, 2, 2, 5, 4, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "724",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _<_<_\n*^***\n_ _ _ _<_\n*^^v*\n_ _ _ _<_\n^****\n_ _ _>_ _\n*^*^*\n_ _>_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[5, 2, 1, 3, 4, 1, 3, 2, 4, 5, 3, 5, 4, 1, 2, 4, 1, 5, 2, 3, 2, 4, 3, 5, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "725",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_>_ _ _ _\nv*v**\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^**\n_ _ _<_ _\n*****\n_>_<_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[5, 4, 1, 2, 3, 2, 1, 3, 4, 5, 1, 5, 2, 3, 4, 3, 2, 4, 5, 1, 4, 3, 5, 1, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "726",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _>_\n**v^*\n_ _ _ _>_\n^**^*\n_ _ _ _ _\nv**^*\n_ _<_<_ _\n**^*^\n_ _>_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 3, 5, 2, 1, 1, 5, 4, 3, 2, 5, 2, 1, 4, 3, 3, 1, 2, 5, 4, 2, 4, 3, 1, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "727",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_<_ _>_ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _>_\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^v*\n_ _>_ _ _\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 4, 5, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 5, 4, 5, 1, 2, 4, 3, 2, 5, 4, 3, 1, 4, 3, 1, 2, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "728",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _<_ _ _\n***vv\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^**\n_ _ _ _<_\n*****\n_<_ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[1, 4, 5, 3, 2, 5, 3, 4, 2, 1, 4, 2, 1, 5, 3, 2, 1, 3, 4, 5, 3, 5, 2, 1, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "729",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _>_ _\n*****\n_<_ _ _ _\n***^*\n_ _ _>_>_\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _>_",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 5, 4, 3, 3, 4, 2, 1, 5, 5, 1, 4, 3, 2, 2, 3, 1, 5, 4, 4, 5, 3, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "730",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v*v*\n_ _ _ _ _\nv***v\n_<_ _ _ _\n***vv\n_ _<_ _ _\nv**^*\n_>_ _ _>_",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 2, 4, 5, 5, 2, 4, 1, 3, 4, 5, 1, 3, 2, 3, 4, 5, 2, 1, 2, 1, 3, 5, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "731",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n****^\n_ _ _ _ _\n****^\n_ _ _>_ _\n*****\n_>_ _ _ _\n****^\n_ _<_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[2, 4, 3, 5, 1, 3, 5, 4, 1, 2, 1, 2, 5, 4, 3, 5, 3, 1, 2, 4, 4, 1, 2, 3, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "732",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n**vv*\n_<_<_ _ _\nv**^*\n_<_ _>_ _\n*****\n_>_ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 2, 1, 5, 3, 3, 1, 5, 4, 2, 2, 3, 4, 1, 5, 1, 5, 3, 2, 4, 5, 4, 2, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "733",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v^**\n_ _ _>_ _\n*****\n_ _<_ _>_\n****^\n_<_ _>_ _\n*****\n_ _ _>_ _",
        "answer": "[[2, 4, 1, 5, 3, 4, 1, 3, 2, 5, 5, 2, 4, 3, 1, 1, 3, 5, 4, 2, 3, 5, 2, 1, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "734",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _<_ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n**v**\n_ _<_ _ _\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^^*\n_>_ _<_ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 5, 1, 2, 4, 2, 4, 5, 1, 3, 1, 3, 4, 5, 2, 4, 1, 2, 3, 5, 5, 2, 3, 4, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "735",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _>_ _\n^****\n_ _ _ _>_\n*^**^\n_ _>_ _<_\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v*^*\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 3, 2, 1, 5, 5, 2, 1, 4, 3, 1, 5, 3, 2, 4, 2, 4, 5, 3, 1, 3, 1, 4, 5, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "736",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n***^*\n_<_ _>_ _\n**^**\n_>_ _ _ _\n**v*v\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 5, 2, 1, 4, 1, 4, 3, 2, 5, 2, 1, 4, 5, 3, 5, 3, 1, 4, 2, 4, 2, 5, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "737",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _<_\n***v*\n_<_ _ _ _\n***^*\n_ _ _ _ _\n**v^*\n_ _ _ _>_\nv****\n_ _>_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[5, 1, 2, 3, 4, 4, 5, 1, 2, 3, 1, 3, 5, 4, 2, 3, 2, 4, 5, 1, 2, 4, 3, 1, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "738",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _>_ _ _\n**v*^\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _<_\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _<_ _",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 2, 5, 4, 4, 2, 1, 3, 5, 5, 1, 4, 2, 3, 3, 4, 5, 1, 2, 2, 5, 3, 4, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "739",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n***^*\n_ _ _<_ _\n****v\n_ _ _<_ _\n^*v**\n_>_ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _>_",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 5, 2, 4, 1, 2, 4, 5, 3, 2, 5, 3, 4, 1, 4, 3, 2, 1, 5, 5, 4, 1, 3, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "740",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\nv**^^\n_ _ _ _<_\n^v***\n_ _ _>_<_\n*^***\n_ _<_ _ _\n*****\n_>_>_ _<_",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 1, 2, 3, 1, 3, 2, 4, 5, 2, 1, 5, 3, 4, 3, 2, 4, 5, 1, 5, 4, 3, 1, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "741",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _<_ _>_\n**^^*\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _>_\nv***v\n_<_ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[2, 3, 4, 1, 5, 5, 1, 2, 4, 3, 1, 2, 3, 5, 4, 4, 5, 1, 3, 2, 3, 4, 5, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "742",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _<_\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v***\n_ _ _ _ _\n****v\n_<_ _ _ _\n***^*\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[5, 1, 4, 2, 3, 3, 5, 1, 4, 2, 1, 4, 2, 3, 5, 2, 3, 5, 1, 4, 4, 2, 3, 5, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "743",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_<_<_<_ _\n*****\n_<_ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v^*^\n_ _ _<_ _\n*****\n_ _<_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[2, 3, 4, 5, 1, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 4, 5, 1, 2, 3, 5, 1, 2, 3, 4, 3, 4, 5, 1, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "744",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _<_ _\n***vv\n_>_ _ _>_\n**^**\n_ _>_ _ _\n**v**\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 5, 4, 3, 4, 2, 1, 3, 5, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 3, 5, 4, 1, 2, 1, 3, 2, 5, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "745",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\nv*v**\n_ _ _<_ _\n*v***\n_<_<_ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _>_ _\n**v*^\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 1, 5, 3, 2, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 5, 4, 2, 1, 3, 3, 5, 1, 2, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "746",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _>_<_\n*****\n_<_ _<_ _\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_>_<_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 4, 3, 5, 1, 2, 3, 5, 4, 3, 5, 1, 4, 2, 5, 4, 2, 1, 3, 4, 3, 5, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "747",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_>_ _ _ _\n**v**\n_ _ _<_ _\n*v^^^\n_ _ _ _ _\n**vv*\n_ _ _ _ _\n***v*\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 4, 5, 1, 1, 5, 2, 3, 4, 2, 1, 3, 4, 5, 5, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4, 3, 5, 1, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "748",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _<_ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^*^\n_ _ _ _ _\n**^v*\n_ _ _ _>_",
        "answer": "[[5, 3, 1, 2, 4, 3, 1, 2, 4, 5, 4, 5, 3, 1, 2, 1, 2, 4, 5, 3, 2, 4, 5, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "749",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_<_ _<_>_\nv****\n_ _ _ _ _\nv***^\n_ _ _>_ _\n*****\n_<_ _>_ _\n***^*\n_>_ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 4, 1, 5, 2, 2, 3, 5, 1, 4, 1, 2, 4, 3, 5, 4, 5, 3, 2, 1, 5, 1, 2, 4, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "750",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n****v\n_ _ _ _ _\n*v***\n_ _ _>_ _\n*v^*^\n_>_ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _<_ _ _",
        "answer": "[[3, 5, 1, 4, 2, 4, 3, 2, 5, 1, 5, 2, 3, 1, 4, 2, 1, 4, 3, 5, 1, 4, 5, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "751",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _>_<_ _\n*****\n_ _<_>_ _\n**v*v\n_ _ _<_ _\n*vv**\n_ _<_ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 1, 3, 2, 2, 3, 4, 1, 5, 1, 2, 3, 5, 4, 5, 1, 2, 4, 3, 3, 4, 5, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },
    {
        "idx": "752",
        "question": "\nFutoshiki Puzzle Explanation:\n\nWhat is Futoshiki?\n- Futoshiki (also known as \"Unequal\") is a logic puzzle played on a square grid (e.g., 5x5).\n- The goal is to fill each cell with a number from 1 to the size of the grid (e.g., 1-5 for a 5x5 grid).\n- Each number must appear exactly once in each row and column (like a Latin square).\n\nRules:\n- Each row and column must contain all numbers from 1 to the grid size, with no repetitions.\n- The inequality signs between cells must be respected:\n  - '>' means the left cell must be greater than the right cell\n  - '<' means the left cell must be less than the right cell\n  - '^' means the cell above must be greater than the cell below\n  - 'v' means the cell above must be less than the cell below\n  - '*' represents no constraint between cells\nAnswer the following puzzle:\n_ _ _ _ _\n*****\n_ _ _ _ _\n*^v**\n_ _ _ _ _\nv**v*\n_ _>_ _ _\n^v*vv\n_ _ _<_<_",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 4, 5, 2, 4, 2, 5, 1, 3, 2, 5, 3, 4, 1, 1, 4, 2, 3, 5, 5, 3, 1, 2, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "17"
    },

    {
        "idx": "91",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5+ B:2 C:7+ D:2-\nAAB\nACD\nCCD",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "165",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6* B:2 C:7+ D:3+\nAAB\nACC\nDDC",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 2, 3, 1, 1, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "133",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6* B:4* C:3 D:3/\nAAA\nBBC\nBDD",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "153",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:2- B:4* C:2- D:1-\nABB\nABC\nDDC",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "21",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3+ B:6* C:6* D:3*\nABB\nACC\nDDC",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 1, 3, 1, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "146",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1- B:3* C:18* D:3+\nABB\nACD\nCCD",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 3, 1, 3, 2, 3, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "32",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6+ B:6* C:3 D:4+\nABB\nACD\nADD",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 1, 3, 1, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "117",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:7+ B:3 C:6+ D:2\nAAB\nAAC\nDCC",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 3, 3, 1, 2, 2, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "111",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:2* B:5+ C:1 D:3* E:3 F:2\nABB\nACD\nEFD",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 2, 2, 1, 3, 3, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "57",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3+ B:6+ C:18* D:1\nAAB\nCDB\nCCB",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 3, 3, 1, 2, 2, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "20",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6* B:1- C:3 D:3 E:2\nABB\nAAC\nADE",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 1, 2, 1, 3, 1, 3, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "94",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1 B:1- C:7+ D:3*\nABB\nCCD\nCDD",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 2, 3, 2, 1, 2, 1, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "127",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6* B:2 C:7+ D:2/\nAAB\nACC\nDDC",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 2, 3, 1, 1, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "109",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6+ B:9* C:2 D:3+\nABC\nABB\nADD",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 2, 2, 1, 3, 3, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "52",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5+ B:6+ C:3/ D:2*\nABB\nABC\nDDC",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 2, 3, 1, 1, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "138",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5+ B:3* C:1- D:5+\nAAB\nCBB\nCDD",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 1, 2, 1, 3, 1, 3, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "35",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:8+ B:1 C:1- D:3 E:1\nABC\nADC\nAAE",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 3, 1, 3, 2, 3, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "70",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:2- B:1 C:6* D:7+\nABC\nADC\nDDC",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "58",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3 B:8+ C:6+ D:1\nABC\nBBC\nBDC",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 1, 1, 3, 2, 2, 1, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "53",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1- B:2* C:3/ D:2 E:3\nAAB\nCBB\nCDE",
        "answer": "[[2, 3, 1, 3, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "254",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1 B:2 C:10+ D:7+ E:10+ F:12* G:1-\nABCC\nDDDC\nEFFG\nEEEG",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 3, 4, 4, 1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 4, 1, 3, 4, 1, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "309",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:4 B:2 C:10+ D:3* E:48* F:6* G:2\nABCC\nDDCC\nDEEF\nGEEF",
        "answer": "[[4, 2, 3, 1, 3, 1, 2, 4, 1, 3, 4, 2, 2, 4, 1, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "247",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1 B:72* C:2 D:7+ E:1 F:4 G:1- H:12*\nABBB\nCDBE\nFDDG\nHHHG",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 2, 4, 2, 4, 3, 1, 4, 2, 1, 3, 3, 1, 4, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "285",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3* B:24* C:4 D:2 E:11+ F:3 G:6*\nAABC\nABBD\nEEEF\nEGGG",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 4, 1, 3, 4, 2, 2, 4, 1, 3, 4, 2, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "173",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:16* B:8+ C:24* D:2 E:3+ F:4/ G:3\nAABB\nCAAB\nCDEF\nCGEF",
        "answer": "[[1, 4, 3, 2, 2, 1, 4, 3, 3, 2, 1, 4, 4, 3, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "269",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3 B:2* C:24* D:24* E:8* F:1 G:7+\nABBC\nDDDC\nEECC\nEFGG",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 1, 4, 4, 3, 2, 1, 1, 4, 3, 2, 2, 1, 4, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "265",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:12* B:2 C:3* D:11+ E:18* F:1- G:4\nAAAB\nCDDD\nCDEE\nFFEG",
        "answer": "[[4, 3, 1, 2, 3, 2, 4, 1, 1, 4, 2, 3, 2, 1, 3, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "284",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:36* B:8* C:6* D:3+ E:12* F:1 G:2-\nAAAB\nCDAB\nCDEE\nFGGE",
        "answer": "[[4, 3, 1, 2, 2, 1, 3, 4, 3, 2, 4, 1, 1, 4, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "222",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6+ B:4* C:4 D:7+ E:3 F:7+ G:12*\nAABB\nCADD\nEFGD\nFFGG",
        "answer": "[[2, 3, 4, 1, 4, 1, 2, 3, 3, 4, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "185",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6* B:8* C:12* D:6+ E:8* F:3 G:4\nABBB\nACCD\nEEDD\nEEFG",
        "answer": "[[3, 4, 1, 2, 2, 3, 4, 1, 4, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "212",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1 B:8* C:6* D:9+ E:6* F:48* G:1\nABBC\nDDBC\nDEFF\nEEFG",
        "answer": "[[1, 4, 2, 3, 4, 3, 1, 2, 2, 1, 3, 4, 3, 2, 4, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "198",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6+ B:12* C:12* D:12* E:5+ F:4 G:1\nABBB\nACDD\nCCDD\nEEFG",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 3, 4, 4, 3, 1, 2, 1, 4, 2, 3, 3, 2, 4, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "243",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:8+ B:1- C:8* D:3 E:7+ F:1- G:2*\nABCD\nABCC\nAEFG\nEEFG",
        "answer": "[[4, 2, 1, 3, 1, 3, 2, 4, 3, 1, 4, 2, 2, 4, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "301",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:2 B:2/ C:12* D:8* E:12* F:2- G:9+\nABCD\nEBCD\nEFFD\nEGGG",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 3, 4, 3, 2, 4, 1, 4, 3, 1, 2, 1, 4, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "260",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:10+ B:36* C:4/ D:2 E:2 F:1 G:2/ H:3\nAAAA\nBBCD\nBECF\nBGGH",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 3, 4, 4, 3, 1, 2, 3, 2, 4, 1, 1, 4, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "290",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:9+ B:12* C:8* D:1 E:8+ F:1- G:6*\nAAAB\nCDBB\nCEFF\nEEGG",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 4, 1, 2, 1, 3, 4, 4, 3, 1, 2, 1, 4, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "306",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:4 B:12* C:6* D:1 E:1- F:2 G:5+ H:3 I:4 J:2 K:1\nABBC\nDEBC\nFEGG\nHIJK",
        "answer": "[[4, 1, 3, 2, 1, 2, 4, 3, 2, 3, 1, 4, 3, 4, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "180",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:12* B:2/ C:6* D:9+ E:2* F:3 G:16*\nABCC\nABCD\nEFGD\nEGGD",
        "answer": "[[4, 2, 3, 1, 3, 1, 2, 4, 1, 3, 4, 2, 2, 4, 1, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "191",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:8+ B:4/ C:6* D:24* E:12* F:4/ G:1\nABBC\nAADC\nEEDF\nGEDF",
        "answer": "[[3, 4, 1, 2, 4, 1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 4, 1, 1, 2, 3, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "235",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:2 B:12* C:24* D:12* E:5+ F:3 G:5+\nABBB\nCCDD\nCEFG\nCEGG",
        "answer": "[[2, 3, 1, 4, 1, 2, 4, 3, 4, 1, 3, 2, 3, 4, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "469",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:20* B:96* C:1 D:15* E:2 F:3- G:15* H:2 I:20* J:10+ K:4+\nABBBC\nABDDE\nAFGGG\nHFIJJ\nKKIJJ",
        "answer": "[[5, 3, 2, 4, 1, 1, 4, 3, 5, 2, 4, 2, 1, 3, 5, 2, 5, 4, 1, 3, 3, 1, 5, 2, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "494",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:4 B:5* C:10+ D:9* E:6+ F:4 G:2 H:60* I:7+ J:15* K:2/\nABCCC\nDBBEE\nDDFGH\nIIJJH\nKKJHH",
        "answer": "[[4, 1, 2, 5, 3, 3, 5, 1, 4, 2, 1, 3, 4, 2, 5, 5, 2, 3, 1, 4, 2, 4, 5, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "432",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:2 B:3 C:4- D:13+ E:1 F:2 G:72* H:13+ I:14+ J:8+ K:1\nABCDD\nEFCDG\nHHGGG\nHIIJK\nHIIJJ",
        "answer": "[[2, 3, 1, 5, 4, 1, 2, 5, 4, 3, 5, 1, 4, 3, 2, 4, 5, 3, 2, 1, 3, 4, 2, 1, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "429",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:24* B:7+ C:8+ D:7+ E:5+ F:20* G:9+ H:6+ I:6* J:3- K:5\nAAABB\nCDDBE\nCFFGE\nCHHGG\nIIJJK",
        "answer": "[[4, 3, 2, 5, 1, 5, 4, 3, 1, 2, 1, 5, 4, 2, 3, 2, 1, 5, 3, 4, 3, 2, 1, 4, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "444",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3- B:7+ C:60* D:20* E:6* F:4 G:30* H:3 I:15* J:7+ K:1\nABCDD\nABCED\nFBCEG\nHICJG\nKIJJG",
        "answer": "[[2, 4, 3, 5, 1, 5, 2, 1, 3, 4, 4, 1, 5, 2, 3, 3, 5, 4, 1, 2, 1, 3, 2, 4, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "438",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:200* B:3/ C:1 D:3 E:2 F:2- G:2- H:13+ I:16* J:150* K:2\nAAABC\nADEBF\nGGHHF\nIIHJJ\nIKHJJ",
        "answer": "[[2, 5, 4, 3, 1, 5, 3, 2, 1, 4, 3, 1, 5, 4, 2, 1, 4, 3, 2, 5, 4, 2, 1, 5, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "425",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:40* B:20* C:3 D:24* E:8* F:15* G:12* H:5 I:1 J:30* K:2\nAAABC\nDDBBE\nDFGHE\nIFGJE\nKFGJJ",
        "answer": "[[5, 4, 2, 1, 3, 3, 2, 5, 4, 1, 4, 3, 1, 5, 2, 1, 5, 3, 2, 4, 2, 1, 4, 3, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "393",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3* B:4/ C:9+ D:20* E:5+ F:40* G:3 H:6+ I:8+ J:4 K:45*\nABCCD\nABEDD\nFGEHH\nFIJKH\nFIIKK",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 5, 4, 2, 1, 4, 3, 2, 5, 5, 3, 2, 1, 4, 2, 5, 4, 3, 1, 4, 2, 1, 5, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "439",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6+ B:8* C:2- D:2 E:15* F:15* G:4/ H:3- I:60* J:24* K:1\nABCCD\nABBEE\nFFBGE\nHHIGJ\nKIIJJ",
        "answer": "[[4, 1, 3, 5, 2, 2, 4, 1, 3, 5, 3, 5, 2, 4, 1, 5, 2, 4, 1, 3, 1, 3, 5, 2, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "493",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1 B:3 C:60* D:3- E:20* F:40* G:24* H:10+ I:5+ J:3+ K:4\nABCCD\nEFCGD\nEFGGH\nIFHHH\nIFJJK",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 5, 4, 2, 4, 1, 3, 2, 5, 5, 2, 4, 3, 1, 2, 4, 1, 5, 3, 3, 5, 2, 1, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "464",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:7+ B:1 C:100* D:6* E:3* F:1- G:8+ H:30* I:4 J:3- K:12*\nAABCD\nEACCD\nEFFGG\nHHHGI\nJJKKK",
        "answer": "[[4, 2, 1, 5, 3, 3, 1, 5, 4, 2, 1, 4, 3, 2, 5, 5, 3, 2, 1, 4, 2, 5, 4, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "476",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3- B:3/ C:9+ D:20* E:6+ F:20* G:12* H:60* I:3- J:1 K:2\nABCCC\nABDDE\nFFFEE\nGGHHI\nJKHHI",
        "answer": "[[5, 1, 2, 3, 4, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1, 4, 5, 1, 2, 3, 3, 4, 5, 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "388",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:20* B:5 C:3 D:3+ E:20* F:5+ G:2- H:10+ I:4/ J:18* K:10+\nABCDD\nAEEFF\nAGEHI\nJGHHI\nJJKKK",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 3, 1, 2, 5, 1, 4, 2, 3, 1, 2, 5, 3, 4, 3, 4, 2, 5, 1, 2, 3, 1, 4, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "347",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:7+ B:2 C:3/ D:4 E:12+ F:30* G:12* H:10+ I:7+ J:2 K:20*\nABCCD\nAEEEF\nGHFFF\nGHIIJ\nHHIKK",
        "answer": "[[5, 2, 1, 3, 4, 2, 4, 3, 5, 1, 4, 1, 5, 2, 3, 3, 5, 4, 1, 2, 1, 3, 2, 4, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "488",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:7+ B:60* C:2 D:12+ E:9+ F:8+ G:5 H:4 I:4/ J:15* K:1-\nABBBC\nAADDD\nEFFDG\nEFFHI\nJJKKI",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 4, 5, 2, 2, 4, 5, 1, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 5, 5, 2, 3, 4, 1, 3, 5, 1, 2, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "337",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5+ B:3* C:10+ D:4 E:7+ F:3- G:32* H:2- I:15* J:9+ K:8*\nABCCD\nABCEE\nFFGHH\nIIGGJ\nKKKJJ",
        "answer": "[[1, 3, 5, 2, 4, 4, 1, 3, 5, 2, 5, 2, 4, 1, 3, 3, 5, 2, 4, 1, 2, 4, 1, 3, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "365",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:4* B:3* C:10+ D:11+ E:12+ F:8* G:2- H:9+ I:4/ J:3/ K:5\nABCDD\nABCCD\nEEFGG\nHEFII\nHHJJK",
        "answer": "[[4, 1, 3, 5, 2, 1, 3, 5, 2, 4, 5, 2, 4, 1, 3, 3, 5, 2, 4, 1, 2, 4, 1, 3, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "435",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:9+ B:20* C:24* D:6+ E:9+ F:12+ G:1 H:4* I:7+ J:5 K:2\nAABCC\nDBBCE\nDBFEE\nDGFFH\nIIJKH",
        "answer": "[[5, 4, 1, 3, 2, 1, 5, 2, 4, 3, 3, 2, 4, 1, 5, 2, 1, 3, 5, 4, 4, 3, 5, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "417",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5/ B:2/ C:15* D:4 E:6+ F:30* G:24* H:9+ I:5/ J:6* K:1-\nABCCD\nABEEF\nGGGGF\nHHIJF\nKKIJJ",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 3, 5, 4, 5, 1, 2, 4, 3, 2, 3, 4, 1, 5, 4, 5, 1, 3, 2, 3, 4, 5, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "424",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:8+ B:1 C:4 D:5 E:40* F:150* G:4/ H:5+ I:12* J:8+ K:5*\nAABCD\nAEFFG\nHEFFG\nHEIJJ\nKKIJJ",
        "answer": "[[2, 3, 1, 4, 5, 3, 4, 2, 5, 1, 1, 2, 5, 3, 4, 4, 5, 3, 1, 2, 5, 1, 4, 2, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "533",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:9+ B:1- C:30* D:4+ E:60* F:9+ G:12* H:6+ I:7+ J:6* K:20* L:12+ M:2/ N:2 O:13+ P:4-\nAAABBC\nDDEFFC\nGEEHIJ\nGKKHIJ\nLLLHMM\nNOOOPP",
        "answer": "[[6, 2, 1, 4, 3, 5, 1, 3, 2, 5, 4, 6, 4, 6, 5, 2, 1, 3, 3, 5, 4, 1, 6, 2, 5, 1, 6, 3, 2, 4, 2, 4, 3, 6, 5, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "503",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1- B:6* C:100* D:2- E:4+ F:8+ G:30* H:24* I:6* J:13+ K:1- L:1- M:14+ N:8+ O:2 P:3\nAABBCC\nDEEFFC\nDGGGHH\nIJJKLH\nIMJKLN\nMMOPNN",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 6, 1, 5, 4, 4, 3, 1, 2, 6, 5, 2, 1, 5, 6, 4, 3, 1, 6, 4, 5, 3, 2, 6, 5, 3, 4, 2, 1, 5, 4, 2, 3, 1, 6]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "660",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5 B:4* C:9+ D:3 E:15+ F:30* G:6* H:18* I:24* J:1- K:6+ L:9+ M:11+ N:1- O:7+ P:2\nABBCDE\nFFCCEE\nGHIIEJ\nGHHIKJ\nGLMNKO\nLLMNPO",
        "answer": "[[5, 4, 1, 6, 3, 2, 6, 5, 2, 1, 4, 3, 2, 1, 4, 3, 6, 5, 1, 6, 3, 2, 5, 4, 3, 2, 5, 4, 1, 6, 4, 3, 6, 5, 2, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "636",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:2 B:5* C:9+ D:6 E:12+ F:72* G:10+ H:15+ I:3/ J:24* K:48* L:8+ M:2/ N:3* O:5 P:2\nABCCDE\nFBCGGE\nFFFGHE\nIJKHHL\nIJKMNL\nOPKMNN",
        "answer": "[[2, 5, 3, 1, 6, 4, 4, 1, 5, 3, 2, 6, 6, 3, 1, 5, 4, 2, 1, 4, 2, 6, 5, 3, 3, 6, 4, 2, 1, 5, 5, 2, 6, 4, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "661",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:60* B:24* C:1- D:3* E:6* F:24* G:72* H:6+ I:13+ J:5 K:2 L:2- M:6+ N:24* O:15* P:3/\nAABCCD\nAABEED\nFFFGHH\nIIJGGK\nILLMNN\nIOOMPP",
        "answer": "[[1, 2, 6, 4, 5, 3, 5, 6, 4, 2, 3, 1, 3, 4, 2, 6, 1, 5, 6, 1, 5, 3, 4, 2, 2, 3, 1, 5, 6, 4, 4, 5, 3, 1, 2, 6]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "639",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3 B:20* C:2 D:15+ E:12+ F:3 G:1- H:2* I:10+ J:30* K:2/ L:20* M:540* N:6/ O:4 P:6*\nABCDDD\nEBBFGH\nEEIIGH\nJJKKLM\nJNNLLM\nOPPPMM",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 6, 5, 4, 6, 4, 5, 3, 2, 1, 1, 5, 6, 4, 3, 2, 5, 3, 4, 2, 1, 6, 2, 6, 1, 5, 4, 3, 4, 2, 3, 1, 6, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "509",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:10+ B:17+ C:5 D:10* E:12* F:1- G:10+ H:6+ I:1 J:40* K:6 L:12+ M:3 N:7+ O:14+ P:4\nAABBBC\nDABEEE\nDFFGGH\nIJJJKH\nLLMNOH\nPLNNOO",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 6, 4, 2, 5, 2, 6, 5, 3, 1, 4, 5, 3, 2, 6, 4, 1, 1, 5, 4, 2, 6, 3, 6, 4, 3, 1, 5, 2, 4, 2, 1, 5, 3, 6]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "556",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:48* B:30* C:12* D:6/ E:20* F:5+ G:6/ H:15* I:12* J:10+ K:4 L:14+ M:6+ N:5 O:6 P:4*\nABBCCD\nAAECCD\nFFEGGH\nIIJJKH\nIIJLLM\nNOPPLM",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 6, 3, 2, 1, 3, 4, 5, 2, 1, 6, 2, 3, 4, 1, 6, 5, 6, 1, 2, 5, 4, 3, 1, 2, 3, 6, 5, 4, 5, 6, 1, 4, 3, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "626",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:12+ B:13+ C:9+ D:24* E:1 F:6* G:1- H:13+ I:15* J:2 K:1 L:9+ M:12+ N:30* O:3+ P:6\nAABBCD\nAAEBCD\nFGHHHD\nFGIIJK\nLMMINN\nLMMOOP",
        "answer": "[[3, 1, 2, 6, 5, 4, 2, 6, 1, 5, 4, 3, 1, 5, 6, 4, 3, 2, 6, 4, 5, 3, 2, 1, 4, 2, 3, 1, 6, 5, 5, 3, 4, 2, 1, 6]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "555",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1- B:24* C:20* D:24* E:7+ F:6* G:3 H:30* I:120* J:12+ K:36* L:3+ M:1 N:9+ O:15* P:4\nAABBCC\nDDEBFF\nDGEHHH\nIJJKLL\nIIJKKM\nNNNOOP",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 1, 6, 4, 5, 1, 6, 5, 4, 2, 3, 4, 3, 2, 1, 5, 6, 6, 5, 4, 3, 1, 2, 5, 4, 3, 2, 6, 1, 2, 1, 6, 5, 3, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "501",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6 B:4- C:1- D:2/ E:7+ F:4- G:6 H:7+ I:9+ J:60* K:20* L:8* M:15* N:10+ O:12+ P:10+\nABCCDD\nEBFGHH\nEIFJJJ\nEIKKLM\nNNOLLM\nNOOPPP",
        "answer": "[[6, 5, 3, 4, 1, 2, 2, 1, 5, 6, 3, 4, 4, 3, 1, 2, 5, 6, 1, 6, 4, 5, 2, 3, 3, 2, 6, 1, 4, 5, 5, 4, 2, 3, 6, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "579",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:12* B:5+ C:1- D:20* E:10+ F:24* G:2* H:2- I:1- J:12+ K:1- L:15+ M:6+ N:5 O:4+ P:6\nABBCCD\nAEBFDD\nGEEFHH\nGIIJJK\nLLMMJK\nNLOOJP",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 1, 5, 6, 4, 4, 3, 2, 6, 1, 5, 2, 1, 6, 4, 5, 3, 1, 6, 5, 3, 4, 2, 6, 5, 4, 2, 3, 1, 5, 4, 3, 1, 2, 6]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "571",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:3 B:96* C:60* D:1 E:10+ F:7+ G:3+ H:5+ I:1- J:11+ K:72* L:18* M:75* N:4 O:1 P:8+\nABBCDE\nFBGCCE\nFHGIIE\nJHKKLL\nJMMKLN\nJOMKPP",
        "answer": "[[3, 6, 4, 2, 1, 5, 1, 4, 2, 6, 5, 3, 6, 3, 1, 5, 4, 2, 5, 2, 6, 4, 3, 1, 2, 5, 3, 1, 6, 4, 4, 1, 5, 3, 2, 6]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "570",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5* B:13+ C:8+ D:2 E:16+ F:4 G:4 H:8+ I:1 J:48* K:5 L:10+ M:120* N:1 O:2* P:60* Q:6\nAABBCD\nAEEBCF\nGEEHHI\nJJJKLL\nMMNOPL\nMMQOPP",
        "answer": "[[5, 1, 3, 4, 6, 2, 1, 3, 5, 6, 2, 4, 4, 6, 2, 3, 5, 1, 6, 2, 4, 5, 1, 3, 3, 5, 1, 2, 4, 6, 2, 4, 6, 1, 3, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "651",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6 B:16+ C:6* D:5 E:1 F:16+ G:24* H:12+ I:4 J:6/ K:1- L:60* M:30* N:1 O:12* P:2\nABBCCC\nDBBEFF\nGHHIFF\nGHHJJK\nGLMMMK\nNLLOOP",
        "answer": "[[6, 5, 4, 2, 3, 1, 5, 4, 3, 1, 2, 6, 2, 1, 6, 4, 5, 3, 4, 3, 2, 6, 1, 5, 3, 2, 1, 5, 6, 4, 1, 6, 5, 3, 4, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "523",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:90* B:120* C:7+ D:6* E:360* F:7+ G:18* H:2 I:7+ J:4 K:5 L:18* M:11+ N:1 O:4 P:5-\nAABCDD\nABBCEE\nAFGCEE\nHFGGIJ\nKFLMIN\nOLLMPP",
        "answer": "[[6, 5, 4, 1, 3, 2, 1, 6, 5, 2, 4, 3, 3, 2, 1, 4, 6, 5, 2, 1, 6, 3, 5, 4, 5, 4, 3, 6, 2, 1, 4, 3, 2, 5, 1, 6]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "566",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5 B:12* C:4* D:10+ E:6* F:30* G:4 H:24* I:3- J:24* K:2- L:9+ M:18* N:8+ O:7+ P:8+\nABBCCD\nEEFCGD\nHHFIID\nHHJJKK\nLLJMMN\nOOPPNN",
        "answer": "[[5, 6, 2, 4, 1, 3, 2, 3, 5, 1, 4, 6, 3, 4, 6, 2, 5, 1, 1, 2, 4, 6, 3, 5, 4, 5, 1, 3, 6, 2, 6, 1, 3, 5, 2, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "621",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:12* B:1- C:1 D:1- E:1- F:10+ G:72* H:24* I:2* J:6/ K:5- L:11+ M:3- N:11+ O:12* P:5\nAABCDE\nAFBGDE\nFFHGIJ\nKLHGIJ\nKLHMNN\nOOOMNP",
        "answer": "[[3, 2, 6, 1, 5, 4, 2, 1, 5, 6, 4, 3, 5, 4, 2, 3, 1, 6, 6, 5, 3, 4, 2, 1, 1, 6, 4, 5, 3, 2, 4, 3, 1, 2, 6, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "617",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1- B:1- C:1 D:2 E:6 F:100* G:3/ H:5+ I:10+ J:12* K:13+ L:9+ M:6+ N:30* O:10* P:13+\nABCDEF\nABGHFF\nIIGHHJ\nIKKLMJ\nNNKLMM\nOOOPPP",
        "answer": "[[4, 3, 1, 2, 6, 5, 3, 2, 6, 1, 5, 4, 5, 4, 2, 3, 1, 6, 1, 6, 4, 5, 3, 2, 6, 5, 3, 4, 2, 1, 2, 1, 5, 6, 4, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "635",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1- B:30* C:12* D:6* E:1- F:5- G:8* H:14+ I:11+ J:24* K:60* L:5 M:5+ N:2 O:6 P:5/\nABCCDE\nABDDDE\nFGGGHI\nFJKLHI\nMJKHHN\nMJKOPP",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 6, 2, 1, 3, 5, 6, 1, 3, 2, 4, 6, 1, 2, 4, 3, 5, 1, 2, 3, 5, 4, 6, 3, 4, 5, 1, 6, 2, 2, 3, 4, 6, 5, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "756",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:1- B:5- C:6 D:16+ E:4+ F:5- G:30* H:4- I:7 J:4+ K:12+ L:15+ M:1- N:2 O:1- P:18* Q:5/ R:12* S:24* T:13+ U:13+ V:2-\nAABCDEF\nGGBDDEF\nGHHIJKK\nLLMNJOK\nPLMQROS\nPTTQRUS\nPTVVUUS",
        "answer": "[[4, 5, 1, 6, 7, 3, 2, 2, 3, 6, 4, 5, 1, 7, 5, 6, 2, 7, 1, 4, 3, 7, 1, 4, 2, 3, 6, 5, 6, 7, 3, 1, 2, 5, 4, 3, 4, 7, 5, 6, 2, 1, 1, 2, 5, 3, 4, 7, 6]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "700",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:32* B:5 C:2- D:13+ E:42* F:35* G:72* H:6* I:7+ J:4- K:7+ L:7 M:3/ N:3/ O:18+ P:7+ Q:6 R:10+ S:18+ T:1 U:15+ V:1-\nAABCCDD\nEAFFGHI\nEJJGGHI\nKLMMNOI\nKPQRNOO\nPPRRSSO\nTUUUSVV",
        "answer": "[[4, 2, 5, 3, 1, 7, 6, 6, 4, 7, 5, 3, 2, 1, 7, 5, 1, 6, 4, 3, 2, 2, 7, 3, 1, 6, 5, 4, 5, 3, 6, 4, 2, 1, 7, 3, 1, 4, 2, 7, 6, 5, 1, 6, 2, 7, 5, 4, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "791",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:15+ B:1- C:8* D:10+ E:11+ F:3 G:2 H:60* I:1 J:16+ K:14+ L:28* M:14* N:5 O:11+ P:6+ Q:11+ R:7+ S:14* T:7+ U:24* V:15*\nABBCCDD\nAAEEEDF\nGHHIJJJ\nKHLLMNO\nKPPQMRO\nKPSQMRT\nUUSVVTT",
        "answer": "[[3, 5, 6, 2, 4, 7, 1, 5, 7, 1, 4, 6, 2, 3, 2, 4, 5, 1, 3, 6, 7, 1, 3, 4, 7, 2, 5, 6, 7, 2, 3, 6, 1, 4, 5, 6, 1, 2, 5, 7, 3, 4, 4, 6, 7, 3, 5, 1, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "811",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:4 B:36* C:10+ D:15+ E:11+ F:17+ G:2 H:42* I:7 J:1- K:9+ L:14+ M:1- N:1- O:21* P:4 Q:13+ R:4* S:11+ T:5 U:3 V:6\nABBCDDE\nBBCCFDE\nGHIJFFK\nLHMJNNK\nLHMOOPK\nLQQORSS\nTQUVRRS",
        "answer": "[[4, 3, 2, 5, 7, 1, 6, 3, 2, 1, 4, 6, 7, 5, 2, 1, 7, 3, 5, 6, 4, 1, 7, 6, 2, 4, 5, 3, 7, 6, 5, 1, 3, 4, 2, 6, 5, 4, 7, 2, 3, 1, 5, 4, 3, 6, 1, 2, 7]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "831",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:8+ B:10+ C:126* D:10+ E:8+ F:84* G:4* H:60* I:28* J:11+ K:126* L:6 M:60* N:4- O:3 P:1 Q:13+ R:4- S:28* T:3 U:2 V:4*\nABBCDDE\nAFGCDHE\nFFGCHHE\nIIJJJKL\nIMMNKKO\nPQMNRSS\nQQTURVV",
        "answer": "[[2, 3, 7, 6, 4, 5, 1, 6, 7, 4, 3, 1, 2, 5, 3, 4, 1, 7, 5, 6, 2, 7, 1, 5, 4, 2, 3, 6, 4, 5, 2, 1, 6, 7, 3, 1, 2, 6, 5, 3, 4, 7, 5, 6, 3, 2, 7, 1, 4]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "692",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:70* B:4 C:84* D:3 E:30* F:4/ G:6* H:60* I:126* J:11+ K:28* L:12* M:3/ N:5 O:9+ P:6* Q:9+ R:49* S:24* T:30* U:6 V:1\nAAABCCD\nEFFGHCC\nEIIGHJK\nLIMGHJK\nLLMNOOK\nPQRRSST\nPQRUVST",
        "answer": "[[7, 2, 5, 4, 6, 1, 3, 6, 1, 4, 3, 5, 7, 2, 5, 7, 3, 2, 4, 6, 1, 4, 6, 2, 1, 3, 5, 7, 1, 3, 6, 5, 7, 2, 4, 3, 5, 1, 7, 2, 4, 6, 2, 4, 7, 6, 1, 3, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "817",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:8+ B:84* C:8+ D:6* E:42* F:40* G:35* H:6 I:4 J:2- K:12+ L:9+ M:4 N:28* O:6 P:8+ Q:12+ R:56* S:6* T:48* U:5 V:4+\nAAABBBC\nDEEFGGC\nDEFFGHI\nDJKLLMN\nOJKPPNN\nQRRRPSS\nQTTTUVV",
        "answer": "[[4, 1, 3, 6, 2, 7, 5, 2, 6, 1, 4, 7, 5, 3, 3, 7, 2, 5, 1, 6, 4, 1, 5, 7, 3, 6, 4, 2, 6, 3, 5, 1, 4, 2, 7, 5, 2, 4, 7, 3, 1, 6, 7, 4, 6, 2, 5, 3, 1]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "819",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:28* B:10+ C:3- D:42* E:7+ F:24* G:19+ H:1- I:12+ J:11+ K:6* L:12+ M:4- N:4- O:7+ P:12* Q:7 R:5 S:1 T:11+ U:6 V:3\nAABCDEE\nABBCDDF\nGHHIIJF\nGKKKIJF\nGGLMMNN\nOOLPPPQ\nRSLTTUV",
        "answer": "[[4, 7, 1, 6, 3, 5, 2, 1, 4, 5, 3, 7, 2, 6, 3, 6, 7, 5, 2, 4, 1, 6, 2, 3, 1, 5, 7, 4, 7, 3, 4, 2, 6, 1, 5, 2, 5, 6, 4, 1, 3, 7, 5, 1, 2, 7, 4, 6, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "679",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:2 B:14+ C:1 D:16+ E:9+ F:2- G:10+ H:9+ I:60* J:2- K:5* L:12+ M:35* N:9+ O:9+ P:84* Q:14+ R:7 S:5* T:2 U:24* V:5\nABBBCDD\nEFFGGGD\nEHHIIIJ\nKLLMMNJ\nKKLOONP\nQRSSOTP\nQQSUUVP",
        "answer": "[[2, 5, 3, 6, 1, 7, 4, 3, 6, 4, 7, 2, 1, 5, 6, 2, 7, 3, 5, 4, 1, 1, 4, 2, 5, 7, 6, 3, 5, 1, 6, 2, 4, 3, 7, 4, 7, 5, 1, 3, 2, 6, 7, 3, 1, 4, 6, 5, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "788",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:6* B:2- C:24* D:168* E:5 F:1- G:8+ H:90* I:70* J:8+ K:9+ L:3/ M:13+ N:12* O:4 P:5 Q:2- R:10+ S:3* T:6 U:7 V:70*\nAAABBCC\nDDAEFFG\nDHIIJJG\nHHIKKKL\nHMNNOPL\nQMRSTUV\nQMRSSVV",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 3, 7, 5, 6, 4, 7, 6, 1, 5, 3, 4, 2, 4, 3, 5, 2, 7, 1, 6, 6, 5, 7, 4, 2, 3, 1, 1, 7, 2, 6, 4, 5, 3, 3, 2, 4, 1, 6, 7, 5, 5, 4, 6, 3, 1, 2, 7]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "749",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5 B:2- C:3 D:28* E:1 F:6 G:7 H:35* I:9+ J:19+ K:8* L:10+ M:15* N:20+ O:3- P:10* Q:7 R:12+ S:14* T:2- U:15* V:2/\nABCDDEF\nGBHIJJK\nLHHIIJK\nLMNNNJK\nLMNOPPQ\nRRSOPTU\nRSSVVTU",
        "answer": "[[5, 2, 3, 7, 4, 1, 6, 7, 4, 5, 2, 6, 3, 1, 3, 7, 1, 5, 2, 6, 4, 1, 5, 6, 3, 7, 4, 2, 6, 3, 4, 1, 5, 2, 7, 2, 6, 7, 4, 1, 5, 3, 4, 1, 2, 6, 3, 7, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "763",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:120* B:7 C:13+ D:2- E:6+ F:7+ G:5- H:12* I:1 J:18+ K:6* L:15+ M:1- N:11+ O:1- P:6- Q:10+ R:5/ S:10+ T:8* U:20* V:9+\nAABCCDD\nEAFFCGG\nEHHIJJJ\nEKKLMMN\nOPLLQQN\nOPRRQST\nUUVVSST",
        "answer": "[[5, 6, 7, 4, 2, 1, 3, 3, 4, 5, 2, 7, 6, 1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 6, 5, 7, 1, 2, 3, 7, 5, 4, 6, 7, 1, 2, 6, 4, 3, 5, 6, 7, 1, 5, 3, 2, 4, 4, 5, 6, 3, 1, 7, 2]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "823",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:70* B:4 C:108* D:4- E:5/ F:2 G:12* H:42* I:8+ J:30* K:5/ L:4* M:280* N:4+ O:24* P:18+ Q:42* R:9+ S:8+ T:5 U:6 V:3\nABCCDEE\nAAFCDGH\nIJKKLGH\nIJMMLLH\nINMMOPP\nQNRSOPP\nQRRSTUV",
        "answer": "[[2, 4, 6, 3, 7, 1, 5, 5, 7, 2, 6, 3, 4, 1, 4, 6, 1, 5, 2, 3, 7, 3, 5, 7, 4, 1, 2, 6, 1, 3, 5, 2, 6, 7, 4, 6, 1, 3, 7, 4, 5, 2, 7, 2, 4, 1, 5, 6, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "729",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:8+ B:4 C:2/ D:35* E:18* F:10* G:147* H:4 I:2 J:4/ K:6 L:7/ M:30* N:6 O:12+ P:16+ Q:9+ R:60* S:56* T:11+ U:1- V:1\nAABCCDD\nEAFGGHI\nEFFGJJK\nLLMMMNO\nPPQQRRO\nPPSQRTO\nUUSSVTT",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 4, 6, 3, 7, 5, 6, 5, 1, 3, 7, 4, 2, 3, 2, 5, 7, 4, 1, 6, 1, 7, 3, 5, 2, 6, 4, 4, 3, 6, 1, 5, 2, 7, 5, 4, 7, 2, 6, 3, 1, 7, 6, 2, 4, 1, 5, 3]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "759",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:5 B:4- C:10+ D:24* E:9+ F:4 G:3 H:60* I:56* J:4/ K:2- L:9+ M:24* N:210* O:4+ P:2- Q:7/ R:5- S:120* T:16* U:10+ V:5\nABBCDEF\nGHCCDEE\nIHHJKKL\nIMNJOPL\nIMNNOPQ\nRMSSTTQ\nRSSUUTV",
        "answer": "[[5, 7, 3, 2, 6, 1, 4, 3, 5, 1, 7, 4, 6, 2, 4, 6, 2, 1, 5, 7, 3, 7, 2, 5, 4, 1, 3, 6, 2, 4, 7, 6, 3, 5, 1, 1, 3, 6, 5, 2, 4, 7, 6, 1, 4, 3, 7, 2, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "697",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:15+ B:17+ C:12* D:9+ E:19+ F:3- G:3- H:14+ I:12* J:6* K:7 L:3- M:4 N:5* O:15+ P:12+ Q:4 R:13+ S:3 T:4 U:6 V:5\nAAAABCC\nDDEEBFG\nHDEEBFG\nHHIIJJK\nLMNNJOO\nLPNQRSO\nPPTRRUV",
        "answer": "[[7, 1, 2, 5, 6, 4, 3, 1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 5, 4, 5, 6, 7, 3, 4, 2, 1, 4, 5, 6, 2, 3, 1, 7, 3, 4, 5, 1, 2, 7, 6, 6, 7, 1, 4, 5, 3, 2, 2, 3, 4, 7, 1, 6, 5]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "682",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:12* B:4 C:7+ D:11+ E:90* F:1 G:4 H:7 I:72* J:30* K:7 L:6+ M:17+ N:42* O:70* P:15* Q:2- R:12+ S:12+ T:9+ U:3 V:5+\nABCDDDE\nAFCGHEE\nAIIIJKL\nMMNNJJL\nMONPPQQ\nOORPSST\nURRVVST",
        "answer": "[[2, 4, 5, 7, 3, 1, 6, 6, 1, 2, 4, 7, 5, 3, 1, 3, 4, 6, 2, 7, 5, 4, 6, 7, 2, 5, 3, 1, 7, 2, 3, 5, 1, 6, 4, 5, 7, 1, 3, 6, 4, 2, 3, 5, 6, 1, 4, 2, 7]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "781",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:8+ B:1- C:90* D:210* E:23+ F:10+ G:4 H:420* I:15* J:1 K:2 L:6 M:12* N:7 O:28* P:24* Q:15+ R:3 S:6 T:4 U:1 V:70*\nAABCCDD\nAEBCFDG\nEEHFFIJ\nEKHHHIL\nMMNOOIP\nQQQROPP\nSQTUVVV",
        "answer": "[[4, 1, 2, 6, 3, 7, 5, 3, 7, 1, 5, 2, 6, 4, 7, 4, 5, 2, 6, 3, 1, 5, 2, 3, 7, 4, 1, 6, 2, 6, 7, 4, 1, 5, 3, 1, 5, 6, 3, 7, 4, 2, 6, 3, 4, 1, 5, 2, 7]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "726",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:9+ B:12+ C:70* D:10+ E:9+ F:2 G:18* H:84* I:60* J:4 K:12+ L:3+ M:15* N:42* O:13+ P:5+ Q:7+ R:2- S:7 T:6+ U:12+ V:6*\nAABBCDD\nEABFCGG\nEHIJCKL\nMHIIKKL\nMHNNOPP\nQRSNOTU\nQRVVOTU",
        "answer": "[[4, 1, 5, 6, 2, 7, 3, 7, 4, 1, 2, 5, 3, 6, 2, 6, 3, 4, 7, 5, 1, 3, 7, 4, 5, 1, 6, 2, 5, 2, 6, 7, 3, 1, 4, 6, 3, 7, 1, 4, 2, 5, 1, 5, 2, 3, 6, 4, 7]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    },
    {
        "idx": "734",
        "question": "KenKen is a puzzle where you fill a grid with digits (1 through N for an NxN grid) so that:\n1. Each row and column contains each digit exactly once (Latin square)\n2. Cages (outlined groups of cells) must satisfy the target number using the specified operation (+,-,*,/) Note that - means the larger number minus the smaller number, and / means the larger number divided by the smaller number.\n3. For single-cell cages, just place the target number\n4. Letters (A,B,C...) represent different cages, with constraints listed below each puzzle\nPlease answer in the format [[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, ...]] that directly combine all rows of the solution grid into a single row, with no special characters between rows.\nA:2* B:84* C:72* D:5 E:5 F:1- G:4- H:4/ I:8+ J:16+ K:6+ L:7 M:12* N:28* O:40* P:13+ Q:84* R:8+ S:8* T:2- U:7/ V:1-\nAABBCCD\nEFFBGCH\nIIJJGKH\nLMJNOKK\nPMNNOOQ\nPRSTUUQ\nPRSTVVQ",
        "answer": "[[2, 1, 7, 6, 4, 3, 5, 5, 4, 3, 2, 7, 6, 1, 1, 7, 6, 5, 3, 2, 4, 7, 6, 5, 4, 2, 1, 3, 3, 2, 1, 7, 5, 4, 6, 6, 5, 4, 3, 1, 7, 2, 4, 3, 2, 1, 6, 5, 7]]",
        "rule_id": "16"
    }
]